Chapter 1: The Journalist

Published 10/14/2011

"Recognition code 927, I am a potato."

=ooo=

The journalist carrying a small briefcase looked up at the tall, newly-completed office building, a towering edifice of steel and glass in the heart of London's business district, contemplating his assignment and the man he was to interview today, hopefully. It had not been easy, getting this assignment — his publisher had dealt with an almost overwhelming number of delays, reschedules, and missed appointments, just to get him in to see the man who sat at the top of this monument to the resources of TBC Enterprises, Ltd.

The journalist smiled grimly at the irony of a corporation of this size identified as "limited." TBC Enterprises had been at the vanguard of many business endeavors since its incorporation thirteen years ago. In the past few years its interests had begun to favor the fields of nanotechnology — creating smaller and smaller structures for use in advanced manufacturing and the emerging field of biotechnology. Already the company was one of the leaders in the field in Britain, and it was vigorously pursuing a place of prominence in the global nanotech market.

That was the reason for today's interview. He was here to talk with Harry James Potter-Evans-Verres, the Chairman and CEO of TBC Enterprises. Mr. Potter-Evans-Verres had an impressive resume — he'd graduated from Oxford, where his father, Professor Michael Verres-Evans, was then an eminent professor of biochemistry. He'd had his secondary education at a private school located in Scotland, though details on his time there were sketchy — the name of the school wasn't even known. It was a fact that he'd overcome an unusual nervous system condition, a 26-hour sleep cycle that was known in the medical literature as hypernychthemeral syndrome, or more commonly as non-24 sleep-wake syndrome, which kept him awake two extra hours every day. This had been cited by his office as one of the reasons for the delays in interviewing him. Privately, however, the journalist considered this more of an excuse than a reason.

Entering the building, he took the lift up to the main offices of TBC, which he found took up the entire floor. Stepping from the lift, the journalist looked around, trying to determine where Potter-Evans-Verres' office would be. A short distance from the lift was a counter where a young woman watched him unobtrusively, waiting for him to approach. Well, who was he to disappoint her?

"Good morning," the journalist said, smiling as he stepped up to the counter. "I'm Mr. Monroe, from Singularity Today magazine. I have an appointment with Mr. Harry Potter-Evans-Verres."

The young woman nodded and glanced at a nearby screen. "Yes," she said, after what seemed a longer than necessary wait. "Your appointment was to be over lunch with Mr. Potter — you're an hour early."

"Sorry," Monroe said, smiling apologetically. "I wasn't sure when he took lunch. I decided early was better than late."

The young woman nodded but did not smile. "I'll take to you his office," she said, and led Monroe through a convoluted path of desks, corridors, and cubicles, to a waiting area nearly on the opposite side of the floor. Next to a large, highly polished oaken door sat a pleasant-looking young woman, a redhead this time, who stood at their approach.

"Mr. Monroe, this is Mrs. Thomas, Mr. Potter's personal assistant," she said, introducing them, and the redhead shook his hand politely. Her grip was firm for a woman, Monroe noted, as he took stock of her athletic build.

"Thank you, Debbie," Mrs. Thomas nodded at her, which Debbie returned then walked away. The redhead's eyes followed her for a moment before turning back to Monroe with an apologetic look on her face.

"Terribly sorry for the mix-up," she said, and Monroe gave her a puzzled frown. "Mr. Potter is very busy this morning — he may not have time for your interview, Mr. Monroe."

Monroe sighed softly. Another delay, why was he not surprised? "Would it be a terrible inconvenience if I waited, in case his schedule clears up? My editor may tear what's left of his hair out if he hears we have to delay the interview with Mr. — eh, Potter — another month."

The redhead looked dubious. "I can't guarantee anything, Mr. Monroe. Mr. Potter is quite busy, as I've said, and you may be here for some time before he has any time to spare for you. However," she continued, as my countenance fell, "I see no reason why you cannot wait, if that's your preference."

"Wonderful!" Monroe beamed at her. "That would be fantastic. I can review my notes for the interview while I wait." The journalist looked around. The waiting area was not large, with only a small though comfortable-looking divan and a few plush chairs for furnishings. He looked around for any coffee or tea stations or some kind of refreshment or vending area, but saw nothing. This level of TBC Enterprises appeared to be all business.

The redhead seemed to read his intention. "Would you like something to drink, Mr. Monroe?" she inquired. "We have tea, coffee, and soda."

"A soda would be fine," he told her. "A Pepsi or Coke, whichever you have."

"We have both," she smiled. "Which would you —?"

The polished oak door opened and a man with short black hair that stuck out in several places, with oval wireframe glasses, poked his head out at them, turning to the redhead. "Ginny," he said shortly. "I need the McLaughlin report on my desk by lunch, please." His eyes flicked momentarily to Monroe, but he did not acknowledge his presence.

"Yes, sir," Mrs. Thomas replied. "I'll have that to you in a jiffy."

Harry Potter's head (for that was who the man was, his face was instantly recognizable) disappeared and the door closed. Ginny Thomas's eyes did not quite meet Monroe's as she said, "I'll get that soda —"

"A Pepsi will be fine," Monroe told her, then sat in one of the waiting area chairs, placing his briefcase on the floor next to him. He was smiling smugly to himself. The cat was out of the bag now; there was no way he was going anywhere until Harry Potter walked out of that office and he'd at least tried to talk to him. He sat down on the divan, pulling a small notepad from his jacket. In fact, he might even consider going through the oaken door to see him now, once Mrs. Thomas left her desk for any reason.

But instead of hurrying off to get his drink, she walked around behind her desk, bent over, and came up with a glass of ice and a can of soda. Monroe blinked, wondering if there was a mini-fridge behind the desk he hadn't seen.

She handed him the glass, pouring the fizzing liquid into it from the can. "Mr. Potter will be with you when he becomes available," she said, a bit uncomfortably, then returned to her seat. Monroe watched her for a few minutes, waiting to see whether she would leave her desk or not, but she had gotten on the phone and was talking too softly for him to hear. He finally shrugged, sipped his soda, and began reviewing his questions for the interview.

Time passed slowly, almost tortuously. Monroe kept glancing up at the door to Potter's office, wondering what the man was doing in there, as Ginny at the receptionist's desk made call after call, typing on her computer in between. Other people came and went, dropping off folders or other materials at her desk, though it never seemed to become cluttered. Monroe was watching surreptitiously, trying to discover where she was putting all that paperwork, but the nearest he could figure she was putting it into drawers in her desk — drawers which should shortly be filled to bursting, even assuming they were empty when she began. It was a mystery.

It was only around 11:15 by the time Monroe had reviewed his notes for the third time, and put them away. He checked his watch every few minutes thereafter until it was nearly noon. Would Potter go to lunch, or was he planning on dodging this interview as well, just as he had dodged his past three appointments? Time stretched on, past noon, then twelve-fifteen, then twelve-thirty. Finally, Monroe stood. This was becoming ridiculous. They might throw him out, but he was going into that office.

"What are you —?" Mrs. Thomas began, then stood as Monroe walked past her desk, gripped the doorknob and began to turn it. "Wait, you can't —!"

Monroe ignored her. "Mr. Potter-Evans-Verres," he began, as the door swung aside. "I'm James Monroe and —" and he stopped, looking around the empty room; it seemed larger, somehow, than Monroe would have expected for a corner office. Potter was gone, somehow. The office itself was quite elegant, with a large desk of polished oak, nearly devoid of any paperwork or other materials, and an expensive-looking leather sofa along one wall, with matching end tables at either end. On the other wall was a set of bookcases, filled with books. Monroe could see at a glance that they covered a wide range of subjects — even some with strange titles with words like Transfiguration, Legilimency, and Potioneering. What were those?

For the moment, however, Monroe ignored the books, determined to find where Harry Potter-Evans-Verres had gone. He strode over to the other door and opened it, finding a toilet, shower and wardrobe, but no other exit. Unless he was hiding in the shower (he wasn't — Monroe opened the door to check) there seemed to be no way he could have left the office.

"Mr. Monroe!" Ginny had finally caught up with him. She had a rather stern expression on her face that momentarily gave Monroe pause. "I must ask you to leave Mr. Potter's office or —"

"Or he'll refuse to see me?" Monroe finished. "He's already done that several times now. I'm starting to feel a bit persecuted here, Miss —"

"Mrs. Thomas," she corrected, her voice still stern. "I'm sorry about that, but it cannot be helped. When Mr. Potter is busy he has very little time for anything else."

"I suppose not," Monroe agreed. He was now looking around the room, for any sign of where Harry Potter had gone. "But it would be simpler if he simply declined an interview instead of these cat-and-mouse games he's playing with my magazine. Singularity Today is read by most of the major players in the GNR and MEMS fields, and we thought Mr. Potter wanted an opportunity to put this company in the limelight of the push for the Singularity. If that's not the case then I can write that he declined to be interviewwww…" His voice trailed off.

Monroe felt a momentary disorientation and shook his head, trying to clear the sudden fuzziness he felt. He looked around. The room he was standing in was unfamiliar to him. "What — what was I just saying?" He asked the young woman, a redhead, who was putting something back into a pocket in her skirt, a woman whose name he couldn't remember.

"You were just saying you had to leave for lunch," the woman said smoothly, taking him by the arm and steering him toward the door. "I'm sorry we had to postpone the interview yet again, but these things happen, you know."

"Uh, yes," Monroe said uncertainly, being led out into a small reception area. "That's…too bad, isn't it?"

"One of the girls will escort you to the lift," the young woman said briefly. "Have a pleasant day, Mr. Monroe."

"Um, thanks," Monroe said, still confused. At the edge of the reception area, however he stopped. "There's something I'm supposed to remember…" he muttered, looking around as if doing so would help him recall what it was.

"I'm sure you'll think of it before long," the redhead said, signaling for a girl at a nearby desk to come over. "Debbie here will take you to the lift." She noticed his briefcase next to his chair in the waiting area. "I'll get your briefcase for you."

"Okay," Monroe nodded, then turned to her with a sudden glint in his eyes. "I remember now! Recognition code 927, I am a potato."

Ginny started. "What did you say?" she asked, staring at him in shock, his briefcase still in her hands.

"Recognition code 927, I am a potato," Monroe repeated. "It means I've forgotten something…"

"Where did you hear that phrase?" another voice asked. Monroe and Ginny turned to see Mr. Harry Potter-Evans-Verres striding from his office. He was giving Monroe a very odd look.

Monroe shrugged. "It's just … something I use to remind myself I've forgotten something," he replied. "If I find myself thinking it, it means I've been saying it over and over in my head, to remind myself that I've forgotten something, somehow."

"Do you remember what you forgot?" Potter asked.

"Well, now that I've seen you, sir," Monroe answered. "I recall that we had an interview scheduled for today." He looked at Ginny. "I'm not sure why the young lady here was about to escort me to the exit."

"Lunch is nearly over, anyway," Ginny said quickly. "We should probably reschedule the interview to another time — next week, perhaps?"

Potter was still giving Monroe an odd look. "No," he said, slowly. "Now is as good a time as any. We can have something brought in." His expression suddenly became normal. "Does that sound good to you, Mr. Monroe?"

"Uh, sure," Monroe nodded, still looking a bit confused. "I'm game."

They started toward the office door, but Monroe stopped, turning around. "My briefcase," he said, "I have some release forms for you to sign —"

"We'll take care of them after the interview," Potter said, smoothly. "Ginny, will you keep Mr. Monroe's briefcase at your desk, please?"

"Yes, sir," Ginny nodded. "I'm about to go to lunch, if that's okay."

Potter nodded. "Of course. Have a good lunch." He led Monroe back into his office. He gestured to the leather sofa and Monroe sat down at one end, while he took the other. "Our meals will be ready shortly," he told Monroe, settling back comfortably in the soft leather. "Meanwhile, we can get a little better acquainted. I suppose you know something about me?"

"Oh, yes," Monroe agreed, smiling. "Harry James Potter-Evans-Verres, one of the ten richest individuals in the world, and the Chairman and CEO for the largest closely held corporation in the western hemisphere. You were adopted by the eminent Professor of biochemistry at Oxford, Michael Verres-Evans, and his wife Petunia Evans-Verres, thirty-five years ago after the death of your natural parents, James and Lily Potter, in some kind of car accident, is that correct?"

Harry nodded. "Old news, of course," he said, almost dismissively. "I'm sure that's not what your readers at Singularity Today want to hear about, though."

"A little human interest never hurts," Monroe pointed out. "People would be interested in your sleep-cycle disorder, for example, and how you manage to deal with it with your busy schedule."

"I do okay," Harry replied, shortly. "Before we begin the interview, I do have a few questions for you."

"Really?" Monroe looked bemused. "Questions about the interview, I presume?"

"No," Harry shook his head. "Questions about you."

Monroe laughed nervously. "I thought I was interviewing you, Mr. Potter."

Harry smiled disarmingly. "Think of it as getting to know me better by telling me about yourself," he suggested.

Monroe shifted on the couch, looking thoughtful. "What would you like to know about me?" he asked, a bit of worry in his voice.

Harry held up a placating hand. "Oh, nothing deep or dark, Mr. Monroe! We're just getting a little better acquainted. I think it will help break the ice between us during the interview. For example, how did you come up with that mnemonic you mentioned earlier, that 'recognition code 927, I am a potato'?"

Monroe looked nonplussed for a few moments. "I never thought about it," he said at last. "It's just a mnemonic phrase I use."

"But why that particular phrase?" Harry pressed. "Did you ever hear someone mention it before you used it?"

"Is it important?" Monroe asked in a puzzled tone. "I don't see what your interest —"

There was a soft chime that seemed to come from the middle of the room, although Monroe didn't see anything there that could have made the sound. In the ceiling, perhaps?

Harry stood and moved toward the bookcases. Monroe stood as well, but didn't move; he watched as Harry approached one of the bookcases. Harry reached into the bookcase, and two of the sets of shelves opened outward, revealing a hidden room. "That's pretty cool," Monroe said, sounding impressed.

"Lunch is served," Harry said, gesturing toward the room with a slight bow.

Come into my parlor, was Monroe's sudden impulsive thought, but he smiled at the invitation and entered the room. It wasn't large, but there was a polished cherry dinner table and four chairs in the middle, with a server along one wall. In the far corner there was another door, but it was closed. One the table were two place settings, meals already in place with steam rising from the food. A basket of rolls and two decanters were placed between the plates.

At another gesture from Harry, Monroe sat down in the nearest chair, then glanced at his meal. On his plate was a filet mignon, bacon wrapped around the edge, and cognac sauce on top of it, along with a loaded baked potato and asparagus spears. "Filet mignon," Monroe said as Harry took his seat opposite him. "Very nice. I'm surprised about the baked potato, though."

"I thought you would appreciate a 'meat and potatoes' lunch," Harry said, preparing his napkin. "Considering that you're American."

Monroe looked bemused. "Is my accent that bad?"

"Oh, no," Harry demurred. "But I checked up on you," he added, reaching for a decanter. "Some wine with your steak?"

Monroe nodded, an odd look on his face. As Harry poured the wine, he asked, "Checked up on me? For an interview?" He chuckled nervously. "Did I pass?"

Harry made an "ehh" gesture with his shoulders. "Not altogether," he replied, candidly. "Some details about your past are a bit sketchy."

Monroe leaned forward. "Some details about your past are sketchy as well, sir. For example the school you attended in Scotland between 1991 and 1998 — no one seems to know where it was, exactly, or even what its name was. You went right from there, wherever it was, into Oxford, where you graduated with an Executive MBA and a Masters in Theoretical Physics. In three years."

"It was three and a half years," Harry noted. "I thought you were here to talk about the Singularity, Mr. Monroe."

"So did I," Monroe retorted. "But you've got books in that bookcase out there on stuff like Transfiguration, Legilimency and Potioneering. None of that sounds like theoretical physics, and certainly not like business administration. What's all that about?"

"I read a lot of different subjects," Harry explained, while simultaneously failing to explain. "Besides," he smiled thinly. "You weren't supposed to see those books — I would have removed them before inviting you into my office. But you decided not to wait for my invitation; I'm starting to wonder whether this interview is a good idea or not."

"That's up to you," Monroe said, flatly. "But there will be an article in Singularity Today about you, one way or another."

Harry leaned back against the sofa. "That sounds pretty ominous," he remarked. "A threat?"

"More like a promise," Monroe replied. "My editor wants an article about your company, whether an interview with you is in it or not. If you want to let our readers know what your vision on the Singularity is and the role TBC will play in achieving it, you can agree to the interview. If not, well…" he shrugged.

Harry chuckled briefly. "More like a threat, then," he retorted. "I'll tell you what. I'll give the interview if you'll tell me where you heard that mnemonic you used earlier."

Monroe shook his head. "Mr. Potter, I told you, I don't know where that came from!"

"Ve haf vays uf makingk you tok," Harry sneered, in a bad German accent.

Monroe looked at him strangely. "You're kidding. That sounds like it's right out of Hogan's Heroes." Monroe wondered if Harry even knew the reference.

"I was thinking more like Jack Bauer," Harry replied. "If he was a German. And not very fluent in English. But I'm kidding, anyway — well, at least, mostly kidding. We do have a way to recover the memory."

"What? TMS? Memory drugs?" Monroe looked apprehensive. "I'm not sure I can agree to anything like that."

"It's nothing like that, I assure you," Harry replied. "In fact, I believe you will find it quite interesting."

Monroe swallowed a mouthful of potatoes, then leaned forward. "Well, maybe we should start with that, so I'll know what I'm getting into."

Harry put down his knife and fork, then steepled his fingers in front of him, staring at Monroe pensively. "Why don't we begin with the interview? After we finish our lunch, if you don't mind — I'm a bit hungry."

=ooo=

"Oi! Ginny!"

Ginny Thomas sighed and turned toward the café where her brother, sitting at an outside table, had just rather crudely and unnecessarily yelled to get her attention. "I saw you, Ron, you don't have to shout like that."

"Just wanted to be sure you saw me," Ron said, as she sat down opposite him. There was already a pot pie in front of him, half consumed, and a bottle of butterbeer (which, Ginny assumed, was not his first). "I ordered you a salad, like you said," he added. "But they kept it in the kitchen 'til you got here."

"Great," Ginny snorted. "I've only got thirty minutes today." She slid her wand out of her skirt pocket and flicked it. A small parchment airplane popped out of the end and flew into the café, giving the servers notice she'd arrived.

Ron laughed. "Come on — Harry gives you more time than that for lunch, doesn't he? We've sat here for hours before and you never seemed in a hurry then."

"I have work to do, Ron," Ginny pointed out. "I can't always take however much time I want, just because Harry Potter is my boss. It's not like I'm working in that madhouse you, Fred and George started."

Weasleys' Wizarding Wheezes was a novelty business Fred and George started during their fourth year at Hogwarts, originally as a mail order service. By the end of their fifth year they'd worked out an arrangement with Harry Potter, who lent them enough money to rent out a store front in Diagon Alley and begin selling their wares in earnest. They'd become wildly successful, and after his fifth year Ron joined the business as a junior partner.

"Beats working in an office wearing a business suit ten or more hours a day," Ron retorted. "I couldn't work in an environment like that."

"Yeah, where you actually have to get something done every day," Ginny sniped, as a server brought out her salad and set it down in front of her, then hurried back inside before she got caught in the crossfire. The sometimes-heated brother-and-sister arguments of Ginny Thomas and Ron Weasley had become legend at the café, carrying over from their days at Hogwarts.

Ron looked indignant at her remark. "We get stuff done," he huffed. "I've been testing a box Fred came up with that you can use to record songs off the WWN and play again any time you want, just by tapping it with your wand and saying the name of the song."

Ginny gave him an ironic look. "Muggles have had MP3 players for over 20 years, Ron. Most of the Muggleborns who come to work for us have one."

"Whatever," Ron snorted. "Fred and George think they'll fly off the shelves."

"Sure, everyone who wants to hear Celestina Warbeck sing her Greatest Hits," Ginny laughed. "Maybe Mum will buy one, if Fred and George don't give her one for her birthday."

Ron was silent for a while, playing with his pot pie. He seemed to have lost his appetite. "So how is the Head-Boy-Who-Lived?" he finally asked.

"Still mad about that?" Ginny asked, with a vicious little sneer. "It's been nearly twenty years, Ronald."

"I'm not mad about it," Ron demurred. "It's just a joke, you know? Boy-Who-Lived — Head-Boy-Who-Lived. Get it?"

Ginny rolled her eyes. "I got it back when Harry was made Head Boy over you in your final year. Not easy competing against him, was it?"

Ron was beginning to turn red. "I'm not upset about it," he growled, his tone clearly indicating otherwise. "Can we drop it, please?"

"You brought it up," Ginny pointed out. She leaned forward suddenly. "Oh, I was going to tell you — that writer for that Muggle magazine that's been wanting to interview him for, like, forever, came in again today."

Ron grinned, his anger forgotten. "He's a persistent one, isn't he? What did you do to him now?"

"I Obliviated him."

"Merlin's pants, Gin!" Ron exclaimed. "What for? I thought you said he was harmless!"

"Well," Ginny leaned in closer, lowering her voice. "He sort of threatened to write a bad article about Harry in the magazine, if he didn't agree to be interviewed. I had to do something drastic to make him forget that. But then, something really strange happened."

"Stranger than Ginny Weasley Thomas busting a Memory Charm on a Muggle?" Ron looked amused. "You should have stayed with the Holyhead Harpies instead of going to Muggle business school, sis."

"Well wait'll you hear," Ginny replied, her voice still low. "I'm escorting this guy out of Harry's office, after he broke in trying to find him and I Obliviated him, and he's trying to remember why he's there, and suddenly he says, 'I remember what it was: recognition code 927, I am a potato'."

Ron spit out a mouthful of butterbeer; fortunately most of it missed Ginny. "You're kidding," he said, wiping his mouth as Ginny cursed and grabbed a napkin to wipe off her blouse. "Isn't that the phrase Harry used whenever he forgot something or thought he'd been Obliviated?"

"Yeah, exactly," Ginny said, still dabbing at her blouse. "Next time I'll wait until you're finished drinking! Anyway, I think it freaked Harry out, because he came out of his office and started talking to the guy, and they went back into his office to do the interview."

Ron sat back and laughed heartily. "So he finally got that interview out of Harry, did he?" Ron shook his head, still smiling after he finally stopped laughing. "You said it would rain purple dragon piss on London before he'd do that!"

Ginny pointed a finger at him, her bright brown eyes flashing. "That's enough out of you," she snapped. "It was that damned recognition code!"

Ron stopped grinning and took on a calculating look. "D'you think that writer found out about it somehow, and used it to get Harry's attention?"

Ginny nodded. "It had to have been. Harry knew the Muggle was there, he put his head out of the office and asked me for a report. I think he was just going to let the guy sit there all afternoon. But about half-past twelve the writer suddenly jumped up and just burst into Harry's office."

"Where was Harry?" Ron asked. He lowered his voice. "Under that Invisibility Cloak of his?"

"I think so," Ginny nodded. Her voice was equally quiet. "He couldn't have been in his lab, he wouldn't have — oh, hi!"

Ron looked around quickly and involuntarily caught his breath. Standing nearby was Hermione Granger-Potter, smiling at the two of them. "Hi, Hermione," he said, with an involuntary squeak in his voice that made him wince. "Didn't, uh, see you there."

"I was just inside the café," Hermione smiled, with a nod toward the door she come out of. "I thought I heard you laughing, Ron."

Ron smiled, looking a bit sheepish. Never, ever, if he lived to be a thousand years old, would he ever let on that he'd had (had?) a crush on Hermione Granger in school.

"We've just been talking about Harry," Ginny spoke up. She pushed one of the empty chairs at the table toward Hermione. "Want to join us?" she asked, with a sideways glance toward Ron to gauge his reaction. Never, ever, would she let on she knew about Ron's crush on Hermione. Especially not now, with her and Harry being married and all. It just wouldn't do to stir that pot, no matter how much she, Ginny, might want to.

Hermione looked apologetic. "I have to get back to the Ministry," she said. "I thought I would just get out of the office for a while, get some air. We had such a lovely time celebrating Harry's birthday yesterday I wanted to enjoy some real sunshine for a while."

"Sunshine, huh?" Ron smiled. "That's appropriate."

"What -?" Hermione looked at him blankly for a moment, then laughed softly. "Oh yes. I'd forgotten about that." Which neither Ron nor Ginny believed for a moment — Hermione never forgot anything.

"I should be getting back. You know how demanding the Minister is," Hermione said.

Ginny rolled her eyes. "Yeah, we know," she said, with irony. Ron merely smiled, saying nothing.

"Anyway," Hermione continued. "I'd better be going. I'll tell Harry tonight I saw you today, Ron — he tells me we never see anyone anymore, except Ginny."

"He may be late tonight," Ginny spoke up, as Hermione waved and began to turn away. "He's doing an interview with a magazine journalist right now."

"Really?" Hermione looked surprised. "I thought he was holding out for an interview with one of the online news services, like BBCNet or CNNWorldNet. I wonder what changed his mind?"

"Well…" Ginny gave her a long look. "This journalist used the phrase 'recognition code 927, I am a potato' in Harry's hearing."

Hermione stared at her. "You're joking! Where could a Muggle have heard that?"

"I don't know," Ginny shook her head. "But I think Harry wanted to find out."

"Oh, dear," Hermione said, unconsciously sitting down in the chair Ginny had originally offered her. "This has never happened before. Has it?"

"I don't think so," Ginny said.

"I wonder what he's doing right now?" Hermione said, almost to herself, as she turned her head in the direction of Harry's office building, where TBC Enterprises was located. She had an impulse to Apparate directly into his office, and might have done so, except that (1) you couldn't Apparate into or out of Diagon Alley any more — entrance was strictly through the archway in the Leaky Cauldron's back courtyard, or through a Floo connection or Ministry-authorized Portkey; and (2) the entire floor where Harry's office was located had an Anti-Apparition Jinx on it as well as an Anti-Portkey Hex, and no Floo connections — you had to arrive on another floor then take the elevator up.

"He's probably just giving that bloke a quick, meaningless interview," Ginny offered, sensing Hermione's consternation. "He wasn't really ready for an interview anyway, I think."

"True…" Hermione agreed, absently. "I'd advised him against it — he really needs to talk with one of the larger online news services, magazines don't reach enough people these days. But…that recognition code… I just don't know." She didn't want to say it aloud, but Hermione Granger-Potter was afraid that Chaos had just been let loose in their lives once again.

=ooo=

Author's Notes: The story begins on August 1, 2016, 35 years after Harry's parents were murdered in Godric's Hollow, and 25 years after Harry began studying at Hogwarts. Since the first 77 chapters of Methods of Rationality have not even made it through Year One at Hogwarts, not all of the implied circumstances in this first chapter may pan out as written. The next chapter will be up in three weeks, so this story can alternate with Vampire's Assistant.

Chapter 3: The Interview Pt 2

Updated 11/18/2011

"I've wanted an opportunity to speak like that once more for years now."

"A pensive?" Monroe repeated, frowning. "A pensive what?"

"No, it's P-E-N-S-I-E-V-E," Harry spelled out the word.

"Oh." Monroe finally got it. "It's a pun. Well, I'm not that excited about something you're going to use on me that has the word 'sieve' in it."

Harry was running his hand slowly around the rim of the gray stone bowl. "This was given to me by a good friend, who used it for many years. He stored extra memories in it when he felt his mind was getting a little too cluttered. I've viewed some of them over the years as well. You can use the bowl to view your own memories again at any time, and they get reintegrated back into your mind when you do."

Monroe, who still knew very little about magic, nevertheless immediately perceived a flaw in that design. "What happens if you view someone else's memories? Do they go into that person's mind?"

"No," Harry replied. "You can view other people's memories in perfect detail, and remember them after you've seen them, but each person's memories are unique, and only flow back into the brain they came out of."

Monroe was looking at the bowl apprehensively. "I'm beginning to think this is a bad idea," he muttered. Could this thing suck out all of his memories, leaving him a drooling idiot? Is that what Potter wanted, to suck out his memories of this interview, and steal his recorder, leaving him with nothing to report? Monroe still had his ace in the hole, the secondary recording device hidden within his clothing, as well as his Record-A-Pen in his jacket pocket, but if Potter somehow yanked out the memory that he'd ever gone on this interview, he might not remember to check his backup.

"You did promise," Harry pointed out. "You shook on it."

"Yeah," Monroe retorted. "Without knowing what I was getting into! And then you turned my freaking world upside down!"

"That's what makes a good article," Harry persisted.

"Assuming I don't get locked up in the loony bin for telling it," Monroe came back. "Assuming you even let me out of here without turning me into a zombie. Assuming I wake up tomorrow and don't think this was all just a dream."

"You're so cynical," Harry muttered, reprovingly. "What have you got to lose?"

A lot, Monroe though. Even if he kept his memories of this conversation, even if his Record-A-Pen still had the interview recorded on it, what was to keep his editors at Singularity Today from thinking he was trying to perpetrate a massive hoax on them? What was to keep Potter-Evans-Verres from saying it was all tongue-in-cheek and that he, Monroe, had misunderstood? But —

"More than you seem to think," was all Monroe said. "Will you give me your word that, if you're questioned about this 'magic' you're been showing me, you won't deny everything or say it was just a hoax?"

"Absolutely," Harry nodded. "You have my word as a rationalist."

Great, thought Monroe. That's a real comfort — a rationalist magic-user. "Do you also give your word that you're going to let me out of here without sucking all my memories of this interview out of my head?"

"I promise, unless you ask me to," Harry agreed once again, with a qualification. "Satisfied?"

Unless I ask him to? Monroe thought. Why in the world would I do that? Maybe this rationalist thing of his makes him answer in a hyper-literal viewpoint.

"Not altogether," the journalist admitted. "But…okay. What do we do next?"

Harry took on a detached look, as if he were reciting a well-learned routine. "You should spend a minute or so thinking about the situation — in your case, the phrase 'Recognition code 927 — I am a potato.' When you're sufficiently composed, I will cast a short spell to extract the memories associated with that phrase, and will place them in the Pensieve. After that, you and I will enter the memories and view them."

"Alright," Monroe nodded, then began concentrating on the phrase in question, although there were no memories he could recall explicitly about it. Would that be enough to satisfy Potter, that there was nothing for him to see? It would have to be. "What now?" he asked, a minute or so later.

Harry took out his wand once again. He slowly moved the tip toward Monroe's temple, who watched nervously at its approach. When it finally touched, Harry said, "Pensextraxi!" and drew it slowly away from the journalist, who watched the wand moving away until he saw the tip, whereupon he jerked violently.

A silver strand of — of something was attached to the tip of Harry's wand. "What the hell?" he shouted, but Harry put a hand on his shoulder to stop him from pulling away entirely.

"Don't move…" Harry muttered, continuing to draw his wand away from Monroe's head. "I'm extracting your thoughts." Monroe felt a brief tug, and the silver strand floated free at the tip of Harry's wand. Harry moved his wand over the Pensieve and wiggled it briefly; the strand of silvery stuff wafted downward, landing in the liquid-like substance in the bowl and seemed to dissipate. "Okay," Harry announced. "We're ready to go."

He pointed to the Pensieve. "Do what I do," he told Monroe. "We're going to lean over and slowly put our faces into the bowl. Don't worry," he added, at Monroe's expression. "It's not liquid, so you won't drown. Be prepared for a falling sensation, however."

"Falling?" Monroe looked startled. "What's going to happen to us?"

"Nothing," Harry assured him. "When we enter the memories we'll be floating down into them. You and anyone else associated with these memories will be there, but we won't be able to interact with them. We'll only see and hear what you saw and heard — the Pensieve does not read your inner thoughts. Are you ready?"

"No," Monroe said, resigned. "But let's get it over with."

Both men faced each other over the stone basin, then slowly lowered their faces toward the silvery liquid, Monroe watching Harry's actions carefully. As his nose touched the stuff, Monroe felt himself suddenly jerked forward into a cold blackness that seemed to spin him around and around violently, yet the sensation was merely unsettling, not painful.

Suddenly the blackness resolved into a place unfamiliar to the journalist, as he landed without the sensation of hitting the ground in a vast, brightly-lit room. He looked around. Harry was standing next to him, his expression inscrutable.

"Where are we?" Monroe asked him.

"You don't know?" Harry asked in reply, his tone unreadable. "Look around, see if you recognize anything. Or anyone."

Monroe glanced around him. The room he was in was very large and very open, longer than it was wide, but not by much, and four magnificent wooden tables ran down its length, two on each side of where they were standing. There were children seated at each of the tables, all of them eating or talking or reading; they must be at some kind of boarding school, Monroe decided, and was about to turn and ask if this was the school Harry attended when a glance upward made him stop and gape in awe.

Above them were thousands of candles, not suspended from chandeliers, but floating in midair! And beyond the candles… the morning sky itself was visible, a vast canopy stretching over the entire room.

"Kind of amazing, isn't it?" Harry's voice said in his ear, and Monroe nodded mutely. He had never seen anything like this. It must be the school Potter attended in Scotland! A magic school! But why would his thoughts bring them here? Had they gotten into one of Harry's memories by mistake?

Just then a boy ran past them, a boy with unruly black hair that reminded Monroe of Potter's untamed hair, and practically leapt into a seat at the table nearest them, wedging apart two boys; one of them glared at his rudeness, but the other boy just kept on eating — his plate was filled with eggs, sausage and fried potatoes, Monroe saw — similar to his own favorite breakfast as a youth.

The black-haired boy had grabbed something off his belt and was reaching into it. It was a small, leathery pouch, Monroe saw, and he pulled a small piece of paper out of it and consulted it briefly, then grabbed an entire pie that was sitting nearby and stuffed it into the pouch. As Monroe watched, fascinated, the mouth of the pouch expanded so the pie could fit inside, then shrunk back to its original diameter with a small burp.

"Hey!" a girl with curly brown hair looked at the black-haired boy indignantly. "That's everyone's dessert! You can't just take one whole pie and put it in your pouch!"

But even as she was saying this, the boy had grabbed another pie and fed it into his pouch. "I'm not taking one pie, I'm taking two," he informed her. He spun around and stood. "Sorry everyone, gotta run now!" Several other people shouted at him, outraged at his actions, but he ignored them, trotted down to the end of the tables and exited the large set of double doors that led out of the room.

Monroe glanced back at the empty spot where the boy had momentarily seated himself. The piece of paper he'd pulled from his pouch was still on the table, and the boy who had continued eating his breakfast idly picked it up and was looking at it. Monroe leaned over the boy's shoulder to read what was written on it.

On the note was a handwritten message, along with several annotations made to one side. The annotations were some type of list.

Two candy bars (small).
First note (-1 attempt)
Empty box of snack bars
Second note (1 point spent)
Six snack bars.
Third note (-20 points, bad guess! And -2 pajama points)
Fourth note (1 point spent) plus underwear comment
Cherry pie (first throw)
Blueberry pie (second throw, with warning note)
Fifth note (+10 style, -1 million for good thinking) 2 turns left
Sixth note (appeal failed, -1 billion for asking the wrong questions)
Final note, failure and minus infinity points.

The note itself was shorter.

Dear Me,
Please play the game. You can only play the game once in a lifetime.
This is an irreplaceable opportunity.
Recognition code 927, I am a potato.

Yours,
You.

"Oh." Monroe said. He didn't understand the note, but there was the mnemonic code Harry had questioned him about, clearly written there. He stood up and looked at Harry, who had been looking over the boy's other shoulder.

"Welp," the Harry standing beside him said, in a monotone. "Now we know." Though that fact clearly did not seem to satisfy him.

"I don't get it," Monroe said, bewildered. "Who is this kid? What's he doing in this place?"

"That's what I'd like to know, too," Harry said, evenly. "We're seeing these things from his perspective, and these are your extracted thoughts. Therefore it follows that this boy is you."

=ooo=

"Don't give me that!" Malfoy snapped, glaring at Dean Thomas's image on his white screen — another one of Potter's improvements to wizard communications over the past few decades, though not one of his original ideas. "Potter never intended to give that Muggle an interview in the first place — now you're trying to say he's taking extra time?"

"You know how his mind works," Dean shrugged.

No, Malfoy thought. I don't know how his mind works, not anymore, but instead he said, "Just let us know when he finally leaves the building, Mr. Thomas."

"I'm sure you'll know the moment he does, Head Auror," Dean replied, acidly. The connection terminated.

Draco Malfoy sat back in his chair. Of course they would know — they had Harry's building closely monitored, inside and out. The only place they weren't authorized to surveil was the Potter private residence on the top three floors of the building, occupied by Potter and his wife, Hermione Granger-Potter.

When the Muggle finally emerged from the building, Aurors would close in and quickly transport him to headquarters, where he could be adequately debriefed and properly Obliviated, if necessary. If any of Potter's schemes of informing the Muggles of the Wizarding world were somehow bound up in this Muggle's head, they would be removed and false memories would be implanted in their place—memories that were not very complimentary of Harry Potter's Muggle business ventures, if Draco had his way. Potter was becoming much too powerful in the Muggle world; someone had to apply some leverage there. For the Wizarding world it was already too late, Draco knew.

Harry's power and prestige in the Wizarding world was already a foregone conclusion. By the time he had left Hogwarts he had already owned most of Diagon Alley's businesses, either directly or through what he'd called "investments" with the business owners themselves. Even shops in Knockturn Alley had not been safe from his reach — the owners there were known to be even more interested in money than many of the other businesses in Diagon Alley, and Harry had preyed upon that greed to his advantage.

Potter also had more influence over the goblins of Gringotts than even Draco's father wielded these days, and that took real wealth, not the paltry fortune Potter's birth parents would have left him, a sum known to Lord Malfoy at the time, though he had not told Draco until years later. Draco did not know how Harry had come into such money except that it likely had to do with Harry's being a "scientist," as he'd liked to call himself while at Hogwarts. While Draco had learned the techniques of science from Harry, and had adopted a few of its principles, his most important lessons had always come from his father.

And so, adhering to those techniques, and to the traditions the Malfoys had followed for centuries, he was now the second most powerful person in Wizarding Britain — the Head Auror for the Ministry of Magic, answerable only to the Minister herself. Who, a small voice in Draco's head reminded him, was married to Harry Potter, the real most powerful person in Wizarding Britain. Did that leave him at Number Three? Draco was inclined to think "no" — his influence in the Ministry, along with his father's influence in the Wizengamot, could change the very laws themselves, if need be. Someday, Draco knew as well, his father would pass on, making him Lord Malfoy, and this stepping-stone job as Head Auror would be put behind him, for real power. Until then, he would continue to win friends and influence people here in the Ministry, preparing for that day.

Besides, who knew? Draco allowed himself a small smile. If something happened to Granger-Potter's popularity and she was sacked, he might actually find himself positioned to move into the Number One spot in Wizarding Britain's government. Wouldn't that be something, along with his father's power to help him change the face of the nation? Draco basked in the glow of that happy thought for some time before taking out his wand and tapping the white screen, resuming his monitoring of Potter's building.

=ooo=

"Me?" Monroe gasped. He leaned down until he was level with the boy's face, looking at him carefully. He did look familiar, the journalist had to admit. "But how could I be —"

"We can continue this in my workshop," Harry said, and they both floated upward into darkness. Monroe felt himself spinning end for end somehow, then stood up from the stone basin he had been leaning over before things went surreal, looking at Harry, who was regarding him with a calculating look.

"How could I be at that school?" Monroe asked again. "That was the school you attended, I assume?"

"Yes," Harry confirmed. "It was. Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry. Which makes this an interesting problem. I've been trying to remember who that boy was. He was sitting at the Ravenclaw table, but he wasn't any of my dorm mates —"

"What do you mean by 'the Ravenclaw table'?" Monroe asked. "The tables had names?"

"Hogwarts was divided into four Houses," Harry explained. "Ravenclaw, Gryffindor, Hufflepuff and Slytherin. Students were Sorted into one of the Houses when they first arrived at school."

"Which one were you sorted into?" Monroe asked him.

Harry chuckled softly. "I was something of a special case. The Sorting Hat — it's an old wizard's hat that's placed on the head of each student in order to sort them —"

"This hat puts in one of these 'Houses,' then?" Monroe wanted to know.

"In a way," Harry agreed. "It mostly uses the student's own inclinations and desires when it does so, though — anyway, it wanted to sort me into either Hufflepuff or Gryffindor. Those Houses are mostly known for having hardworking, loyal and brave students, by the way. It thought I'd be too isolated in Ravenclaw, and in Slytherin — well, in Slytherin I'd be under a lot of pressure to be ambitious, to get ahead. Either way, it was afraid I'd end up as a Dark Lord if I ended up in one of those last two Houses."

"A Dark Lord?" Monroe echoed. "Do I want to know what that is?"

Harry didn't answer for a moment, just looked at the Muggle standing across the Pensieve from him. There wasn't much point to telling him what a Dark Lord was; he wasn't going to remember any of this conversation, anyway — by his own choice, of course. Harry certainly wasn't going to tell Monroe how close he had come to becoming a Dark Lord himself over the past 25 years. And only villains in stories revealed their plots, especially stupid ones. Harry was not stupid, much less a villain.

"You probably don't," he said. "Anyway, you've fulfilled your part of the bargain, so the interview is over. You can leave."

"Leave?" Monroe looked around the workroom. What other devices like that lightsaber were in this room, unrevealed to the world? How vast was this magical business, that men like Potter were a part of the normal world and they didn't even know about them? What would the world be like if everyone had access to magic? Would it be part of the Singularity? That much seemed almost inevitable if men like Potter were working toward it as well as men like Ray Kurzweil, Nick Bostrom, Aubrey de Grey, and Eliezer Yudkowsky? "Don't you have any questions for me? Aren't you curious about who that boy at the table was?"

"Oh, yes, I'm very curious about who that was," Harry agreed. "But they were your memories, and you don't remember how you got there, do you?"

"No," Monroe admitted, after a moment.

"Then the memories surrounding the ones you remember were probably Obliviated," Harry reasoned. "Otherwise we would have seen the ones showing why you were there."

"But who would have done that?" Monroe asked, a hint of desperation in his voice.

"Any competent wizard performing a Memory Charm knows better than to leave a trail back to himself," Harry answered. "I didn't recognize that kid, either — he might have been in one of the other Houses, but I thought I'd seen the faces of every first year when we were all Sorted, and I don't remember his. He might've been a second- or third-year, but I don't ever remember seeing his face again at the school."

"How many students attend Hogwarts each year?" Monroe asked, eager for any information about the magical world.

"It varies from year to year," Harry told him. "But it was around 800 students total, on average."

"That's a lot of kids to keep track of," Monroe pointed out.

"Most of the professors there knew everyone by name," Harry said. "At least, the ones who taught the most important subjects did."

"And what were those subjects?" Monroe prompted.

"I'd love to tell you all about them," Harry said, seriously. "But…I think it's a pretty foregone conclusion that the Ministry is going to pick you up the minute you walk out of here."

"The Ministry?" Monroe exclaimed. "What do they know about all this?"

"Not the boys on Downing Street," Harry told him. "Though the Muggle Prime Minister is aware of our existence. I mean, he's aware that the Ministry of Magic exists and is run by people who can use magic."

Monroe looked blankly at him. Then, "Well, I should have guessed there'd be some kind of magical government running things. But what do they want with me? As you say, I'm just a Muggle."

"They're concerned that I might have told you about our magical society."

"But you did tell me!" Monroe's voice had gone shrill. "Why'd you do that, if you knew they were going to questions me?"

"I thought I might be able to slip you by," Harry shrugged. "But no such luck this time — they were watching to see how long you spent in the building, and it's been long enough to arouse suspicion."

"Well that's just great!" Monroe looked super pissed off. He spun angrily away from Harry, staring across the workshop. "What are they going to do to me?"

"Probably just Obliviate you and send you on your way," Harry speculated. As Monroe sighed with relief, he added, "Though they might decide to make an example of you to me…"

"An example?" Monroe turned slowly to face Harry again. "What does that mean?"

"Well, they can't really do anything to me," Harry explained. "Too much political fallout if the Minister's spouse gets put in Azkaban, you see. So they might put you in prison, as a deterrent to me trying to inform anyone else in the Muggle world about our existence."

"You're saying they'd put ME in jail to teach YOU a lesson?" Monroe said, disbelievingly.

"Something like that."

"That is just so wrong on so many levels," Monroe muttered in a plaintive voice.

Harry shrugged. "It's the way many in the Ministry think, though."

Monroe was beginning to look scared. "So how do I get out of this?"

"Out of having the magical cops take you in?" Harry looked amused. "Oh, you're not getting out of that, amigo. If they want you, they're going to take you."

"Okay —" Monroe was rubbing the back of his neck, almost ready to panic. "— okay — I mean, how do I beat the rap?"

"Well…" Harry looked unhappy. "I guess I could Obliviate the memories you have, if you're willing to erase your recording of the interview."

Monroe now looked unhappy as well, but took the Record-A-Pen out of his jacket pocket. "I can do that," he said, sliding aside the pocket clip and manipulating some small controls that were revealed. He held up the small LCD screen to Harry, showing him 0MB Recorded displayed on it. "It's gone."

Harry gave him a skeptical look. "Is that the only recording device you had on you, Monroe?"

Monroe stared at him for several seconds, then shook his head. He reached down to the bottom of his jacket, running a finger along one edge; the seam parted and another small recording device fell out. "I don't know if they would have found this, though," he said, holding it up for Harry to inspect it. "It would have registered as an RFID chip on any scanner."

"Except for any magical scanner," Harry said, looking at it closely. "Very clever, though. You'd better erase it, too."

Monroe nodded and used a ball-point pen tip to press on a small depression in the device. A few moments later it beeped twice, signifying the memory was cleared. Monroe dropped it into his jacket pocket.

"That's it," he said, spreading his arms. "I'm clean, except for what's in my head."

"Okay," Harry said. "Follow me." Harry led the journalist back through the workroom, to the door they had originally come through, where Harry's dining area was. As they both stepped through, the door slid closed and seemed to disappear behind them, as if it had never been there at all.

"This should do," Harry said, taking out his wand. "Sorry about this, James," he nodded in respect to the journalist. "I enjoyed our talk, short as it was." His wand came up —

"Maybe we can meet again," Monroe suddenly suggested. "You know — have another go at this, maybe?"

Harry gave him a grin. "We'll see," he said. "But I wouldn't hold my breath, if I were you." His wand tip made small but complicated motions even as Monroe frowned at his final remark.

"What do you mean —?"

"Obliviate!"

Monroe's expression went slack, his eyes unseeing. Harry held the wand on him as he circled around behind the frozen figure.

"We had a nice interview," Harry said softly, speaking into Monroe's ear. "Even though you forgot to turn on your recording device. I invited you to lunch in my private dining room, filet mignon with a baked potato and vegetables, with wine; you drank a bit more than you should have, and I let you lie down for a while on a couch. When you wake up, you'll be ready to leave, and we'll exit back into my office and out into the waiting area, where you'll get your briefcase from Ginny and leave.

"You will not remember being Obliviated, or even discussing it with anyone. You will not remember the recognition code nor where you learned of it, however you might have come to be at Hogwarts." Though that was something Harry intended to pursue, once the Muggle was gone. "Now, awaken."

Monroe blinked, then yawned. He turned to Harry. "Thanks for letting me take a nap, Mr. Potter. I'm sorry to have imposed on you. And thanks for lunch, it was wonderful!"

"I'm happy to have met you, Mr. Monroe," Harry smiled. "And I hope you can do something with our interview, even if your recording device missed it all."

"Oh, it was entirely my fault," Monroe pointed out. He reached out a hand, and they shook. "Good luck with your efforts on the Singularity, Mr. Potter."

Harry nodded, and the Muggle turned, exiting through Harry's office door, where Ginny passed him his briefcase and one of the other secretaries, Debbie, waited to bring him down to the ground floor lobby.

Ginny came into the room afterwards. She said nothing, but with her hand held close to her chest, made a small finger-snapping gesture. Harry nodded slightly.

"Did you have fun?" Ginny asked aloud, knowing that none of the Ministry's surveillance spells were working at the moment.

"More or less," Harry said, a bit distractedly. "I almost feel sorry for the guy — he probably won't get home tonight, if Malfoy is as thorough with him as usual. But —" he shrugged "— he asked for it, coming in here and demanding an interview and all."

"And saying the secret words," Ginny added, matter-of-factly.

"That, too."

=ooo=

Monroe was humming an old movie tune as he left Potter's building, turning toward the Underground Station that had brought him here earlier today. The interview could have gone better, at least as he remembered it, but it still wasn't bad. If he got back to his computer right away and began shaping his recollections into words, he might recapture most of the conversation.

Hmm hmm hmm, hmm-hmm-hmm, hmm-hmm-hmm,
Hmm hmm hmm Hmm-hmm-hmm, hmm-hmm-hmm.
Hmm Hm-Hmm Hmm Hmm Hm-hm-hm, hmm hmm, hmm hmm hm-hm-hm, hmm hmm, hm-hm-Hmm, hmm-Hmm-Hmmm,
Hmm Hm-Hmm Hmm Hmm Hm-hm-hm, hmm hmm, hmm hmm hm-hm-hm, hmm hmm, hm-hm-hmm, hm-hm-hmmm.

If Monroe had been aware of the title of the song he was humming, he might have had more of a sense of foreboding, of imminent DOOM.

A half-block from the Underground entrance, he was suddenly bookended by two large men in long, black trenchcoats, who chivvied him into a nearby alley before he could so much as protest.

Each man was over six feet in height, and they were well away from the main street before Monroe regained enough wit to become indignant at their actions.

"What's going on? If it's money you want I'm afraid I have very little —"

"Da boss wants ta speak wit' youse, so shaddup an' come along peaceful-like," one of them growled in a voice that seemed too soft for such words. He looked over Monroe's head at the other man, grinning broadly. "You know," he said, in a much more erudite tone, "I've wanted an opportunity to speak like that once more for years now."

"Where are you two taking me?" Monroe demanded. "I want to see some iden—" He suddenly slumped as the other man pressed a wand into his ribs and whispered a single word. The two large men stopped, holding up the unconscious journalist.

"That shut him up pretty quickly," the first man said. "What'd you use?"

"Somnium," the second man said. "It's not very powerful, so it's suitable for Muggles."

The first man nodded agreement. "Da boss — I mean, Mr. Malfoy — wants us back at the Ministry as soon as possible after we pick this one up. Do you have the Portkey?"

"Of course, Mr. Crabbe." The second man brought out a small scrap of parchment. "It will activate upon the touch of three individual's fingers," he said.

Crabbe snorted. "It sounds like Mr. Malfoy didn't expect us to fail, did he?"

Mr. Goyle grinned. "Against a Muggle? I should think not." He maneuvered the sleeping Muggle's hand so one of his fingers touched the parchment he held, then Mr. Crabbe reached out and put a finger on it as well. There was a sudden whirl of color and wind, and the alleyway was empty once again.

Chapter 4: Interrogation 101

Updated 12/02/2011

"You know, love, we are alone in here. You can say 'piss' if you want to."

When Monroe awoke he found himself sitting in a small, nondescript room, his arms resting on the arms of the chair he was seated in. There was nothing else in the room but a large mirror on one wall, which Monroe immediately pegged as "two-way." There was no clock, no table, no other chairs, It was, he supposed, a typical interrogation room in a typical London police station, which he had fortunately never been in before (until now).

The first question Monroe planned for his would-be interrogators was, Why am I here? He'd tried to ask the two men who'd taken him in, but before he could get any answers out of them he was already here. Had he passed out, or had they done something like taser him? He couldn't remembering being hit with an electric shock, though.

Time passed, how much, Monroe couldn't say; his watch was no longer on his wrist. He'd tried to check his jacket pocket for his Record-A-Pen, but his arms were affixed to the chair, somehow, and he couldn't pull them loose. Whatever was going on here, he was just going to have to wait until they came to him.

Two large men entered the room, and Monroe sat up straight (at least, as much as he could, considering his arms were stuck to the chair), watching them warily. The larger of the pair had brown hair and seemed to wear a perpetual sneer on his face. The smaller man (though not smaller by much) had a crew cut and his dark hair looked coarse and bristly. He regarded Monroe with pinched expression, as if he would have preferred being in a badly maintained restroom rather than where he was. They were both dressed in black overcoats, shirts and pants with shiny black boots.

The larger of the two men seemed to be in charge. He positioned himself in front of Monroe while the other one stood off to one side, watching them. Both of them were regarding him with calculating looks. Monroe, for his part, could only stare impassively back at them until one of them decided to speak. It didn't take long.

"What," the big (okay, bigger) man, in a deep but surprisingly soft voice asked, "do you know about magic?"

"Magic?" Monroe gave him an inquiring, puzzled look. "What do you mean — like, 'Hey Rocky, watch me pull a rabbit out my hat?' magic, or what?"

The big man hesitated, confused. "Er — what?"

"Never saw that show?" Monroe wondered. "Maybe they never showed it here in England."

The two men looked at one another. "Never mind that," the big man said, irritably. "You know why you're here, doncha?"

"Not really," Monroe replied. "I just got out of an interview with Harry Potter-Evans-Verres and was on my way home to write it up, and you two came out of nowhere, knocked me out, and I woke up here. I'm still waiting to hear what you want."

"What we want," the other behemoth said, in a threatening tone. "Is for you to tell us what you an' Potter talked about."

"The S-Singularity," Monroe answered, hesitantly. He had a feeling these guys would have no idea what that was.

He was right. The two men looked at one another again. "Are we supposed to know what that is?" the smaller man asked.

"Nah," the bigger man said, dismissively. "Mr. Malfoy says it's some Muggle thing Potter's working on. He says it's not going to happen for a long time, if ever."

"How does Mr. Malfoy know that?" Monroe asked, wondering who this Malfoy character was.

"'Cause Mr. Malfoy's Head Auror an' he knows loads of stuff a stupid Muggle like you don't," the smaller man snarled.

"But I know what the Singularity is," Monroe replied, emboldened by their ignorance. "And apparently neither of you do. So both of you are more stupid than a Muggle." Whatever that was.

Both men stiffened. "This 'Singularity' nonsense is Muggle fairy tales!" the larger man snarled.

Monroe almost laughed. "It seems to me that you're just taking this Mr. Malfoy's word, and not trying to find out for yourself."

"It ain't our job to find out for ourselves!" the other man said. "It's our job to —"

"It's your job to do what you're told!" a new voice interjected. Both men looked around. Standing in the door was a tall, thin blond man, his hair flowing freely about his head. He had pale, sharp features, and was dressed similarly to the first two men. "I didn't tell you to question the detainee."

"We thought we'd warm him up for you, Boss," the smaller man muttered. "He doesn't want to talk —"

"Don't call me 'Boss,'" the blond snapped. "And of course he doesn't want to talk! Both of you —" he jerked a thumb at the door. "— get out. I'm going to talk to him alone. Go file your daily reports — it'll be time for us to go home soon."

Both of the behemoths nodded, looking cowed by this new man's presence, and quickly beat a path to the door. After they were gone, the blond man stood regarding Monroe for several minutes. Monroe tried to ignore it and wait him out, but the silence, after the badgering he'd endured from his previous interrrogators, was unnerving.

Finally the man spoke. "You are James Monroe, is that correct?"

"Yes," Monroe answered. "Are you going to tell me why I'm here?"

"Oh, I think you know why you're here," the blond man answered. "You were just conducting an interview with Harry Potter-Evans-Verres, were you not?"

"I was," Monroe agreed. Based on what the other two men had said, it seemed like they though he'd talked with Potter about something they weren't supposed to discuss. "We weren't supposed to discuss the Singularity?"

The man snorted derision. "We don't care about that, it's Mu — it's pseudoscientific claptrap."

"You mean 'Muggle' claptrap?" Monroe asked. "The other two guys used that word a lot."

The blond was silent for several moments. He appeared to be engaged in a silent debate with himself. "You don't need to worry about that," he said at last. "I just need to know what you and Potter talked about."

"The Singularity, like I said." Monroe was beginning to feel irritated; these men, whoever they were (because it was now clear they weren't the regular police) were clearly dismissive of the idea of the Singularity. Which was not an entirely new idea to Monroe — people dismissed the idea all the time, though less lately than they had in past years. "You may not like the idea but it's a lot more mainstream now than it was even five years ago."

"I doubt that Potter is really interested in it these days," the blond man retorted. "He's got more pressing concerns. It doesn't matter anyway —" he waved a hand dismissively. "Perhaps we should discuss the phrase that got you into the interview in the first place."

"What phrase is that?" Monroe looked puzzled. "'Mr. Potter, may I please have an interview?'"

"No." The blond looked annoyed. "Recognition code 927, I am a potato."

Monroe gave him a blank stare. "I've never heard that phrase before."

"Really?" The blond man wore a triumphant sneer. "How do you explain this, then?" He pointed to the mirror on the wall in front of them, and it shimmered, becoming a view screen. Onscreen was Monroe and the redhead he'd met outside Harry Potter's office, a Mrs. Thomas. As he watched, the woman was trying to steer him into leaving when he mentioned the line the blond man said he'd used.

"Well?" the blond man looked expectantly at him, when the image faded.

"That looked like me," Monroe admitted. "But I don't remember saying that."

The man was nodding slowly. "So…Obliviation, probably. Not that unexpected, really — he must have realized we were watching, dammit!"

"What's 'Obliviation'?" Monroe asked, apprehensive that it would be just what the word sounded like.

"Oh —" the blond man shrugged carelessly. "He made you forget some of your conversation with him. Perhaps most of it. I could test that, but it doesn't seem necessary."

"How would you test it?" Monroe asked. If Potter had made him forget things, he really wanted to find out what he'd forgotten, if possible.

The blond man gave him a calculating look. "I'd give you a few drops of Veritaserum," he said. "A few drops and you would truthfully tell everything you know about your conversation with Potter."

"I've never heard of this 'Veritaserum,'" Monroe said, slowly. "Obviously it's some kind of truth drug, but why would the British police use that kind of stuff? It sounds more like something MI5 would have. James Bond stuff."

"Police?" The blond man was giving him that calculating look again. "Oh, no…we're not the police, Mr. Monroe. We're the double secret police."

=ooo=

At that same time a few miles away, Harry Potter-Evans-Verres was sitting in the living room of his private residence reading today's copy of the Daily Prophet. Late afternoon was usually the first chance he got to read the wizarding newspaper, before Hermione got home and they either made dinner or went out to dine somewhere.

Harry's living room was similar to the same room in his parent's house — it was lined with bookshelves, upon which were thousands of books. Unlike his parents, however, these bookshelves held many more books than any normal bookshelf could — the result of Extension and Retrieval Charms that would allow stacks of books behind the rows showing to come forward for perusal and selection.

And those books, as numerous as they were (Harry would sometimes idly estimate to himself that his living room library contained almost 100,000 books, more than in the Hogwarts Library when he left the school) there were other libraries where he kept even more books, many of which would have most wizards gasping in surprise if they could read them. However, they were unreadable—a side-effect of a very old spell, the Interdict of Merlin, which made information about powerful spells written down by wizards unintelligible to anyone but the original author. Harry had been collecting books such as those from libraries and individual wizards across Britain for the past 20 years, beginning even before he left Hogwarts. One never knew when the Interdict might be lifted and those books could become readable by anyone.

For now, however, Harry had found an article about Hogwarts new Headmistress, Pomona Sprout, who was taking over for Minerva McGonagall, who had recently decided to retire after her 90th birthday. Headmistress Sprout had been approved by the governors of the school and today, August first, would be her official first day as Headmistress. She had announced at the ceremony that the position of Herbology Teacher had been accepted by Justin Finch-Fletchley.

Harry sighed softly to himself. It was a shame Neville wasn't around; he was a very good Herbology student — he would have made an excellent professor if he hadn't… well, there was no use dwelling on the past, Harry decided.

Harry heard the front door to their residence open. The "front door" actually led to a small waiting area containing a few chairs and access to an elevator that ran exclusively between the waiting room and the ground floor of the building, accessible to someone who could Apparate or Portkey into the room. And only Hermione (and a few others) knew the special unlocking spell that would open the door leading into their residence.

"I'm home!" Harry heard her call out a few seconds later. She walked into the living room, smiling as she saw him, and Harry put down the paper to return her greeting.

"Hello, love," he said. "Just now finishing work?"

"Yes," she nodded, sitting down in a nearby chair. "Very busy at work today," she sighed, sitting back wearily in the chair and closing her eyes. Once upon a time Hermione had rarely shown her tiredness to Harry; she tried to look tireless in front of him for much of the first year they knew one another, back at Hogwarts. Now, he hardly ever saw her when she wasn't tired or busy with work. It was a pretty sure bet she wouldn't be interested in making dinner for them tonight.

"Do you fancy dinner at Mary's Place tonight?" Harry asked, naming one of the finest restaurants in Diagon Alley. Without opening her eyes, Hermione shrugged slightly. "My treat," Harry added, and Hermione smiled without opening her eyes. It was something of a joke between them that whenever Hermione wanted to go to Mary's Place, Harry would suggest the Ministry should pick up the tab since she usually did nothing but discuss Ministry business while they were there.

Perhaps tonight would be different. Harry hoped so, because he didn't want to get into a discussion about what the "official Ministry position" on his interview with the Muggle journalist Monroe was. "Dean told me Ginny said she and her brother Ron saw you in Diagon Alley at lunch."

Hermione opened her eyes to look at him. "When did he tell you that?"

"Just before I left work earlier today. They were making plans to go to dinner and she mentioned it to him."

"How did your interview go?" she asked.

"Well enough," he said, his expression not changing beyond a slight shrug of his shoulders. "I suppose it'll keep up the Muggle interest in the Singularity."

"What did you think of your interviewer?" Hermione asked, closing her eyes once again. "Was he glad to finally get to see you?"

"Oh, I suppose," Harry replied. "Even though he burst into my office without knocking, trying to catch me off-guard."

"I'm not sure I could blame him," Hermione commented. "You've been giving him and that magazine of his the runaround for months now. Why did you give him that interview, Harry?" She looked over at him, her expression curious. "You've been telling me amount of exposure they could give you wasn't worth your while."

Harry was silent a moment. "Just — something he said," he replied, finally.

"What was that?" Hermione pressed. She already knew, of course, but she wanted to give her husband the chance to tell her by his own choice.

"He knew…the recognition code phrase I used as a kid," Harry said at last.

"Really?" Hermione feigned surprise, feeling slightly guilty for doing so. It was hard keeping secrets from her husband, but even he couldn't be privy to all the secrets the Ministry kept — especially ones that involved him. "Did you find out how he knew it?"

Harry wasn't looking at her. "Yeah, eventually," he muttered.

Hermione looked at him a long moment. "Are we going to need to reserve the 'Room' at Mary's Place tonight, to talk about it?"

"Why do you ask that?" Harry looked at her then, with the most innocent face. It was never a good sign, she knew, when he looked that innocent.

"I take it that's a yes," she shook her head wearily. "I'll make the reservation."

=ooo=

Mary's Place contained a special, separate dining area known as "Mary's Room." This room, as Harry had once been told, was used by two kinds of people: the first sort were engaged in illicit dalliances, and the second sort led interesting lives.

He and Hermione were now seated in that room, perusing their menus as the waitress, a young woman neither of them recognized, waited for them to make up their minds. Harry, who had already eaten filet mignon earlier that day, decided on roasted Diracawl breast in Dirigible Plum sauce, with Sopophorus potatoes au gratin and carrots. Hermione, after intense internal debate, settled on a vegetable lasagna and a salad. The young woman bowed respectfully and silently left the room, closing the door behind her.

Hermione took out her wand, pointing it to the bolt on the door, which slid into place with a metallic clack. She then spoke half a dozen wards, enough to sufficiently protect them from any scyring of the room by anyone capable of wizardry of lesser caliber than, say, Albus Dumbledore himself.

"So," she said, putting away her wand. "What went on between you and that journalist, James Monroe?"

"Mostly just that interview," Harry answered. "He didn't remember where he'd heard the recognition code."

"And you were satisfied with that?" Hermione asked, skeptically. She knew Harry better than that. "What would Dean say about it, if I asked him?"

"Dean doesn't know anything," Harry said, truthfully. "Ginny heard the guy say it, though, after she'd already Obliviated him when he broke into my office."

"Ginny Obliviated someone?" Hermione looked shocked.

"It was within Ministry guidelines," Harry said, in a placating manner. "He might have noticed that my office is… a bit too big for where it is on that floor."

"Never mind that, then," Hermione dismissed that issue. "Do you know that Monroe is still at the Ministry, even now, being questioned by Malfoy?"

Harry frowned. "It sounds like Malfoy's just trying to twist my tail. Monroe doesn't know anything."

"He wouldn't be there now if you hadn't made it look so suspicious in the first place," Hermione pointed out.

"Wait a minute," Harry was annoyed at her implication. "You're saying it's my fault Malfoy's treating him like crap? I can't control what Draco does!"

"You can control what you do, Harry!" Hermione argued. "Your interview should have taken an hour — Monroe was there for over three! Of course Draco's going to be suspicious!"

"I had him stay for lunch!" Harry protested. "What's wrong with lunch? Malfoy's just being vindictive!"

"Well, he's got reason to be, hasn't he?" Hermione said, wearily. "You and he haven't exactly been great friends since we all left Hogwarts."

"He went one way, I went another," Harry reminded her. "You know I wasn't going to let Lucius Malfoy decide what I was going to do for the rest of my life. I already had plans, Hermione!"

"I know that," she said, quietly. "They didn't seem to include me then, either."

"Now that's not fair," Harry warned her. "You — you had other priorities then, too. You were the one who said we were through."

"But I didn't really mean it." Hermione's voice was almost a whisper now. "I thought you'd get that. But I was wrong."

Harry's mouth twisted with frustration. "You went to university, too," he said, his voice lowering in response to hers. "It impressed the hell out of Scrimgeour when you came back, didn't it?"

"Yes," she nodded. "I wondered if it would go against me, spending four years in a Muggle college, but Scrimgeour liked my ideas. Not everyone did, though."

It was true. There were some at the Ministry who were not impressed with Muggle education, no matter how progressive its ideas, and Draco Malfoy, then an Auror, had said as much. It was debatable whether his remarks would have gotten him fired — being the son of Lord Malfoy, Draco getting sacked wasn't in the cards, even then. Lord Malfoy was still a force to be reckoned with, in the Wizengamot and in the Ministry itself. Ironically, however, it wasn't until Hermione herself became Minister that Draco was made Head Auror, under her administration.

There was silence for a time. Hermione fidgeted with a cloth napkin while Harry pretended to study the walls of Mary's Room in detail. At a sudden knock on the door Hermione jumped, then drew her wand and waved it at the door, opening the bolt and causing the door to swing open. The server, carrying their meals, appeared and quickly set them on the table, then bowed and departed. The bolt slammed shut again and wards were put up again, but neither of them spoke again for some time.

Finally Hermione looked at Harry. "So, what are you going to do about Mr. Monroe?" she asked, taking a bit of her salad.

It took Harry a while to answer — two mouthfuls of her lasagna, in fact. "Nothing, I think. If I try to intercede on his behalf it's going to look to Malfoy like I'm trying to hide something."

"And you aren't?" Hermione sounded extremely skeptical.

"I removed Monroe's memory about the recognition code," Harry admitted. "There's nothing else for him to talk about except the interview, and Draco thinks the Singularity is a Muggle pipe dream. He's probably scared Monroe learned something about the Wizarding world and is going to spill what he knows in that magazine he works for, or on the Web." Harry took a bite of his Diricawl breast. "This is very good, by the way. Do you want a bite?"

"Maybe later." Hermione had a worried expression on her face. "Harry. You may think Draco is out to get you, but he's not Head Auror because he's a vindictive ba- because he's vindictive. He's Head Auror because he knows how to anticipate problems and deal proactively with them. One of those problems is threats to the Secrecy Statutes. You know that —"

"Yes, I do," Harry agreed, cutting her off. He put down his fork. "Okay, look—I'll level with you. I did find out how Monroe knew the recognition code."

Hermione leaned forward, her vegetable lasagna forgotten. "How?"

Harry gave her a level look. "I used the Pensieve."

Hermione's head dropped. "Oh, Harry…" she said, into her lasagna.

"I had to know!" Harry exclaimed, almost pleadingly. "I haven't used that mnemonic since before I left Hogwarts!"

Hermione didn't answer right away. When she finally looked up, her expression was determined. "So," she said, with a brisk finality, "what are you going to do to help free Mr. Monroe, since you're the primary reason he's being held by the Aurors in the first place?"

"What do you want me to do?" Harry asked plaintively. "If I intervene on his behalf it's going to make Draco suspicious."

"He's already suspicious!" Hermione snapped. "But he may just think this is some way for you to take the — mickey — out of him."

Harry made a show of looking about the room for several moment. "You know, love, we are alone in here. You can say 'piss' if you want to."

Hermione ignored that comment. "Are you going to do something to help him, or am I going to have to do it?"

"That's not going to help at all," Harry pointed out. "Draco's going to think you're covering for me." Hermione made no response to this, either; she simply continued to stare sternly at him across the table.

Harry fidgeted unconsciously; he know that stare—it meant he wasn't talking his way out of this no matter how hard he tried.

"All right!" he said at last. "We'll stop by the Ministry on our way home; I'll convince Draco that Monroe really knows nothing."

"Because you Obliviated him," Hermione added, pointedly.

"He already knows that!" Harry said, curtly.

"And how do you know that?" Hermione challenged.

Harry cocked his head. "Because he has my office and waiting area under surveillance." Not to mention my private dining room, he didn't add aloud. It would be useful to keep that to himself, in case he wanted to pass some disinformation along to the Ministry snoops. Now, would his wife pretend she didn't know anything about the bugs he just mentioned?

Hermione stared at him for over a minute before she said. "How did you find that out?"

"I'm CEO of a global corporation," Harry replied, standing up, his Diricawl breast only half-finished. "I expect the competition to try and find out what I'm doing."

Hermione didn't look happy, though she stood as well, watching as Harry dropped a handful of Galleons on the ticket the server had left with their food. "The Ministry isn't your competition, Harry," she told him, a hint of sadness in her voice. "Don't make this about you and Draco and your — your pissing contest." She gave him a defiant look. "And don't make this about you and me — I'm not going to bail you out of this."

"I wouldn't expect you to," Harry said, levelly. "Draco is not going to be a problem."

=ooo=

Monroe was slumped forward in his chair, held up only by whatever held his arms to the armrests. His captor had been questioning him, seemingly for hours, for no reason Monroe could discern and seemingly no end in sight. How could he convince the man that he knew nothing about what Potter was doing?

"It would be a lot simpler," the blond-haired man. Malfoy, was saying. "If you would just activate whatever's going to restore your memory when you leave here. We're going to find out anyway, eventually."

"I still don't know what you're talking about," Monroe muttered wearily. "You're the one who's saying my memory was erased — I have to take your word for it! And I have to take your word that there's some way to get that memory back."

"Potter's tricky," Malfoy replied, ignoring Monroe's excuses. Potter would have given him false memories, memories layered in place of the ones he'd removed. "There are ways he could restore the memories he took from you without you ever knowing what you were carrying that would do that. We've examined everything you were carrying on you when you arrived; none of it is enchanted, or not so that we can detect, anyway. What were you going to do when you got home?"

Monroe blinked, trying to remember. "I was — going to check my Record-A-Pen for any saved audio."

"This?" Malfoy asked, holding up the pen-like object. "How?"

"Um…twist the clip, it will reveal some buttons that can be used to download the contents to a MP3 player."

"Do you have one of these 'MP3 players'?"

"In my…in my briefcase," Monroe said, trying to remember whether there really was one in there or not. He thought there was, but how could he know? What if Malfoy had already taken it? What if Potter had taken it? He had no idea who was trustworthy any more.

The blond man reached into a small pouch on his belt and muttered something Monroe couldn't hear. A moment later he began withdrawing his hand, and Monroe gaped as the pouch's lip suddenly began widening… as he watched, disbelieving, his entire briefcase came out of the pouch with an audible burp.

"What the hell?" Monroe gasped, though he felt too tired to shout as loudly as he wanted to. "How could —" He suddenly stopped as Malfoy drew a stick from another pocket with his free hand, waving it in front of himself. A small table appeared out of nowhere, and the man set Monroe's briefcase on top of it, then tapped it with his wand, causing the case to pop open.

Malfoy looked over the contents of the briefcase carefully. He finally picked up a small device the size of a lighter. "Is this it?" he asked.

Monroe nodded without saying anything. What could he say? Things had just leaped past strange into the surreal. The man held out the player toward him. "How does it work?" he asked.

"My arms…" Monroe began, but at that moment both of them suddenly came free. Monroe rubbed his forearms for a moment, then took the player from Malfoy.

"Have it play whatever's on it," Malfoy ordered.

"It's empty," Monroe said, glancing at the small display. "I haven't downloaded —"

"Just activate it," the blond man ordered, in a preemptive tone. Monroe obediently pushed the play button. There was a quick double beep indicating nothing was on the device. Monroe looked at his captor, shrugging to indicate he didn't know what else to do.

"Activate any hidden recordings on it," Malfoy told him.

"There aren't any," Monroe snapped, annoyed at the man's seeming paranoia. "It's just a plain old MP3 player, not some fancy James Bond device."

Malfoy started to speak again, but a tapping sound from behind the mirror diverted his attention. He looked back at the mirror, putting a hand to his ear.

"Hell," he muttered softly, then looked back at Monroe. "It seems someone's here to argue for your release." He waved the stick he carried at Monroe, whose arms were suddenly pulled back against the chair's armrests. "Sit tight."

"Like I have any choice," Monroe muttered, as the man left the room.

In the hallway outside the interrogation room were Harry and Hermione, with Crabbe and Goyle standing behind them, trying (and failing) to appear inconspicuous. Malfoy gave Potter and the Minister an expressionless look before asking of Potter, "Are you here to rescue your pet Muggle?"

"He's not my pet Muggle," Harry replied, his look equally expressionless. "But you're not going to get anything out of him."

"Oh?" Malfoy allowed himself a knowing sneer. "How do you know that?"

"Because there's nothing for him to tell you," Harry replied at once. "Remember, I spent over three hours with him earlier today."

"I'm quite aware of that," Malfoy retorted, with a short glance at Hermione, whose expression remained calm and aloof. "That's part of my problem, as you should well know."

"Yeah, I know," Harry grinned. "You probably think I planted some kind of knowledge time-bomb in his head," he pointed to his own temple for emphasis.

"Or something even more devious," Malfoy agreed, humorlessly. "There's very little I put past you these days, Potter."

"Would you two please stop this…pissing contest," Hermione finally spoke up. Both men looked at her. Behind her and Harry, Crabbe and Goyle gave each other small, knowing smiles. For a mudblood, this Minister could mix it up with Mr. Malfoy pretty good.

"Neither of you trust one another," Hermione went on. "We all know that. And neither of you are going admit you've gone too far in this — this fiasco of an interrogation. But both of you have; Draco, because there's no good reason to suspect this Monroe of knowing anything he shouldn't, and Harry, because he should never have let the man come under Ministry scrutiny in the first place.

"So I want you the two of you to get past this petty bickering amongst yourselves and solve the problem," Hermione declared, with finality.

Harry was giving her a look of mild amusement. "I thought you weren't going to intervene in my behalf," he commented.

"I haven't," Hermione retorted. "I'm intervening in Mr. Monroe's behalf. He's the one whose time you're wasting right now."

"As well as mine," Draco added, giving Harry a hard stare. "If all this is unnecessary and the Muggle really knows nothing. Which I doubt," he finished.

Harry folded his arms across his chest, saying nothing. It was hard to tell whether he was simply being stubborn or whether some deeper, more devious plot was being hatched within his brain.

"Alright," he said at last. "I'll tell you what I know. I found out where Monroe heard the recognition code phrase."

"Finally." Malfoy waited expectantly.

"He saw it written on a scrap of paper I left on the Ravenclaw table next to him at breakfast, my first day at Hogwarts."

"What?" Hermione and Draco both exclaimed at the same time. Behind them, even Crabbe and Goyle were jolted by this news. The Minister and the Head Auror glanced at one another, then Draco spoke.

"He's a Muggle, Harry! How could he possibly have been at Hogwarts? Did you know about this, Minister?"

Hermione shook her head. "He told me he found out, but not the details, until just now. Harry, what you're saying is impossible."

"I know that," Harry agreed, evenly. "But that's what I saw in the Pensieve."

"You used the Pensieve on him?" Draco practically shouted. "No wonder you Obliviated him!"

"I slipped a Hypnotic Potion into his food before I showed him anything magical," Harry replied. He had indeed done that, but the dosage was so small that the effects would have lasted only a minute or so — Harry had only wanted enough in the Muggle's system that it would register if checked for, giving him a valid reason for revealing magic to a Muggle. "It was supposed to last longer, but I must've miscalculated how much of it he ate. He woke up while we were still in the Pensieve, and I had to Obliviate him. Otherwise I would have just given him a post-hypnotic suggestion not to remember what he'd seen, and you'd have picked that up during your questioning." The handy thing about being a perfect Occlumens, Harry knew, was that even staring directly into Malfoy's eyes, he knew there was no way the Head Auror could tell he was lying. It was legal to reveal the existence of magic to a Muggle if he or she were already under the influence of a mind-altering potion or spell (or if they were a blood relative, in the case of Muggle-borns).

"I didn't detect that," Malfoy replied, not surprisingly, and Harry reflected that there was no way for him to be sure that Draco wasn't a perfect Occlumens as well — it was certainly something Lord Malfoy would have ordered his son to train for. On the other hand, Draco might have tested for it and gotten a false negative result. "I've been waiting for you to admit your reason for Obliviating him."

He was probably lying about that, Harry concluded. So — Draco was a perfect Occlumens as well. Another tidbit of information for him to file away about the Head Auror. Aloud, however, he said only, "What do you make of his memory of being at Hogwarts, then?"

Draco was silent for several seconds, contemplating. "It sounds like a false memory," he said at last. "I don't remember anyone there named James Monroe."

"Neither do I," Hermione chimed in. "But why would anyone put a false memory like that into a Muggle?"

"To send Harry a message," Draco suggested. That seemed pretty obvious. It was the kind of setup Draco himself would have concocted, if he were serious about getting Harry Potter into trouble — try to trip him up, get him to do something illegal so he could nail him. As it was, Harry was skirting the edges of legality with the Hypnotic Potion (if he'd actually used, it; Draco had lied about detecting it and Harry might have fallen for that, but it was unlikely). He didn't have enough to bring Harry before the Wizengamot for violating the Secrecy restrictions; you had to knowingly violate them, which Harry hadn't (if his story was true, and Draco couldn't disprove it at the moment, not without corroborating evidence from Monroe).

"What kind of message would that be?" Hermione wanted to know. She couldn't quite see into the more subtle moves some Dark wizards might try, things Harry and Draco were both well accustomed to, but it was obvious that anyone using a Muggle this way was up to no good.

"That things aren't as they appear," Harry said. "Monroe couldn't have been at Hogwarts, but his memories indicate he was, so someone is manipulating all of this." He did not look happy. Usually it was him manipulating things — he did not care to have someone trying to pull his strings.

"What do you want to do, then?" Draco asked, though he wasn't sure he was going to agree with Harry's answer.

"Let him go," Harry said. "Obliviate any memories he has of this place, place him in his home, asleep, and let him wake up normally tomorrow. Let him think he went to bed too tired to write anything yesterday."

"And how does that position us to find out what's really going on?" Draco asked, skeptically.

"If someone's pulling Monroe's strings, he'll show up again," Harry hypothesized. "And it's almost certain someone's manipulating him." And he was going to find out who that was, Harry promised himself.

Draco frowned. If Harry was right about this, it was a good way to shunt him and the Ministry out of the way while he interrogated Monroe about it at his leisure. On the other hand, the questioning of Monroe was going nowhere at the moment — if there was something he was hiding, it was hidden from Monroe as well, probably by whoever was manipulating him. He would have to be extra-vigilant about monitoring Potter's movements and contacts for the next few weeks.

"Very well," he said at last. He looked past Harry and Hermione to his two subordinates. "You two, get Monroe back to his apartment and remove his memories of being here in the Ministry or of anyone to do with it, including yourselves. Put him to sleep and leave no trace of yourselves in his apartment."

"Yes, Mr. Malfoy," Crabbe nodded, and they went into the room where Monroe was sitting, still fixed to his chair.

As they left, Harry muttered, "Good minions," under his breath, but still audible enough to be heard. Crabbe shot him a look, but Malfoy shook his head fractionally and the big man turned away with a grunt, saying nothing.

"You know," Draco said, almost conversationally, after they were gone. "Both Vincent and Gregory are fully qualified in their professions at the Ministry — you don't have to keep rubbing that in." Harry made no comment, simply holding up his hands in a gesture of no contest.

"Well, I'm going home," Draco added, when it was clear Hermione had nothing further to say. "Both of you have a good evening." He walked away from them.

A few moments later both Harry and Hermione turned and began walking toward the elevators that would take them to the Atrium and from there, a Floo trip back to their building. "Do you really think someone else is involved?" Hermione asked as they entered the elevator.

"I don't know," Harry answered honestly. "But I don't know anyone beside Draco who might have pulled this off, and I don't think he's the one this time." He paused for a moment, considering. "Maybe I should have a chat with my experts on impossible situations."

=ooo=

James Monroe awoke early the next morning, his thoughts fuzzy and confused. He was in his own bedroom, he could tell, but how he got home or what he did before going to sleep he had no idea. In fact, he could remember nothing that had happened after he walked out of the TBC building the day before.

Monroe sat up, rubbing sleep from his eyes. What did he remember from yesterday? It all seemed a jumble of disassociated memories; the only thing he could recall clearly was his interview with Harry Potter —

A clear thought suddenly burned in his brain, something he'd known before, but had somehow forgotten: Recognition code 927, I am a potato.

And with that, all of yesterday suddenly returned, unbidden, into his mind. Monroe stared upward, astonished, at the memories that suddenly filled his head. If only half of this wasn't just some dream or hallucination, then he was sitting on the biggest story of the century, or the millennium. Monroe grabbed a notepad and pencil off his nightstand and began furiously writing down what he recalled.

Chapter 6: The Cat Came Back

Updated 1/14/2012

"And who do you think I am, Potter?"

=ooo=

"James Monroe?" Verity had finished with her customer and walked over to where Angelina and Monroe were talking. "Aren't you that Mu—" she caught herself "—er, that man that visited Harry's business the other day, the journalist?"

"Yes," Monroe nodded. "But I've discovered a few things about myself since then, and I wanted to talk to him about them."

"What things?" Verity asked, looking suspicious and concerned. This man, according to Fred, had been pestering Harry Potter for months for an interview for a Muggle magazine, about some crazy Muggle idea called the Singulary, or something like that. How could he have even made it into Diagon Alley in the first place, if he was a Muggle? Had some wizard let him in? Who would allow a Muggle to walk around in Diagon Alley unattended?

As if reading her thoughts, Monroe reached into his jacket and withdrew a slender piece of wood. "I picked this up at Ollivanders before I came here. Mahogany, twelve inches, with a dragon heartstring core." He put the wand away. "Bill remembered my name as well — apparently Harry Potter has talked a lot about me to all of you in the past few days. He was surprised to see me in Diagon Alley. He told me Harry and his brothers were having a meeting, purpose unknown, but I suspect it was to discuss me."

Verity and Angelina looked at one another, concern on both of their faces. How could Monroe guess all this? Verity tried again, "How could you —"

"How could I have gotten into Diagon Alley without a wand?" Monroe guessed her question. "Well, one of the customers in the Leaky Cauldron let me in, after I'd explained to the proprietress that I'd lost my first wand —"

"How did you know where the Leaky Cauldron was?" Angelina interrupted. "Did Harry tell you?"

"No, it was just something that popped into my head when I woke up after the Aurors Obliviated me and put me back in my apartment."

"Aurors?" Verity was surprised. "What do you know about Aurors?"

"Perhaps I should speak with Harry about this," Monroe suggested. "It's kind of complicated. Until this morning, I had no idea I was a wizard."

Verity and Angelina both looked surprised, but Luna, who had come up and was listening as well, nodded knowingly. "He was probably one of the wizards who disappeared during the height of the Rotfang Conspiracy, back in the '90's."

"Luna!" Verity frowned disapprovingly. "I thought we decided that —" she was going to say that the Rotfang Conspiracy was some wild idea that her father Xenophilius had come up with, but changed mid-sentence to "— decided that the Rotfang Conspiracy was disbanded when Hermione Granger became Minister of Magic."

"Oh yes," Luna agreed, complacently. "But this man could have been abducted by the Conspiracy before then." She looked at Monroe. "What do you know about gum disease?"

"What?" Monroe looked at her uncomprehendingly.

"Never mind, it's not important," Angelina butted in. She turned to Luna, who was giving her a hurt look. "I mean, what we need to understand is what led Mr. Monroe here, not where he's been for the past two decades, or however long he's been living as a Muggle."

She turned back to Monroe. "Can you tell us what happened when you met with Harry Potter on Monday?"

=ooo=

It was Ron, interestingly enough, who asked the question first. "So…d'you think that it's possible that he's come back again?"

Fred and George raised their eyebrows, looking at Harry, but he could tell they weren't surprised, but rather interested in what Harry would say. It was also obvious from the emphasis Ron had put in the sentence who 'he' was. He was referring to Voldemort.

"I don't know how that could be," Harry replied. He had to measure his words carefully here, because none of the Weasleys knew the secret of Voldemort's seeming immortality. Only a very few people ever had: Albus Dumbledore, Severus Snape, and Minerva McGonagall were the ones Harry was sure had known about Horcruxes before Harry learned about them, and he suspected that an ex-Auror at the time, Alastor "Mad-Eye" Moody, had known as well. Almost everyone on that short list was dead now, and the only other person Harry had told about them was Hermione, and she only after the fact.

Horcruxes weren't something you wanted the general Wizarding population knowing about — not now, not when Harry was so close to his breakthrough…

"His and my wands were twins," Harry went on. "Mr. Ollivander told me when I bought my wand that its brother had given me my scar, that both wands contained a feather from the same phoenix; phoenix feathers are a relatively rare magical core. We could injure each other with our wands, but could not fatally injure one another with them." At least, that was the explanation that had been given out after Voldemort's demise, to conceal the fact that Harry and Dumbledore had sought out and destroyed the Dark Lord's Horcruxes before confronting him directly. Voldemort, thinking himself invulnerable to death, had faced Harry after Dumbledore's death, with Harry using Dumbledore's wand. Riddle couldn't have known that, before Dumbledore died, he and Harry had dueled and Harry had disarmed the elderly wizard, taking the Elder Wand from him. It was with that wand, the so-called "unbeatable" wand, that Harry had faced Voldemort.

"So you used Dumbledore's wand to kill him," Fred said, and both George and Ron nodded. The story was well-known; to the entire Wizarding World, the story of Harry's defeat of the last great Dark Wizard of the 20th century was the beginning of a Magical Golden Age. The Death Eaters that were still extant upon Voldemort's demise were killed or captured; many of them went to prison, with the exception of a few — Lord Malfoy being one of those, due to his influence in the Wizengamot, was able to plead that he'd been Imperiused and therefore not responsible for his actions on Voldemort's behalf. That was a common enough excuse among Death Eaters, but only Malfoy had the influence (that is, the Galleons) to carry it off successfully.

"Yes," Harry said.

"Whatever happened to that wand?" Ron suddenly asked. "I mean, you still use your old wand, right? What did you do with Dumbledore's wand?"

"Don't you remember?" Fred butted in, before Harry could answer. "At the memorial for Dumbledore? Harry put the wand in the tomb with the Headmaster."

"Oh yeah…" Ron looked down. "I guess I was payin' more attention to — other stuff," he mumbled. Harry knew what he meant, even if he didn't say it. Ron had sat next to Hermione at Dumbledore's memorial service — it was during the short time they had dated, the time when she and Harry weren't seeing one another, because he was helping Dumbledore to kill Horcruxes and no one else could know about that, not even her.

"Okay, then," George said, crisply, trying to get their discussion back on track. "If this Monroe fellow isn't — him — then who is he? How did he learn about Harry's recognition code phrase, if he couldn't have been at Hogwarts?"

"Obviously someone planted it in him," Fred said flatly. "Someone on a par with whoever pulled off the Prank, assuming it wasn't me and George and we Obliviated ourselves afterward."

Harry chuckled. "Still can't give up on wanting to own that, can you?"

"Well," Fred said airily, "even if we can't remember, it does have all the earmarks of being a Weasley prank." Both George and Ron nodded at that as well.

Harry chose not to debate that point. He was pretty sure Quirrell had had something to do with it, but exactly what was unclear. And, since the Defense professor was no longer around to ask, the question would likely remain forever unanswered.

"What about the Muggle journalist, then?" Ron kept going back to that question; he seemed to be more fixated on it than Fred and George were, Harry observed. It made him wonder, once again, how he'd managed to underestimate the youngest Weasley son for so long. If things had turned out even a little differently, Ron might have ended up married to Hermione Granger rather than his current wife, Luna.

"It's his move next," Harry answered, after a moment of reflection. "He was Obliviated three times yesterday — I can't see how he could remember a thing about the Wizarding world by now. If someone else is manipulating him, we may see him again. But I'm not going to hold my breath."

Harry glanced at his watch. "We've been up here for over two hours, now. Your wives are probably wondering what happened to us!"

Fred laughed. "They know fish and chips and Harry Potter make for a long lunch. We'll have to do this again —"

"— in another five years," George finished, grinning. "Or maybe sooner, if we can help it."

The four of them stood and left the room, tramping down the stairs leading back to WWW and their wives, preparing to explain (hopefully with as few lies as possible) what they'd been doing all this time.

=ooo=

"There's not much to tell," Monroe said, carefully. He wasn't sure how much to divulge to these women — he had no idea where their real loyalties might lie, especially when it came to someone like Harry Potter-Evans-Verres. They were all married to Weasleys, and he didn't know the dynamics of that family. "I met with Harry yesterday for an interview about the Singularity —"

"Which is what, exactly?" Verity interrupted. This was supposed to be a Muggle idea — why would Harry be interested in it, unless he had some stake in it?

"It's a point in future history when AI's will attain, then exceed human intelligence, resulting in runaway progress," Monroe replied. "I don't expect you to understand it —"

"Do you understand it?" Angelina asked. "Wizards have had artificial intelligence for centuries."

"I don't think it's the same thing," Monroe disagreed.

"You don't? Based on what — your deep understanding of magic?" Angelina scoffed. "By your own admission you've known you're a wizard less than a day. How do you presume to know about such things?"

"I know more than you might think," Monroe argued. "When my memory came back, a lot of things I'd forgotten were suddenly back in my head once again."

"Like what?" Verity challenged.

"Like my time at Hogwarts," Monroe retorted.

There was silence for several seconds. "But, nobody remembers you from back then," Angelina said at last. "None of our husbands do — they've been trying to remember who you were since Harry first told them about your memory from the Pensieve."

"I know the reason for that," Monroe told her. "But I'm not discussing it with anyone except Harry."

"There's loads we're going to discuss," Harry's voice suddenly said, sounding hard, and everyone in the shop turned to see him and the three Weasley brothers standing at the bottom of the stairs. All four of them were pointing their wands toward Monroe.

"How did you get here?" Harry demanded. "You're not supposed to remember anything about this place, unless someone screwed up — or put memories back in your head."

Monroe was eyeing the four wands pointing at him, but he didn't appear apprehensive or confused this time. "I don't know either way," he answered. "All I do know is, I woke up this morning and thoughts about the Wizarding world suddenly began flooding into my head. I started writing them down, but it became apparent after a few seconds that what I was remembering wasn't just a few isolated memories. I was remembering my entire life."

"He has a wand, too," Luna mentioned. "He showed it to us."

Harry gestured with his wand. "Take it out," he said. "Do it slowly — any sudden moves and we'll all Stun you."

Monroe gave Harry a level look. "You're treating me like some kind of Dark wizard," he said, not making any move at all.

"I suppose we shouldn't rule that out," Harry agreed. "But for now, you're just an unknown — none of us have ever heard of you or remember you as a wizard."

"I was at Hogwarts," Monroe said. "You saw that yourself, in the Pensieve. And I can explain why none of you remember me."

"Then explain," Harry's wand hadn't wavered in pointing at Monroe's heart.

"The Fidelius Charm," Monroe answered.

"Huh-uh," Harry shook his head. "The Fidelius doesn't work that way. If you're suggesting that you or someone else cast a Fidelius to hide your identity, it would only keep anyone who knew you from telling anyone else your name or who you were. If you spent seven years at Hogwarts, that would mean upwards of a thousand people, including the teachers there during those years, would know who you were, even if they couldn't tell anyone about it. That would include us. The memory we saw was during my first year at Hogwarts, but I don't remember you being there at all. Try again."

"There's something you don't know about the Fidelius," Monroe insisted. "You can incorporate a Memory Charm into the spell; it invokes the first time you meet someone, erasing any memories they might have of you. If you add that component to the spell, you have to be the Secret-Keeper; otherwise, you could never introduce yourself to anyone, Muggle or wizard."

Harry glanced towards the Weasley brothers. Fred and George were looking very thoughtful, as if trying to determine whether Monroe's claim made any sense. "Well?" he said, as the silence grew protracted.

"I suppose it's possible," Fred said, looking rather bemused. "The Fidelius is complicated enough on its own, though, without trying to incorporate contingency spells in it, too."

"How plausible is it?" Harry demanded.

George and Fred both shook their heads. "Don't know," George answered this time. "We've never even heard of the idea until now."

"Wait a minute," Ron objected. "Aren't we getting ahead of ourselves here?" The others looked at him. Ron pointed toward Monroe. "How does he even know about all this — the Fidelius, Diagon Alley, everything! I thought he was supposed to be a Muggle!"

"Up until this morning," Monroe spoke up. "I thought I was!"

"And so did Malfoy," Harry said, thoughtfully. "But there are ways to tell if a wizard is trying to impersonate a Muggle. You can't change your magical core even if you Polyjuice yourself into a Muggle identity — your core will be diminished, but it'll still be there, and detectable."

He looked shrewdly at Monroe. "If Malfoy didn't detect that you were really a wizard pretending to be a Muggle, then it stands to reason that you're just a Muggle pretending to be a wizard! Maybe we ought to test that."

Harry's wand was suddenly pointing at Monroe again. "Do you have any objections, Mr. Monroe?"

"I can think of one straightaway," Monroe answered. "How could I have bought a wand if I wasn't a wizard? When I waved it, the wand I bought shot sparks into the air. Bill Weasley at Ollivanders can verify that."

Everyone looked around at one another. That was a pretty good indication of being a wizard, everyone had to agree.

But the wand in Harry's hand hadn't wavered. "Good evidence," he agreed. "But only if you aren't being helped by someone behind the scenes, someone that could cause a wand to shoot sparks in the hand of a Muggle."

"Bloody hell!" Monroe said loudly. "What's it going to take to convince you, then?

Harry lowered his wand slowly to his side. "A duel, I think," he answered quietly.

"You're not serious!" Monroe said automatically, then took another look at Harry. "You are serious!"

"If you attended Hogwarts around the same time we did," Harry pointed out, "you might have participated in the Defense class armies that Professor Quirrell started during my first year at Hogwarts." Harry looked expectantly at Monroe. "Well?"

After a moment, Monroe nodded. "I remember them," he said. "I was in your Chaos Legion."

Harry smiled. "It's not as if I remember, obviously," he said, with a sardonic grin. "But according to you I shouldn't, anyway."

"Wait a minute." Verity stepped forward, between the two men, her hands outstretched. "You two are not having a duel in the middle of our shop!"

"Of course not," Harry smiled, hefting his wand. "We'll do it in the test range."

=ooo=

As Harry gestured for Monroe to follow him, however, Angelina interrupted them again. "I think I want to see this duel for myself, too."

"We'll let you know how it turns out," Fred answered. "Someone has to watch the store, you know."

"Who says you can't do it?" Angelina folded her arms across her chest. "You've been off having lunch for the past two hours!"

"I don't think that's relevant," Fred said, blandly.

"Of course you wouldn't," Angelina sniffed. "But some of us haven't had lunch yet!"

"You don't want us to go without lunch," Verity advised her husband. "We tend to get cranky otherwise."

"Oh, is that what causes that?" George grinned. "I thought perhaps it was…" he decided not to complete his thought as he caught sight of his and Fred's wife both glaring at him.

"I don't care who watches," Harry added. "But you better make up your minds straightaway — I'm not waiting around for you lot to figure it out."

"Ron and Luna will stay," Fred said.

"Wait a minute —!" Ron looked outraged, but Fred's tone had been final.

"It'll be fun, Ronald," Luna said happily. "We don't work together that much anymore — you're always off inventing things these days."

Ron looked disgruntled, but his wife's beaming expression quickly made him smile weakly. "Sure, it'll be fun," he agreed with her. But as Fred and George moved to follow Harry and Monroe to the stairs, he put a hand on George's arm. "I want details!" he said, sotto voce.

=ooo=

The Weasley product testing range had originally been on the first floor of the shop, along with Fred and George's bedroom (which at the time had amounted to a couple of sleeping bags thrown on the floor). Since that time, a steady influx of Galleons, marriage and a desire for comfort had overridden their eagerness to "rough it" — the first floor of the shop had become three bedrooms and their "conference area," the specially-shielded room where Harry and the three youngest Weasley brothers had just had lunch.

The test range was now located under the shop, in a sixty by thirty-foot space that had been magically dug out and shaped. It was actual size so the brothers could accurately assess the effects of whatever item they were working on (using Extension Charms sometimes produced unexpected results).

The entrance was near the middle of the room, lengthwise. Harry led the way in, with Monroe looking around warily as he stepped in behind him, and Fred, George and their wives bringing up the rear.

"Pretty nice, isn't it?" Harry spread his arms, giving Monroe a calculating look. "It's certainly bigger than some of the classrooms the Chaos Legion had to practice in, that first year of our armies."

He pointed to one side of the room. "Stand over there," he said, then took up a position about thirty feet from Monroe. The four Weasleys arrayed themselves on either side of the entrance. When Harry and Monroe were both facing each other, Harry asked, "I suppose you remember how 'friendly' duels work, then?"

Monroe nodded. "No fatal or irreversible spells. No Dark curses. Either duelist can concede at any time." The Weasleys were murmuring among themselves — the rules Monroe had quoted were just what they'd been taught about formal duels.

"Right," Harry said. "I suppose you remember how to cast a Simple Shield Charm, then?"

"Yeah," Monroe replied, then said "Ouch!" as Harry's wand flicked and a spell shot out, hitting him in the chest.

"Maybe not," Harry smirked, as Monroe rubbed his chest. "Not if you can't even defend against a Simple Strike Hex."

"We haven't even started the duel yet!" Monroe snapped, angrily. "Poor form, Potter!"

"We're not in Neverland, Mr. Monroe," Harry answered, grinning. "But I won't argue with you. Are you ready to begin? I'll even let you know, I'll use Ma-ha-su until you're ready for something a little stronger. And we can keep the duel verbal until you're ready to go to the next level."

"Fine," Monroe growled. "Let's begin."

The two men squared off, both holding their wands before them in the stance called for by the rules of formal dueling. Fred stepped forward, his wand held high, then swept it downward, signaling the start of the duel.

Harry's wand snapped forward. "Ma-ha-su!" he said, loudly, even as Monroe's wand began the motions for a Simple Shield; he shouted "Contego!" and the shield flickered into existence in front of his head and chest.

Harry's Simple Strike, however, had been aimed at Monroe's left leg, and he staggered as the bolt struck him. "Son of a bitch," he muttered, followed by "Ma-ha-su!" which Harry easily deflected with a muttered Simple Shield of his own.

"You were in my army?" Harry wondered, mockingly. "Your heart must not have been in it, Monroe, judging by your performance here so far."

"It's still coming back to me," Monroe said, through gritted teeth. "I've been living as a Muggle for a long time now!"

"So you say," Harry replied, then snapped "Somnium!" before Monroe could retort. This was already getting boring, even if Monroe was a wizard who'd been trapped as a Muggle.

But this time Monroe dodged to one side, letting the spell fly past him without casting a spell. At the same moment he responded with "Luminos!"

Harry blocked the spell without difficulty. "Strictly speaking," he noted. "That spell wouldn't do anything to me except make me glow. In a real duel it would be worthless."

"Right," Monroe said, then shouted, "Impedimenta!" even as Harry finished speaking. Harry said "Protego!" just in time for the spell to bounce off it.

"Still not impressed," Harry said, though in truth, the Impediment Jinx would have blasted right through a Simple Shield — if he'd hadn't reacted instinctively he might have been pushed back, off-balance, and there was no telling what Monroe might have done with that slight advantage. "Stupefy!" he said. Let's see if Monroe could take as good as he gave.

"Protego!" Monroe said, forming his own shield just in time to catch Harry's Stunner.

Harry swept his wand to once side, repeating the spell, and the red bolt shot out toward the wall, seemingly wasted. But the Stunner ricocheted, heading toward Monroe. It was only due to dumb luck and slight imprecision in Harry's aim that the bolt glanced off the edge of Monroe's shield, missing him by inches.

Harry's wand was sweeping back toward Monroe when the ex-Muggle's shield vanished and he muttered a spell so softly Harry couldn't hear. He dodged it, letting it speed past him, only to suddenly feel disoriented and confused. What had Monroe just done?

He realized a moment later what had happened. Monroe had sent a second spell just after the first one, aimed for where Harry had stepped when he dodged the first one. Monroe had managed to Confund him! Stupid, stupid!

"Whoa," Fred muttered, seeing Harry staggering and shaking his head. "I didn't think I'd ever see Harry faked out that easily."

Harry quickly raised a shield, protecting himself in case Monroe followed up with something like a Stunner. But the shield was angled slightly to one side, leaving his flank unprotected, and Monroe sent a Stunner toward a wall, letting it ricochet as Harry had done earlier. The Stunner clipped Harry, knocking him to the floor, and his shield evaporated. A moment later a "Somnium" uttered by Monroe left Harry asleep on the floor.

"Bloody hell!" George said, looking at his twin. "Harry just got beat in a duel!"

Monroe looked at Harry on the floor, then at his wand, his expression one of disbelief as well. "Huh," he said. "Didn't think that would really work." Angelina and Verity were both staring at him in shock. How had a man they'd all taken for a Muggle only hours earlier managed to beat one of the best duelists in the Wizarding world so handily?

=ooo=

"Innervate!" Fred said. After a moment Harry opened his eyes, staring up at everyone gathered around him.

"A lucky shot," he said, his voice still slightly slurred from the effects of the Confundus Charm.

"I'm sure you wouldn't have said that if your Stunner ricochet had got me," Monroe sneered.

Harry sat up slowly. "Maybe not," he admitted, as Fred followed up with Finite, to cancel the Confundus. "Ah, better," he said, shaking his head to clear it. He looked up at Monroe. "I suppose the only question left is, why all your memories about being a wizard suddenly came back now."

"I don't have any idea," Monroe answered, as George helped Harry to his feet. "Could all those Memory Charms you and the Ministry laid on me have done something to trigger them?"

"Possible," Harry shrugged. "But it seems like a rather elaborate scenario for anyone to set up, concealing your memories of being a wizard only to have something like one to several Obliviations cause them to return."

"A Fidelius might have been used," George theorized, "Maybe the Secret-Keeper died, or did something to end the spell."

"But if he died, it wouldn't bring back the subject's memories," Fred objected. "Ending the spell would be the only thing that would have let the memories be recalled."

"If that's the case, we have to figure out who did this," Harry said. "Either way, there's some very complex spellwork involved in this, magic that would have been too difficult for any but a very few wizards to perform."

"Who are you thinking of?" Verity asked.

"Dumbledore, for one," Harry answered. "Though I can't see why this would have mattered to him." He turned back to Monroe. "Did you ever talk to Dumbledore during your time at Hogwarts? Even once?"

"I don't remember," Monroe replied. "If I did, it was so insignificant that it probably wasn't worth remembering."

"How about Professor Quirrell?" Harry asked. The room went silent as everyone there stopped talking amongst themselves to hear the answer, especially Fred and George.

"I was in your army, Harry," Monroe answered. "You were the general — you talked to him, not me. I didn't have any reason to talk to Quirrell beyond answering questions in class."

"Mmm," Harry was nodding, his expression bemused but very guarded. "Okay. Maybe we should continue this at my offices. In private."

"What?" Fred and George both said, sounding outraged. "Do you think that's a good idea?" Fred went on. "What if there's some kind of trap —"

"I don't think Monroe is setting a trap for me," Harry said, cutting him off. "He was alone with me the other day for several hours — if he'd wanted to do something then, he could have."

"But it might have something to do with his memory returning," George pointed out, and both Verity and Angelina nodded agreement.

"Better safe than sorry," Angelina pointed out, backing up her husband.

"Agreed," Harry smiled. "So I'll be safe, with the appropriate wards."

"That's not what I meant!" Angelina insisted, but Harry had already taken Monroe by the arm and was leading back up the stairs toward the shop's ground floor. She glared at Fred and George, who both grinned and shrugged sheepishly. When Harry Potter made up his mind about something, it was usually best to let him do what he wanted.

Ron was waiting at the top of the stairs — evidently he'd been trying to listen to whatever had gone on in the test range; Harry walked past him without comment, heading for the ground floor office. Ron looked inquiring at Fred and George as they came up the stairs. "What happened? I couldn't hear anything, you know — those damned sound-deadening spells!"

"Harry lost the duel," George said, in a low voice. At Ron's look of utter surprise he added, "But he doesn't seem that fussed about it. Dunno why that is — he always hated losing."

"Don't I know it?" Ron muttered, almost to himself. He turned to look at Harry, but he and Monroe had already gone into the shop's office. The three Weasley brothers hurried to follow them inside, to see what Harry would do next. Verity, Angelina and Luna followed them inside, making the smallish room seem quite crowded.

Harry was taking a pinch of Floo powder from the bowl on the fireplace mantle. "We're going home," he said matter-of-factly, seeing that everyone seemed quite interested in what he was up to. "I have a few things to discuss with Mr. Monroe about his recent memory recovery."

"Maybe someone should go with you," Angelina suggested, then thrust her chin out defiantly as Harry raised an eyebrow at her. "Well, someone needs to make sure nothing happens to Mr. Monroe!"

"Harry wouldn't do anything to Mr. Monroe," Luna said, pleasantly. "He never did anything to Father in spite of all the headlines the Quibbler printed about him."

It might never have occurred to Luna, Angelina thought, that no one had ever attacked her father because everyone considered the man a harmless crackpot, but she knew saying so would just piss off Fred and annoy George and Verity, so she just said, "Still, it might be a good idea."

"Don't worry about it," Harry muttered. He threw the Floo powder into the fireplace, and green flames began swirling about. "We'll be fine," he said, looking at Fred and George.

Both of the twins shook their heads. "Don't worry about —" Fred began.

"— we won't follow you," George finished, while at the same time both twins silently agreed they would do that. Just in case.

Harry nodded at them, then turned to Monroe. "You know how this works?" he asked, indicating the fireplace and green flames.

"Floo travel," Monroe said matter-of-factly. "I guess I remember."

"Well, don't guess," Harry retorted, stepping forward. "Watch me and do what I do." He stepped into the green flames, turning to face the journalist and the others, then said, "Potter-Evans-Verres residence!" Harry vanished.

After a few seconds, Fred gestured toward the fire. "Well, go on, then," he told Monroe. "We're coming right after."

Monroe looked at the others a second, then nodded and stepped into the flames as well. "Potter-Evans-Verres residence!" he said, as Harry did, and vanished.

Fred stepped forward, hard on Monroe's heels, but as he stepped into the emerald flames they suddenly winked out. He stopped short, staring at the fireplace in a moment of confusion, then cursed. "Dammit! Harry must've activated his Floo Damper!"

The Floo Damper was a control that could be installed on any fireplace on the Floo Network. It curtailed travel to and from the fireplace without removing it from the Network, so homes could be made secure from unwanted visitors with a minimum of hassle. Until Fred and George invented it, shortly before Hermione became Minister of Magic, the Ministry had to be contacted and arrangements made for the removal and restoration of a fireplace to the Floo Network whenever a family planned to be away for some time.

"Why would he do that?" Verity asked.

"I don't think he wants us around while he's talking to Monroe," Fred said, grimly. He looked at George. "He must've cottoned onto what we were planning."

"It wouldn't have been that hard," George admitted. "I think we gave in a bit too easily."

"Probably," Fred agreed. He rubbed his chin, thinking hard. "I think we'd better let Ginny know something's going on. Maybe she can pay Harry a visit, pretending it's for business reasons, and see what he's up to with Monroe."

=ooo=

The grates flashing across Monroe's vision began to slow, until finally he caught sight of Harry standing beyond the grate in front of him, and he felt himself pushed forward and out of the fireplace.

"That wasn't too bad —" Monroe started to say, but jerked at a sudden BANG as something slammed into his chest. Ropes were winding around his chest, his arms and his legs, binding them tightly, so tightly that Monroe couldn't keep his balance and fell over on his side onto the floor. Harry reached down and removed Monroe's wand through a gap in the ropes.

"They won't be following, Monroe," Harry told him, his face close to the journalist's. "I set the damper so no one could follow. It's just you and me, now."

"What the hell's going on, Potter?" Monroe shouted angrily. "What are you doing?"

"I'm sure you know what I'm doing," Harry said tightly as he stood, looking over Monroe's wand briefly before putting it in a pocket. "The others can't be a part of this conversation."

"Oh? Why not?" Monroe sneered. "Because of how silly you're going to look, being fooled by a Muggle who was really a wizard?"

"No," Harry said, calmly. "Because of who you really are."

Monroe laughed harshly. "And who do you think I am, Potter?"

"You're Lord Voldemort."

Chapter 7: The Return of Lord Voldemort?

Updated 1/27/2012

"Harry Potter's nearly a Dark wizard himself."

=ooo=

"Lord Voldemort?" Monroe said, astonished by the accusation. "Me? I'd like to hear how you worked that one out, Potter!"

"Oh, I plan to explain," Harry replied. "You're either Voldemort, disguised to look like someone else, or you're possessed by Voldemort and being forced to act on his behalf, I haven't quite worked out which it is yet."

Monroe looked down at himself, tightly bound by coils of rope around his torso and legs. "Am I going to have to lie around like this while you explain?"

"Oh, are you uncomfortable?" Harry asked, sneering. "How rude of me!" He took out his wand and waved it in Monroe's direction. Monroe rose upward, and Harry floated him over to a nearby plump chair, upholstered in a garish purple material. Harry flicked his wand, dumping Monroe unceremoniously into it. "Comfy now, Monroe?"

Monroe looked around. The room was square and not very large; there was a door opposite the fireplace. Incongruously, a third wall contained a set of elevator doors. Besides the chair he was in sat another chair, this one in red and gold cloth, and an equally garish-looking divan across the room from him. "Where are we?" he asked.

"This," Harry waved an arm to indicate the room, "is the entry way to where my wife and I live." He pointed with his wand toward the door. "It's protected with just about every possible spell I could come up with. Only myself, my wife, and a few friends can get through that door to our apartment. Obviously, you're not one of my friends, so if by some chance you do get free, I advise you not to try escaping through that door."

"Any time you're ready to back up your claim that I'm Voldemort," Monroe said, in a flat tone. "I'm all ears."

"You're not going to enjoy the result if it turns out I'm correct," Harry warned him, dropping into the chair next to his. "I can't allow Voldemort to be set loose on the Wizarding world again."

"It seems like I remember the Wizarding world was certain he was dead, once upon a time," Monroe added matter-of-factly. "And that included you — I remember reading it in the Prophet years ago."

"I was certain," Harry declared. "I faced him with the Elder Wand, one of the Deathly Hallows, and beat him — deflected his Killing Curse back on him. He hit the ground a dead husk."

"And yet you maintain that, somehow, I am Voldemort —"

"— or possessed by him," Harry said, clarifying his position.

"Whatever," Monroe shrugged. "I'm still waiting for your proof. Isn't there some kind of spell you can use to tell whether I'm really someone else?"

Harry had taken out his wand again as Monroe was talking and was idly rolling it between his fingers. "There's a spell that the Ministry uses to determine if someone has been possessed. They developed it specifically to test whether Voldemort had somehow taken over someone else after Quirrell was killed. For a while, being tested was pretty much mandatory if you wanted to work at the Ministry. Even Hermione was tested before she began working there after she left Hogwarts. Well, let's see what happens." Harry pointed his wand at Monroe and uttered several words. After several moments of silence his expression turned from anticipation to something between relief and disappointment.

"Bad news?" Monroe asked, sardonically.

"You're not being possessed by any being the spell can detect," Harry said, looking a bit chagrinned. "But that only supports my initial hypothesis — that you somehow are Voldemort!"

"Voldemort's body was destroyed when he tried to kill you back in 1981," Monroe pointed out.

"There are rituals to recover ones original form," Harry countered. "There were steps taken to counteract those rituals, but Voldemort may have anticipated them and taken steps to ensure he would have the proper materials if he needed them."

"But it seems like he didn't avail himself of those rituals," Monroe went on, "since you destroyed Quirrell along with Voldemort when you two dueled.

"Quirrell's body was taken over by Voldemort," Harry confirmed.

"So where was he in the ten years between 1981 and when Quirrell appeared to take the Defense position at Hogwarts?"

"We never learned the answer to that — Quirrell kept almost every detail of his life after attending Hogwarts secret," Harry said. "Perhaps in the same way you claim to have done — with a modified Fidelius Charm, which is one reason why I think you're him."

"That's not much to go on," Monroe pointed out. "I think you're reaching."

"You would say that if I was right about you," Harry riposted. "But there are more reasons."

Monroe raised his eyebrows inquiringly. "Such as?"

"Such as your single-minded determination to get an interview with me over the past several months," Harry answered immediately. "I did everything but turn you down flat to get you to give up. Yet you kept calling and showing up trying to get in to see me."

"So would any good journalist," Monroe snapped, exasperated. "That's no reason to think I'm some evil Dark Lord, for Christ's sake!"

"By itself, no," Harry agreed. "But there's also —" a statue on the mantelpiece suddenly began flashing, distracting Harry. He stared at it for a moment, surprised, then muttered. "Damn."

"What?" Monroe followed Harry's gaze to the statue. "What's that mean?"

"It means trouble," Harry said, standing up. He reached into a back pocket and brought out a small bag. Reaching inside, he brought out his Invisibility Cloak.

Monroe eyed the Cloak warily. "Oh hell," he muttered. "Does that mean what I think —"

"Shut it," Harry cut him off sharply. He pointed his wand at the journalist and Monroe slumped over, unconscious. With another flick of his wand Harry raised the man in the air, then threw the Invisibility Cloak over him. A final flick dropped the man into the chair he'd been sitting in. Harry reached over and turned a lever on the fireplace to the "on" position, and green flames erupted in its hearth. Stepping out of the fireplace, Ginny Thomas nodded at Harry. "Sorry to bother you," she said, looking around the room as she stepped toward him. "I guessed that you might have gone home since you haven't been back to the office yet."

"What do you need?" Harry asked her, without preamble.

Ginny blinked, taken aback by his abruptness. "Your appointments for the afternoon —"

"Cancel them," Harry said. "Tell them I'm not feeling well."

"We can set up a phone conference," Ginny suggested, "if you don't feel well enough to be at the office."

"No," Harry shook his head. He faked a cough, then turned back to her. "I'm going to lie down as soon as you leave. Let Hermione know I'm home sick, but it's not serious enough for her to come home —"

"Are you sure?" Ginny looked concerned. "You hardly ever get sick, Harry. Maybe you should let them check you out at St. Mungo's —"

"No," Harry said again, more sharply. When Ginny looked startled, he tried to look regretful. "Look, I'm sorry," he told her. "I'm just feeling like I need to lie down for a while. That's all it is. If I'm still not feeling well by the time Hermione gets home, we'll go to St. Mungo's. How's that sound?"

"Okay, I guess," Ginny said, uncertainly. "I'll, uh — I'll head back to work, then." She turned back at the fireplace, but stopped and looked at him again. "Why was the Floo Damper on?"

"What?" Harry said, looking at her blankly. "Oh, I guess it was, wasn't it. That's why you signaled me."

"Well, yeah," Ginny said, with a bit of exasperation. "Otherwise I couldn't get through, could I then?" She gave him an odd look. "Why would you turn off the Floo Damper if you were feeling sick?"

Harry shrugged. "I dunno, I don't remember doing it. Must've been more out of it than I thought." He smiled at her. "Good thing you came by — Hermione might not have been able to come home tonight until I woke up." A thought suddenly occurred to him, and a frown passed quickly across his face.

"Yeah," Ginny said, slowly. She turned toward the fireplace again, then stopped once more. "By the way, have you heard from that Monroe fellow again?"

Harry raised an eyebrow at her. "That journalist? As a matter of fact, he showed up at the shop today."

"Really?" Ginny acted quite surprised by this. "How could he get into Diagon Alley? He's a Muggle!"

"Apparently not," Harry disagreed. "He bought a wand from Bill and walked into Weasleys' just like a real wizard. And he was able to use the wand to cast spells — I tested him to be sure."

"What were you doing there?" Ginny wanted to know. "You haven't come by the shop in years."

"Just overdue for a chat with the boys," Harry shrugged. "We lost track of time; when we came down to the shop, Monroe was there talking with Verity, Angelina and Luna."

"So what happened?" Ginny asked, anxious to hear details.

"Not much," Harry demurred. "I brought him back here, then told him I didn't appreciate him trying to play me for a fool by pretending to be a Muggle, and sent him on his way. I don't think we'll be seeing him again, after all the times he's been Obliviated." He gestured toward the elevator doors. "Well, I hope you don't mind taking care of things at work while I'm resting — you can use the elevator down to the offices, if you prefer."

"Oh — of course," Ginny smiled at him, then walked over to the elevator. "You know I want your job someday, by the way," she said as she walked past him.

Harry laughed. "It won't be long before I'm ready to give it to you!" They both nodded at one another again, then Ginny took out her wand and waved it at the elevator doors. After a few moments they opened, and Ginny entered. She turned and nodded a final time at Harry, then pushed a button inside the elevator.

Harry watched as the doors closed, and for several seconds after. He then turned back to the chair where Monroe's invisible, unconscious form was. He pulled off the Cloak then pointed his wand at the man. "Innervate," he said, and Monroe's eyes blinked as he returned to consciousness.

He looked up at Harry. "Got rid of her, then?" he asked, with a shrewd smile.

Harry stared at him a long moment. "You're not really helping your case, you know. If you were only pretending to be unconscious while listening in on my conversation, I might chalk that up as further proof that you're Voldemort."

Monroe chuckled. "I'm just having you on a bit," he said. "It wasn't hard to guess that your secretary might be looking for you in the middle of a workday afternoon. But I didn't know for sure until you just confirmed it."

"I haven't confirmed anything," Harry retorted. "You have no idea who was just here, do you?" Harry was looking directly into Monroe's eyes as he asked this.

Monroe shrugged. "We can go with that for now," he agreed. "Especially since, if I guessed correctly who was just here, you'll use it against me."

Harry's wand flicked, and the ropes fell away from Monroe's body, dissolving to nothingness as they fell. "It looks like you're going to see more of my home than I anticipated at first," Harry said. "I don't want to remain here in case anyone else decides to come calling. I can't leave the Floo Damper closed now or they'll be suspicious of that."

Monroe stood slowly. "If you don't want me to see this place, I can just leave," he suggested.

Harry shook his head. "Not a chance. Besides, I thought you'd want to stay anyway, to disprove whether you're Voldemort."

"The onus is on you to do that," Monroe pointed out. "You're the one making that claim — you're the one who has to back it up."

"Then I insist you remain," Harry replied. "So I can do so."

"Fine by me," Monroe said. "Because you're wrong."

"We'll see," Harry muttered, then went over to the door leading out of the room. His wand made several complicated motions toward it, then he turned and made another series of motions at Monroe. Finally his wand stopped moving, and Harry opened the door.

"You're protected from the defense wards now," he told Monroe. "But stick close to me — if you get too far away, you'll be immobilized."

"Don't trust me, eh?" Monroe grinned.

"Nope," Harry said, and gestured for the journalist to follow him.

=ooo=

The corridor leading away from the entry opened into a larger room, one that seemed to be a living area, though it looked more like a library to Monroe — the walls were covered in shelves filled with what looked like thousands upon thousands of books. There were a couple of comfortable-looking loungers with a small table between them, with books stacked haphazardly on it. Monroe didn't see a television, but there was a piece of furniture that looked like a television stand positioned in front of the two lounge chairs.

Harry led Monroe through this room toward one of the shelf-covered walls. He gestured with his wand as they came close and a section of shelves opened inward, exposing another corridor. "You sure love your secret passapges, don't you?" Monroe said with a trace of irony in his voice.

"Hogwarts spoiled me," Harry replied. "Follow me."

The corridor, lit by a ceiling that glowed with magical light as they entered, sloped upward as Harry and Monroe walked along it, ending at a formidable looking door that took Harry several passes with his wand to open.

They stepped into a strange, circular room, one with a dozen doors along the walls. As soon as Harry closed the door behind them the room began to spin, faster and faster until the doors were just blurs. Monroe watched this activity with some apprehension — what was Potter up to with all this, and when was he going to settle down and start trying to prove his claim?

The spinning finally slowed and came to a halt. At once Harry called out, "Interview Room," and one of the doors flashed red momentarily. Harry walked over to that door and opened it, gesturing for Monroe to enter.

The room was small and nearly bare, with only two wooden armchairs inside facing one another. The walls, floor and ceiling were flat white; even though there were no visible lights, the room seemed to have its own illumination, just as the corridor did.

"Interview room?" Monroe was looking around, shaking his head. "This looks more like that interrogation room at the Ministry," he scoffed. "Am I going to end up stuck to one of these chairs, like I did there?"

"We won't need to resort to that, I hope," Harry replied. He gestured to one of the chairs. "Have a seat."

Monroe deliberately sat down in the other chair. "Suit yourself," Harry said, and took the first chair.

"So, what's your evidence?" Monroe asked, as Harry slid his wand into a pocket.

Harry sat back, regarding Monroe for some time before he answered. "Do you know how much information I was able to dig up on you over the past day?" he asked.

"No idea," Monroe said. "But it shouldn't be difficult for someone with your resources to hack into both government and private databases and find information on me."

"It wasn't," Harry agreed. "But your background information turns out to be rather dodgy."

"How's that?" Monroe challenged.

"Your history in Britain only goes back to 2010, when you were sent here from America by the publishers of Singularity Today to help research background material for a series being written at the time," Harry said. "You were hired on by the magazine afterwards, somehow skirting the residency requirements of foreign nationals, and turned out a few pieces for the mag every year until late 2015, when you began pestering me for an interview."

"Sounds pretty sinister," Monroe cracked, his cheek resting on one arm propped on his armchair. "I guess that proves I am Voldemort, then?"

"There's more," Harry went on. "It's back in America that your history really gets dodgy. You accepted a job at Paragon Publications, in 2010, but before that, information about James Monroe becomes rather tangled. The only information I have on James Monroe that gets close to matching you has you born on July 31, 1980, in Kansas City, Missouri, attending Kansas State University between 1998 and 2004, graduating with dual Bachelor of Science degrees in Software Engineering and Computer Science from the College of Engineering. That doesn't seem like a path that would lead to being a journalist, I have to say."

"Stranger things have happened," Monroe commented, still leaning on his hand. "Is that what you're offering as 'proof' I'm really Voldemort?"

"No," Harry replied. "But that same James Monroe is still in America right now, working for a company in Kansas City, the same company he's been working for since 2005. And you and he look identical to one other."

"So, that just makes him my doppleganger," Monroe shrugged. "Obviously, I can't be him if he's still in America. And there's no reason to think I stole his identity."

"I'd agree with that," Harry said, "if you were still just a Muggle. But wizards have a lot more options in the identity department than Muggles do, and now that you've been revealed as a wizard, I have to consider those options as well."

"It's going to be quite a leap from me finding out this morning that I'm a wizard, to proving that I'm Voldemort and that I stole this identity from a Muggle six years ago and have lived as Muggle all that time, only to walk into the lions' den at Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes and risk blowing everything," Monroe argued.

"Quirrell did lots of things that, in hindsight, were indications of his affiliation with Voldemort," Harry pointed out. "I always felt an aura of doom about him, such that I could never get closer than a few feet from him before it became nearly overwhelming."

"And yet you and I have spent hours within a few feet of one another," Monroe said, a triumphant gleam in his eye. "Does that not disprove your claim?"

"It doesn't help it much," Harry admitted. "But I have to assume Quirrell (and therefore Voldemort) felt it as well, and that he would have taken steps to negate that feeling, if at all possible, if he's back. That way, I wouldn't feel threatened."

"It sounds like you're coming up with ad hoc reasons to explain away the disparities between me and Voldemort," Monroe said, icily. "Isn't that something a rationalist is supposed to avoid?"

"Not really, in this case," Harry disagreed. "During the interview, and afterwards, neither I nor Malfoy detected that you were a wizard being passed off as a Muggle. There was a trace of magic about you, but I knew Ginny had Obliviated you — that's what I thought I was detecting. And Malfoy, at the Ministry, ignored it because he knew (or guessed) that I'd Obliviated you as well. You might have maneuvered Ginny into doing that to disguise the fact that you were disguised."

"That sounds more like rationalization than rationality," Monroe sneered.

"Well, I do have a final test," Harry added. "So it's still a matter of rationality, assuming you're willing to take the test."

Curiously, Monroe looked interested rather than apprehensive, an affect that vaguely bothered Harry. Could Voldemort have somehow foreseen what he intended to use on this man, and taken steps to counter it? That was beginning to sound like rationalization, Harry realized. He would have to watch that — such muddy thinking could also interfere with the deeper plans he had, plans that were themselves nearing culmination.

"Whatever this test is," Monroe said. "I'll do my best to pass it."

"You won't have to do anything, the test will work with or without your consent. I'll be back in a moment." Harry opened the door and left the room, leaving Monroe alone and staring after him.

=ooo=

The fireplace swirled with emerald flames, and Ginny stepped out of them and into the office where Fred, George and Ron anxiously awaited her return. As she shook soot from her red hair, Fred asked, "Was he there?"

Ginny nodded. "He had to turn the Floo Damper back on so I could get through. He said he wasn't feeling well and was there to have a lie down. Said he didn't know how the Damper got turned off."

"But what about Monroe?" George pressed. "Was he there?"

"Harry said he'd brought him there, then let him go," Ginny answered. "He wasn't in the room as far as I could tell, but Harry might have had time to put him somewhere else. He's got three whole floors in that building, you know."

"We could check with the Ministry," Ron suggested. "See if they were still watching for Monroe to walk out of that building."

"Dunno if that'll matter now," Fred muttered. "At least as far as Harry and the Ministry are concerned — they were worried he was telling secrets to a Muggle. If Monroe is really a wizard, especially an American one, they might want to have words with him, though. He should have at least notified the local magical government when he took up residency here."

"Unless someone Obliviated him and brought him over here without his knowledge," George hypothesized. "But it's hard to imagine anyone but a Dark wizard doing that to another wizard. Maybe some American Dark wizard wanted Monroe out of the country, and dumped him here with false memories of himself as a Muggle."

"Could that be what Harry is trying to figure out?" Ginny asked. "You know he can't resist a mystery. Plus, if a Dark wizard's involved he can get really intense…"

Fred and George both nodded, distracted. Harry was predictable that way — the disaster with Quirrell at the end of his first year had made him quite wary of such things. So far as they knew the Quirrell-Voldemort fusion had been dealt with in the final days of Harry's first year at Hogwarts, with Quirrell dead and Voldemort's ghost banished from existence. The next six years were pretty much normal until Harry's final year, when he became brooding and secretive, and his relationship with Hermione soured. Ron had taken up with her then, a dream come true for him, until the following fall when Hermione began attending a Muggle college instead of going to work at the Ministry, as Ron had. Ron had appeared to shrug their breakup off as if it were no big deal, just the way things turned out, but contrary to what Luna believed, Ron did earn the five N.E.W.T.S. needed to join the Auror Training program, largely in part with Hermione's help during his final year. After their breakup, however, Ron dropped out of Auror Training and went to work with his father in the Misuse of Muggle Artifacts Office, part of the Department of Magical Law Enforcement, where he was when he met Luna Lovegood once again and began seeing her regularly.

"Bollocks," Ron said suddenly, frowning. "Harry Potter's nearly a Dark wizard himself. Dumbledore barely kept him out of it — that's why he spent so much time with Harry his last year at school!"

"You're wrong about Harry," Ginny said fiercely, getting in Ron's face to argue with him. "The work he's been doing has been to help people, including Muggles, live better lives! You don't know what you're talking about, Ron!"

"Yeah, you would defend him, wouldn't you?" Ron snapped at her. "You're still in love with him!" He pursed his lips and made an exaggerated kissing sound, mocking her.

Ginny's face turned almost as red as her hair. "And you're still in love with —"

"Cut it out!" George said loudly, cutting off her retort. "Stick to the problem at hand, you two!" Ginny and Ron both glowered at each other, but they backed away from each other with no further comment, pointedly returning their attention to Fred and George.

"What d'you want to do, then?" Ginny asked, bitingly. "Go back to Harry and make him tell us what's going on? Or maybe you want to get Malfoy involved again?"

"Come on, sis." Fred looked offended at her final suggestion. "Malfoy's been gunning for Harry practically since his daddy bought the Head Aurorship for ickle Draco. What he doesn't know can only be in Harry's best interest."

"Besides," George added, "if we're going to anyone other than Harry, it's going to be someone with real leverage on him—" both Fred and George grinned evilly, and said in one voice "— his wife."

=ooo=

Harry was gone for several minutes, long enough that Monroe had started to worry that he'd be left alone for hours. And without his wand, which was a serious no-no in the Wizarding community — you didn't take a wizard's wand from him without good reason. Only an agent of the Ministry of Magic had the right to confiscate a wizard's wand, and Harry Potter-Evans-Verres was not an agent of the Ministry, so far as Monroe knew.

He also had the feeling that Potter was watching him, somehow, from somewhere outside this room, waiting to see what he would do if left alone long enough. It made Monroe want to stand up and pace around the room, though he'd resisted doing that so far; there was no telling what Potter would read into anything he did.

The door to the room opened and Harry stepped in carrying a glassful of water. "That took longer than I expected," Harry said, apologetically. "I thought I'd see if you wanted some water, since we're out of Pepsi."

"Water's fine," Monroe said, extending his hand toward it, but Harry lifted the glass above his head and poured it over him. Monroe jerked as the cold liquid spilled over him, then glared up at Harry.

"What the hell?" he shouted. "What'd you do that for?"

"Just a little test," Harry said, calmly. His wand was out and pointed at Monroe. The glass vanished from his hand and he stepped back, watching Monroe closely. The journalist was now wet and angry, but nothing else had changed about him.

"That 'water' was from Gringotts," he said. "It's known as the Thief's Downfall — goblins use it when they suspect someone of being deceptive. It washes away all enchantments and magical concealment. If you had been Voldemort, it would have revealed you in your true form."

"And what if I'd been possessed, as you also suspected?" Monroe snapped, shaking water out of his hair.

"The Thief's Downfall would have canceled the possession spell, separating you and Voldemort," Harry answered.

"What if he didn't need a spell?" Monroe wondered. His anger had already dissipated. Using the goblin anti-deception water had been brilliant on Potter's part. "Couldn't his soul just slip into me and take me over somehow?"

Harry looked annoyed at the question. "There's no evidence that souls even exist," he said shortly.

"Then how do you explain Horcruxes?" Monroe asked, his eyes locked on Harry's.

There was silence in the room for quite a while.

"How do you know about Horcruxes?" Harry finally asked.

"It's part of the curriculum at the Salem Institute," Monroe said.

"But you said you attended Hogwarts," Harry objected. "Your memory confirms you were here!"

"But I never said I attended all seven years here," Monroe answered. "I went back to America at the beginning of my third year, to attend school there. By the end of my second year, I realized that the Ministry had a stranglehold on the magic being taught at Hogwarts, especially defense magic. The Defense professor they provided for our second year confirmed that. My parents and I researched schools that had a more progressive outlook on wizard education, and we landed on the Institute.

"The advanced Magical Defense classes went into detail about techniques used by Dark wizards to render themselves invulnerable from harm, or extremely durable," Monroe continued. "Wizards can create a phylactery, what you'd call a Horcrux, to store their life force, or soul. Part of that advanced training includes a magical agreement with the head of the school not to divulge information about such magic to wizards who haven't had such training. Most of the schools in Europe, including Hogwarts, haven't taught anything about Horcruxes in many decades, even the 'iffy' schools like Durmstrang."

"If that part's true," Harry argued. "You shouldn't have been able to say anything about Horcruxes in front of me."

"Except it's pretty obvious you already know about Horcruxes," Monroe told him. "Since you believed I was Voldemort, who was supposedly destroyed in 1992 along with Quirinus Quirrell."

But Harry had turned away, deep in thought. When he turned back to Monroe, he had a calculating expression. "Did the Salem Institute teach you anything about an ancient spell called the Interdict of Merlin?"

"A few things," Monroe answered. "It's a spell that Merlin created near the end of his life, possibly as a response to what he saw as an unchecked proliferation of powerful magic brought about by schools like Hogwarts. He was afraid that wizards would become ascendant over Muggles, whom he thought had more potential than their magical counterparts.

"The Interdict affected Britain, Europe and most of Asia Minor — essentially the extent of the world as Merlin knew it at that time. It seems to be slowly expanding as well; most of the Americas are covered by it now, and most of Asia as well. There are very few places left on Earth it hasn't reached yet."

"Examples?" Harry prompted.

"Antarctica, most likely," Monroe suggested. "The Interdict seems to spread in response to magical activity, and I doubt many wizards have traveled there. But that may be moot now — there are almost no ancient books left that contain spells affected by the Interdict."

"But do you think those books, if some could be found, could be read and understood if the wizard went to Antarctica?" Harry pressed.

"Probably, for a while," Monroe agreed. "But using magic in Antarctica will cause the Interdict to spread there as well, and no one has tried to figure out how quickly the Interdict renders old spell books unreadable."

Monroe was giving Harry an odd look. "I'd have thought that you would have known all this already, Potter."

"I did," Harry nodded. "I just wanted to check your knowledge against mine. Why do you think we haven't been able to duplicate some of those ancient spells. After all, just because we can't glean the information from old books doesn't mean we can't re-invent a spell that was used long ago."

"It may not be that simple," Monroe disagreed. "One of my teachers suggested that the Interdict worked like a Fidelius Charm, but if a wizard hadn't passed on his powerful spells to an apprentice before he died, his death would cause the knowledge of that spell to be lost forever. Once the last wizard died before passing on any powerful spells he or she knew, those spells can no longer be known as long as the Interdict is in effect."
Harry was nodding. "That's what I think as well — all my research points to that conclusion."

"What did your teachers say about it?"

"The Interdict of Merlin is one of the unspoken subjects at Hogwarts, along with Horcruxes and a few other bits of Dark magic," Harry said. "While the Interdict isn't itself Dark, nobody wants to point to Merlin as the reason why we're losing knowledge about spells — he's almost a sacred figure here in Britain."

"I guess I understand that," Monroe nodded. "But he's not quite that revered at the Salem Institute."

Monroe was still giving Harry an odd look. "An hour ago you were almost ready to kill me," he said, "if you'd been convinced I was Voldemort. Now it seems like you've done a complete turnabout."

Harry had a wry look on his face. "I wasn't really that convinced you were Voldemort," he said. "There was a possibility, but only a bare one. But I was interested in how you managed to make everyone at Hogwarts forget you, and why no one has ever mentioned you in the twenty-five years since I began going to school there. That modified Fidelius Charm is very complicated magic. Did your parents help you with that?"

"No," Monroe said. "I designed it myself, in my sixth year at the Institute—mostly as a challenge from a teacher in my Advanced Spell Design class. She told our class that certain spells, like certain potion ingredients, were not miscible."

"She's not exactly wrong, there," Harry said, dryly.

"True, but she didn't think the Fidelius and the Memory Charms could be put together to any good effect. She was hard to convince, too — when I turned in my paper showing how to do so, she only gave me a B." Monroe shrugged. "So I cast the spell on myself. It made for an interesting final year, since everyone in school could talk to me but nobody, not even the teachers, talk or write anything about me."

Monroe chuckled, a bit ruefully. "I became a non-entity at the Institute. In a way, my teacher was right, since that wasn't a very positive experience. My transcript at the Institute is incomplete, because no one could add to it after I cast the spell. The teachers couldn't even grade my homework assignments!"

"But I was able to discuss my interview with you with the Weasleys," Harry said. "Did you cancel the spell? But — if that was true," he realized even as he asked the question, "I would have remembered you at Hogwarts!"

"I modified the spell," Monroe said. "I made the Fidelius effective from 2010 back to my birth, so that anyone who'd met me after I came to England would know me only as a journalist from America."

"Pretty complicated magic," Harry said. It was almost a compliment, coming from him.

"So now what?" Monroe wanted to know. "Are you done with me yet? Do I get to go free?"

"If you want," Harry said. He took out his wand and pointed it at the door; a loud clack sounded and the door swung open a few inches. He took Monroe's wand out of his pocket and handed it to him. "Sorry for taking this," he said. "I didn't want you leaving before we had a chance to talk. Now, unless you're anxious to go back to your Muggle job of writing for Singularity Today, there's something you can help me with, if you're interested."

Monroe stood and walked over to the door, but turned and looked at Harry again. "I can't go back to that job," he said. "You know that as well as I do. If I'm a wizard, I should try to get integrated back into wizarding society."

"I agree," Harry nodded. "That's why I'm asking for your help."

"What do you want help with?" Monroe asked.

"I want you to help me bring about the Magical Singularity."

Chapter 8: The Magical Singularity

Updated 2/10/2012

"Diagon Alley is full of ears…"

"The Magical Singularity?" Monroe repeated. Comprehension of Harry's method was beginning to dawn on him. "Then all this talk about the Technological Singularity —"

"Is just a cover," Harry finished. "I've been using the Technological Singularity as a parallel model for the Magical Singularity. It only makes sense that's what wizards should be trying to achieve — not just the immortality of individuals, or even of all wizards, but the ability of everyone to use magic, Muggles and wizards alike!"

Monroe's brow was furrowed in concentration as he tried to wrap his mind around the idea. "I — I suppose I understand," he said at last. "But your company looks like it's really working toward the Singularity, not just giving it lip service."

"It is," Harry agreed. "If a technological Singularity can come about before I can create the magical Singularity, it probably should. The better advancement always wins, so if technology can beat magic to a Singularity, I'll go with technology.

"But I think magic is ultimately more powerful than Muggle technology, and that's why I've been pursuing a parallel path with it. Wizards have managed to keep their existence secret from most of humanity for centuries now — if the Magical Singularity comes about it could be possible that everyone will be able to use magic. That's why I'd like you to —"

"Before we get into what you want from me —" Monroe interrupted, then looked around the room "—can we get out of here and discuss things somewhere a bit more comfortable? I still feel like you're about to interrogate me."

A few minutes later Harry and Monroe were both seated in plush recliners in a room Harry had called the "Den Room" in the spinning circular room. Each of them now held a drink — Harry had a butterbeer and Monroe a Pepsi — Harry did have a supply of Pepsi, it turned out.

"I get what the idea behind the tech Singularity it," Monroe was saying as he sipped at his drink. "But I'm not sure what you think a magical Singularity is going to entail. Magical knowledge increasing faster than wizards can comprehend?"

"Something along those lines, but it's going to require increased intelligence to handle that," Harry replied. "I've been looking for ways to increase human intelligence magically, like Rowena Ravenclaw's diadem was supposed to increase the wearer's wisdom. So far I haven't come up with anything, probably due to the Interdict of Merlin."

"Have you tried travelling to locations where the Interdict isn't powerful enough to interfere with comprehension when reading ancient books?" Monroe asked.

"Yes, but its effects immediately start to encroach upon an unaffected area whenever any magic is used," Harry complained. "There are so few places left that I'm afraid to use them before I understand how to keep the Interdict from reaching them."

"Have you tried travelling to the location using Muggle means, and avoided using any kind of magic while you're there?" Monroe suggested.

"Yes," Harry said, unhappily. "But the effect still begins to creep in almost as soon as I arrive."

"Hmm," Monroe mused silently for some time. Then, "Who else knows you're working toward a Magical Singularity?"

"The Weasleys have been collecting ancient magic books for me for years, but as far as I know they think it's a hobby, that I just like to collect books, even useless ones."

"Does your wife know?"

"No," Harry said. "But she may suspect I'm doing more than I'm telling her, I've gone on trips without telling her why often enough now. But for all I know she might suspect me of having an affair."

"Are you?" Monroe asked, bluntly. "She may suspect you for other reasons."

Harry chuckled. "I'm not," he replied. "But so far she's made no insinuations that I've taken as suspicion on her part."

"Not even of Ginny Thomas?" Monroe suggested.

Harry was silent for several seconds, frowning. "Why would you say that?" he asked at last. "Ginny's married, too."

Monroe shrugged. "I've noticed the way she looks at you," he said. "It seems like more than a profession interest in you or your work."

"I think you're way off-base," Harry disagreed. "But either way, she doesn't know about my research on magic; neither does her husband Dean. He knows I'm doing magical research, but he thinks it's just to keep my wizarding skills sharp."

"And the Ministry? If the head Auror has a hard-on for you he might have surveillance in place even you don't know about."

"Malfoy?" Harry almost looked amused at that. "Draco's not a real threat to me. He's biding his time until his father dies or makes him Lord of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Malfoy, and I don't think Lucius is anxious to do that, not while his son is in such a useful position in the Ministry."

Monroe was silent for a time. Then, "Well, I'll grant that you know him better than I do. And what you tell your wife is your own business. As well as what you tell yourself about your relationship with Ginny Thomas.

"But I am surprised you haven't brought the Weasleys into this project of yours. As I recall, they were a couple of wisenheimers at school, but they were pretty brilliant with their magic, especially the magical novelties they cobbled up in the first few years I was at Hogwarts."

"They are good," Harry agreed. "The reason I haven't gone to them is mostly because of their younger brother, Ron. Ron and I met the day I went to Hogwarts, on Platform 9¾, and it wasn't a good experience. I spoke to Draco Malfoy, who'd I'd met a few days earlier in Diagon Alley, and Ron assumed if I was talking to him I must be a bad guy."

"That seems a bit previous of him," Monroe noted.

"And I insulted Quidditch," Harry added, a bit wryly. "Told him that the Snitch was a stupid addition that made most of the game moot. I think that was the final straw with Ron." Monroe chuckled, then suddenly did a double-take at Harry.

"So all that business of mucking about with the rules of Quidditch during our second year — that was your doing?" he asked, eyes narrowed.

"I'm afraid so," Harry admitted.

"You were a boy of many talents, even then," Monroe said, not admiringly. "How did you ever find time to study?"

Harry smiled thinly. "Oh, I was able to make time."

Monroe looked at him for several seconds. "Oh, I get it. You had one of those Time Turner things, didn't you?"

"How'd you hear about those?" Harry asked, a bit more sharply he needed to. "Everyone was supposed to think they were — er, Spimster wickets, as I recall."

"Yeah," Monroe agreed dryly, "A device that treated the rare but non-contagious magical condition called Spontaneous Duplication. But just about everyone in Ravenclaw knew what they really were. We were all envious of the kids that got them. I wanted one, too, but McGonagall never called me into her office to give me one."

"Who knows?" Harry commented. "You might've gotten one your third year, when your class schedule increased."

"Maybe," Monroe shrugged. "At the Salem Institute the teachers used the Time Turners, not the students, under the assumption that adult wizards were better experienced in the intricacies of time travel and its hazards."

"I wonder," Harry said idly, almost to himself. "If the Time Turners those Salem wizards used had protective shells on them, to prevent anyone from accidentally breaking them…"

"I never saw one," Monroe answered, though Harry hadn't really asked the question of him. "So I can't tell you." He drained the last of his glass of soda.

"Do you have any of these books you've been talking about?" he asked abruptly. "It might be useful to look at them, if you do."

Harry smiled. "Oh, I have a few," he said, standing. "Follow me." He led them back to the circular room, where after it stopped spinning Harry said, "Tome Room," and a door flashed red. They entered that door, following a short corridor that led to a small room filled with shelves of books.

But what books they were! There were no neatly ordered shelves lined with row upon row of classroom texts, but books of all shapes and sizes: large wood-and-leather bound tomes, grimoires and manuals, small diaries, even loose parchments and scrolls.

Monroe was looking around the room in wonderment. "I had no idea so many of these old books existed. How many are there in here?"

"Roughly a thousand books," Harry answered. "Maybe half that many loose scrolls and sheets of parchment." He took down a coffee table-sized book and opened it on a small table, then stepped aside so Monroe could examine it.

Monroe examined each page carefully. "Some of these spells are readable," he mused as he leafed through the tome. "Some of them are written in English, even if the wording is archaic. I can even read some of the ones written in runes. But yes, some of the words in here are nothing but gibberish to me." He looked up at Harry. "Do we know how powerful or complex the spell has to be before the Interdict makes it unreadable?"

Harry waved an arm around the room, gesturing at the books in general. "I've looked through all of these books, and some of them seem to have spells ordered by complexity or overall power, but it's hard to say what spells we can learn from books today are the most powerful ones the Interdict allows us to read. The Patronus, Fidelius, and Protean Charms are all complicated spellwork, but all of them are available from the Standard Book of Spells, except for the Fidelius, which is specialized magic, but even it can be found in certain spellbooks in clear language."

Monroe turned to a page with one of the affected spells on it. The words were written in runes, which he and Harry could both read, but the words made no sense. "Which of these books have you tried to take outside the Interdict's effects?" Monroe asked.

Harry took out his wand and pointed to a book on the opposite side of the room. It floated off its shelf and over to him. Monroe closed the book he was looking at and they opened Harry's. It, too, was full of both clear and Interdict-obscured spells. Harry flipped to a page about halfway through the book.

"Here's a spell I'd planned to learn once outside the Interdict," he said. They both stared at the text. Like the first book, it was written in runes, but there was transliterated text written in the Roman alphabet next to the runes.

Glycpto Gragnor Fustenis

Msesno gyan do vodop kakan dozir mechaz veeropo badduga voco neobo zsow —
Deulo bapgo moernoe ves tuo bysizi os vettoero —
Basmo zeoloe fzasula theogen gana posento vudu nokwurtz yegrhol —
Zudunu algolo fresen bodogo mazunla —
Festuni lecto alconro poesteo vacuaeliso meonoroso vuptun —
Bagdos verun fallo beguna qaunowe yuoesolo…

"This was one spell I didn't have to translate from the runes," Harry said. "I thought it would save time, since I didn't know how much time I'd have before the Interdict would take effect where I was, but I didn't get more than the first line translated." He pulled out a piece of parchment that was folded and placed at the back of the book, and showed it to Monroe.

Glycpto Gragnor Fustenis
Mind Extension Potion

"That's interesting," Monroe commented, sounding excited. "But you could only translate one line?"

"Then the Interdict kicked in again," Harry said, in a chagrinned tone. "I was very excited to find something like this — it was a major disappointment not to be able to translate more than a bit of it. That's why we need to find a place the Interdict won't immediately render useless to us."

"Have you tried to dispel the Interdict in an area?" Monroe asked.

"It was the first thing I tried," Harry replied. "But there's no dispel charm powerful enough to block it, even temporarily." He shook his head in frustration. "The Interdict has been the biggest impediment I've had in the past decade to bringing about the Magical Singularity."

On one of the shelves, a small statue of Rowena Ravenclaw suddenly flashed red and a small chime sounded. "Hermione's home early," Harry said. "Well, that was unexpected. She must be worried about me," he smiled.

Harry looked at Monroe. "You might as well meet her," he said. "There's no way I could sneak you out of here, anyway."

Monroe gave him a look. "Are we going to tell her anything about —"

"Not a word," Harry warned. "As far as you're concerned, I invited you here, away from the Weasleys, so I could properly apologize for the treatment you received at the Ministry after our interview the other day."

"You never did really apologize for that, by the way," Monroe pointed out.

"I didn't?" Harry smiled again, more evilly this time. "Well, I probably would have gotten around to that, eventually…"

=ooo=

Draco Malfoy was not happy. Not happy at all. But what else was new these days?

The Head Auror had just received information that the Muggle he'd questioned for several hours over a suspicious interview with Harry Potter had turned up in Diagon Alley, bought a wand, and went to the Weasleys' joke shop, where Harry Potter just happened to be having lunch with Fred, George and Ron Weasley.

James Monroe, the Muggle in question, had shown no indication of being a wizard when in Malfoy's custody. He'd been Obliviated and released. But now, according to Malfoy's source, Potter had left the Weasley shop with Monroe, and neither of them had been seen since.

It was beginning to look like Potter was trying to play him for a fool, and Malfoy had already been played for a fool, long before he'd ever met Harry Potter. He wasn't going to let Potter get away with it again.

The question was, how was he going to play this? There was no point in going to the Minister — even if she didn't know what was going on with Potter and Monroe, she probably wouldn't give him any information unless she believed Potter was into something even she couldn't protect him from. Potter had the resources these days to keep most of his shady business practices off both the Muggle and wizarding radars.

And Monroe? As a Muggle he had merely been a pawn in the ongoing game he and Harry Potter played with one another these days, the "Catch-Me-If-You-Can" game that Potter dabbled in, such as the gray market in Ministry-sanctioned magic documents — books, scrolls, or parchments with text that the Interdict of Merlin had rendered unreadable.

Not that more than one couldn't play that game — Malfoy had a hundred or so books and scrolls himself, carefully secreted away in Malfoy Manor where even the best Aurors in his department couldn't detect them. He'd poured over the old books and scrolls himself, wondering how he would crack the Interdict if he were Harry Potter. There were a group of Unspeakables working on the problem as well, but neutralizing the Interdict had been an ongoing Ministry project for decades now, if not centuries, and no one was any closer to dispelling the Interdict or stopping its spread across the world; whenever wizards found a location where the Interdict was weak, it would invariably strengthen when someone tried to read one of the ancient texts affected by Merlin's spell.

But back to the matter at hand — Potter and Monroe, and whatever was going on between them. Potter couldn't be touched unless they caught him in a violation of Wizarding law, and it would have to be a very obvious violation.

Monroe, however, was a different matter entirely. If he'd actually bought a wand from Ollivanders, then he was an unregistered foreign wizard living in Britain under suspicious circumstances; they could pick him up the next time he appeared in public. If Potter knew anything about Monroe being a wizard (and it seemed certain he did; his source had informed Malfoy that Potter had tested Monroe's wizarding abilities) then Malfoy could bring him in to give corroborating evidence about Monroe, and there was nothing Granger could do to help him without it appearing like she was hindering his investigation. If she did that, Draco could likely persuade his father to fund a movement to have Granger voted out as Minister of Magic.

Draco managed a smile at that. Things weren't really as bad as he initially thought! He took two pieces of parchment out of his desk and wrote on them for several moments, then pressed a button on the lower edge of his desk, a button that summoned only two particular Aurors to his office. A few moments later his door opened and Crabbe and Goyle stepped in.

"You remember that Muggle we had in here the other day," Malfoy said, more as a statement than a question, and both men nodded shortly.

"Well, it turns out he's not a Muggle — he's a wizard, he bought a wand in Diagon Alley and was able to use it. I assume you two didn't perform any spells to verify he was a Muggle, did you?"

Crabbe and Goyle looked at one another in surprise. "Mr. Malfoy," Goyle said, hesitantly. "We had no reason to think he was anything other than what you told us — a Muggle!"

"If we thought you'd suspected anything like that we'd have tested him!" Crabbe protested.

"Enough," Malfoy said, holding up a hand for silence. "I had no reason to think he was anything but a Muggle, either. It looked like Potter was passing him hints about the Wizarding world; I wanted to catch him on Secrecy violations.

"But if Monroe is really a wizard, then he's in Britain illegally, and we can bring him in for questioning. He and Potter must have some kind of scheme cooked up, and I want to find out what it is." He handed the paper he had just written on to Crabbe. "Here's a warrant to search the premises at 93 Diagon Alley for any and all information about a wizard known as James Monroe. I want you to take an investigative team and make sure they search very carefully. You get me?"

Both Crabbe and Goyle smirked. "Sure, Mr. Malfoy," Crabbe nodded knowingly. "We'll make sure they turn the entire place over real good."

"Good," Malfoy said. "I want them closed down the rest of the day," he said. "I want to show the Weasleys what they're in for if they start getting too cozy with Harry Potter again."

"And if you see Monroe," he went on, handing the second parchment to Crabbe, "this is a warrant for his arrest, on the charge of failing to register with the Ministry. If you find Potter with him, arrest him, too — I'll figure out the appropriate charges, but you can tell him aiding and abetting if he asks."

Both men nodded and lumbered out of the room, leaving Draco smiling with satisfaction. At the very least, this would cause a major embarrassment for the Minister — at best, the Wizengamot (led by his father) would call for her to step down, and demand the election of a new Minister. If Draco could buy or steal enough votes to win that, it should convince his father that he was at last worthy to hold the title of Lord of the Most Ancient and Noble House of Malfoy.

=ooo=

"Hello, love," Harry said, giving his wife a peck on the cheek as she entered their apartment's living room. "How was your day?"

"Busy," Hermione said, shortly, then put her hand on Harry's forehead. "Are you alright? I heard you were not well."

"The rumors of my illness were greatly exaggerated," Harry quipped, as Hermione felt his cheek as well. "I was just having some indigestion after lunch with Fred, George and Ron; it's been a while since I've had fish and chips — I guess they didn't agree with me."

"Probably from that grease pit across from the Weasleys," Hermione shook her head disapprovingly. "They need another warning about their food quality, it seems." She took a small notebook out of her robe. "I'll have someone—"

"It's not a big deal," Harry said, putting a hand over the notebook. "None of the others had any symptoms, just me. And I'm better now."

"Do you want me to make you something to eat?" Hermione asked, eyeing him closely. "Or maybe you should lie down for a while —"

"No, I'm fine," Harry waved off the suggestions. "And besides, we have a guest I'd like to introduce you to, someone I met in Diagon Alley earlier today."

"Harry!" Hermione gave him a plaintive look. "I wish you'd warned me — I look a mess!"

"It's okay," Harry said, soothingly. "He and I have just been — well, catching up on old times." He turned toward the door and called, "James, you can come in now."

Monroe entered the room, smiling and nodding toward Hermione. "You remember my wife, Hermione Granger-Potter?"

"I don't believe we actually met," Monroe said. He put out a hand and Hermione shook it, mostly by reflex. "I've seen your picture in the Prophet, of course."

Hermione was giving him a strange look. "Excuse me," she said, baffled. "Aren't you supposed to be a Muggle?"

"I thought so," Monroe grinned, "until this morning. I woke up and suddenly all these memories came flooding into my head."

Hermione let go of his hand, her eyes flicking back and forth between Monroe and Harry. "Why did you think you were a Muggle?"

"I don't know," Monroe said. "Harry though I —"

"I came up with a couple of ideas why his memories might have been hidden," Harry cut over him. "But we still don't have anything concrete to go on, yet."

"Harry," Hermione was giving him a sharp look. "Does Malfoy know about this?"

"Well —" Harry glanced at his watch. "We've been talking for a few hours, now, so my guess is, yes, he does. I'm sure someone has told him by now."

Both Monroe and Hermione gave him curious looks. "It almost sounds like you suspect someone of informing on you," Monroe said.

"Diagon Alley is full of ears," Harry answered, obliquely.

"Did you register at the Ministry of Magic when you entered the country?" Hermione asked Monroe. Monroe shook his head.

"I don't remember entering Britain as a wizard," he said. "I didn't know anything about it at all until today!"

"The Aurors will have a legitimate reason to pick you up if you haven't registered as a foreign national living in Wizarding Britain within 30 days of entering the country," Hermione told him. "You'll have to go in as soon as possible and register."

"That's one reason why he's here," Harry said. "I'm hoping you can grease the wheels down at the Ministry a bit so Malfoy won't have any reason to hold him for questioning."

Monroe looked startled by the remark. "Questioning? Again?"

"He'll want to grill you for details about how and why you came to Britain, your purpose here, and how long you plan to stay," Harry said. "I'm sure he'll suspect some kind of collusion between you and me."

"And with me," Hermione added, unhappily. "If I cut through red tape to keep him away from Draco."

"Nothing he'll be able to prove," Harry dismissed her concern. "After all, he had James Obliviated. The case can be made that it went wrong."

"As I recall," Hermione pointed out. "Mr. Monroe was Obliviated several times in the last few days."

"Every time was justifiable under the circumstances," Harry argued.

Hermione shook her head, but Harry was right — at least, as far as she knew with the information she currently had. "Fine," she sighed, resigned to doing as he'd asked. "I'll have the necessaries expedited tomorrow morning. Mr. Monroe, you'll have to come to the Ministry tomorrow afternoon to sign the papers granting you status as a citizen of Wizarding Britain."

Monroe nodded. "Excellent!" Harry clapped him on the shoulder. "Hermione and I will treat you to dinner tomorrow night at Mary's Place. The food there is quite good."

But Hermione was shaking her head. "I can't," she said. "I can't bypass procedure to make Mr. Monroe a citizen and then be seen eating with him right after that. That's too much coincidence even for Draco to swallow!"

Harry's face fell. "I thought you enjoyed dinner at Mary's, love," he said in a disappointed tone. "Malfoy doesn't even need to know you're there."

Hermione gave him a wry look. "How are you going to arrange that?"

"You can use the Invisibility Cloak —"

Hermione's eyes flicked momentarily to Monroe. "Harry, I'm not going to sneak around like some thief in the night —!"

"It's not like that!" Harry objected.

"Well, it would feel like that to me!" Hermione waved her hands as Harry began to argue again. "No, no, no — you and Mr. Monroe go and have a nice dinner, you and I can go again some other night." She wagged a stern finger at him. "You do owe me for this, Harry."

"I know, love. Thank you!" Harry kissed her on the cheek again. "James and I are going to make arrangements for him to spend the night somewhere."

"Not here?" Hermione almost looked surprised. "That's probably a good idea, actually — Draco would surely suspect something was going on if he spent the night here."

"My thought exactly," Harry agreed. "I'll be back in a little while." He and Monroe left the living room, heading to the entrance room.

=ooo=

"That will be five Galleons," Hannah Abbott said, holding out her hand. Monroe dropped the coins onto her palm, and Hannah slipped them into a very secure pocket in her robes while at the same time extending a key for room 11 toward the unknown wizard who'd requested a room with her other hand.

"Checkout time is noon, Mr. Smith," she added, as the man nodded and began to turn away ("James Smith" was the name Monroe had signed in under). "Breakfast is served from seven-thirty to eleven."

"Thank you," Monroe smiled at the woman. He picked up the two butterbeers he'd ordered and turned to walk back to a table not far from the door to the pub. On his way a small man at a table raised a mug as he passed, smiling. Monroe nodded and raised a bottle as well, but gave the man a curious look as he continued on to the table where he sat across from another man sat, a cloak and hood concealing his features.

Hannah was looking at the hooded man as well. There was something familiar about him, but the hood and cloak obscured his features too much for her to recognize him.

"Who was that?" Monroe nodded toward the small man, who was taking large drinks from his mug between raising to each of the other patrons in the bar.

Harry leaned slightly to look around Monroe. "Oh, that's Dedalus Diggle," he said, leaning back quickly so Diggle wouldn't notice him and raise another toast. Harry didn't want to be noticed — it would also draw attention to Monroe, and they could certainly do without that! "An interesting fellow. He's obviously celebrating something this evening — I've never seen him drink so freely."

"Well, anyway, I'm set for the night," Monroe said as he set the other butterbeer he was carrying in front of Harry, who picked it up and took a quick gulp.

"She'll have everything set by lunch," he said, carefully avoiding using his wife's name in case Hannah was listening more closely than she appeared to be. "You can go in about one. I expect there'll be some — discussion — about your status, but it should go through."

"And then?" Monroe prompted.

"And then we can resume our discussions," Harry continued. Monroe nodded agreement.

"Have a good night's rest," Harry said, then tipped back the bottle of butterbeer, draining it. "Ahhhh…" His hood slipped back for a moment but he pulled it back over his face quickly. He wiped his mouth with the back of his hand, grinning at Monroe. "See you later, James."

"Take it easy," Monroe said, and Harry rose and left the Leaky Cauldron. Monroe drained his own bottle, then stood and walked up the wooden staircase leading to the rooms above the bar.

Hannah, who had watched both men leave, stood pondering what (and who) she thought she'd just seen, then informed one of her barmaids she would be in her office for a few minutes and entered the small room where she conducted her most important business.

She sat down at her desk, took a small piece of parchment and a quill, and began writing, certain that the person the note was for would find it interesting that Harry Potter had just been in the Leaky Cauldron with a wizard she'd never seen before. A wizard who matched the description of a fugitive the Ministry was on the lookout for.

=ooo=

Author's Note: For those of you who have been wondering, Less Wrong and I are not the same person.

Chapter 10: The Source of Magic

Updated 3/17/2012

"Bastard! Bastard! BASTARD!"

=ooo=

"What?" For a moment Draco Malfoy sat, mouth agape, dumbfounded by the sheer audacity of a man who would walk willingly into the lions' den of the Ministry of Magic, the very place that sought to capture him, and demand to see the Minister.

Then his lips set in a thin, hard line. There was only one explanation for such boldness, such arrogance. Granger was in on this somehow! Draco's mind worked furiously, trying to see how he could manipulate the circumstances to his advantage. If only Crabbe and Goyle had captured Monroe before he walked into the Ministry! He could have made something out of Monroe's status as an unregistered, illegal wizard!

But that opportunity had passed. Potter had something to do with this as well, of course — the note the Abbott woman had sent the Auror Department virtually put Potter and Monroe there together. The proprietress of The Leaky Cauldron understood who was calling the shots here at the Ministry. While Granger worked to "clean up" what she saw as a government riddled with corruption (herself and her supporters excepted of course), Draco had built alliances — uneasy ones, admittedly, based on influence and a quid pro quo mindset, but ones that worked for him and for his father. While Harry Potter was the de facto landlord of Diagon Alley these days, Draco Malfoy was the de facto rent and tax collector, and the shopkeepers there knew him as the man who kept Harry Potter's greed in check, allowing them to remain in business in spite of the strain Potter's rents and taxes put on them.

Of course, it would never do for them to know that most of the rent and tax gold Malfoy supposedly kept Potter from collecting had actually been put in place by men in the Ministry and Wizengamot that were beholden to Lord Malfoy.

He probably wouldn't be able to charge Monroe for being in Britain illegally; Malfoy could see that even now, but he might be able to salvage something out of this, if he could get Monroe alone for a few minutes. That could be risky — if Potter suspected anything Draco's efforts would be in vain. But it was worth the risk.

A bare moment had passed while Draco calculated all this. His eyes, now as cold and gray as his father's, returned to the young Auror as his face went deceptively neutral. "Where is Monroe now?" he asked in a calm tone.

If the young Auror was surprised by her Head's sudden mood swing, she kept it carefully hidden. "He's, uh, at the Security Station, sir."

"Has the Minister been informed yet?" Draco asked.

The young woman's eyes were beginning to look panicked. She's worried about giving me the wrong answer, Draco could see it. It was true enough; if she'd walked in five minutes ago and given him bad news, he would have likely had her shipped off to the Transylvania detail monitoring vampire activity in that region. He let a small amount of warmth show in his face, then spoke. "It's okay, Zeller, I just need to know."

Chriss Zeller nodded, relieved something awful wasn't going to happen to her. "We sent Alfred up to let her know." Alfred was the guard manning the Atrium security station; he'd replaced Eric Munch a number of years ago when Munch "retired" after inadvertently detaining a newly-appointed Head Auror, whom he hadn't recognized. It was one of the few times Draco had acted without thinking — he'd been incensed that the man hadn't realized who he was and fired him on the spot. It would have severely crippled his future at the Ministry if Lord Malfoy hadn't "arranged" for Munch to return to his position after the "misunderstanding" with the new Head Auror. Malfoy had the matter cleared up, and Munch was put on medical leave until his retirement a month later.

The story of Eric Munch was one of many Zeller had heard about her boss during her training period and the short time she'd worked in the Auror Department. She'd paled when the other Aurors had sent her to deliver the news about James Monroe to the Head. Zeller hoped her Occlumency training would hold as she asked, "Is there — is there anything else, sir?" hoping he was done with her.

"No, that's all," Malfoy said, waving her away. "Dismissed." Zeller nodded again and quickly retreated from the office.

After the door closed Malfoy turned to Crabbe and Goyle; they had remained silent, wondering how the Head would react to the news of Monroe's arrival at the Ministry. It could not be good for either of them, both men knew. Draco had dearly wanted the information he suspected Monroe had on Potter's plans for him, and they had failed to deliver.

But Malfoy merely said, "I want you to put Monroe in an interrogation room — I don't care which one, but use the coin to let me know."

Crabbe smiled thinly and nodded. The "coin" Draco referred to was a Galleon that had a Protean Charm on it, linked with a Galleon Draco kept with him at all times. Crabbe or Goyle could Transfigure their coins with a short message that would also appear on the Head's coin. It was a handy little device that ironically had been invented back in their school days by Hermione Granger, during the Very Bad Year when the Ministry had sent Dolores Umbridge to the school as its Defense professor, back when Cornelius Fudge suspected Dumbledore of mounting a takeover bid for the Ministry.

That fear had been groundless, of course — Dumbledore was crazy but he wasn't stupid; for reasons Draco had never understood about the Headmaster, that old, powerful wizard had no ambition beyond running Hogwarts. In fact, after the crisis with You-Know-Who at the end of Draco's first year, he hardly seemed to have any ambition at all, at least until some years later, when he began inviting Harry Potter to his office more and more, for what purpose Draco had never managed to learn.

Oh, how Draco had wished he could have been a fly Animagus during those years! He'd desperately tried to find a way to spy on Potter and Dumbledore during those meetings — his father had actually given him permission to use whatever means he could to do so, short of becoming an Animagus. The consequences of being an unregistered Animagus were too severe (two years in Azkaban) if he were to be caught, and being a registered Animagus effectively negated any advantage of being able to take another form. His father had forbade him from learning how to become one, though Professor Snape had been willing to teach him — apparently Snape had his own agenda against Potter, though Draco had never found out about that, either. The last few years at Hogwarts were frustrating ones for Draco Malfoy.

"Will do, Boss," Crabbe grunted, then both he and Goyle turned and left the office. Malfoy sat back in his chair, smiling slightly as he pulled the charmed Galleon from the hidden pocket where he kept it. As soon as they let him know where Monroe was, he would use the secret passage from his office to the interrogation area. And then he would set things in motion to bring Harry Potter down, once and for all.

=ooo=

Monroe sat in the uncomfortable wooden chair he'd been shoved at, watching the two large Aurors he'd so neatly avoided the previous evening. Both men's expressions were carefully neutral, unlike the first time he'd been in an interrogation room with them. Monroe supposed that they were keeping their emotions in check, for which he was grateful. It wasn't difficult to imagine they harbored some hard feelings about last night.

The larger of the two men moved casually out of view, reaching into a pocket as he did so. Monroe glanced at the other Auror, the one with coarse, bristle-like hair, then down toward his feet, though his head was turned enough that from the corner of his vision he saw the larger Auror tapping something in his hand with his wand. A moment later both hands disappeared momentarily into the large Auror's pockets, and he sauntered back into Monroe's field of vision.

"You did a pretty good job evading us last night," he said, in a tone more friendly than Monroe would have expected. "You were pretending to be Dedalus Diggle when we walked in, weren't you?"

"Of course." Monroe saw no reason to lie now. "I knew the owner had turned me in."

"How?" the smaller Auror asked, genuine curiosity in his voice.

"She was watching me as I went up to my room," Monroe answered. "There was more than idle interest in her eyes. I might have been wrong, but it seemed prudent to take precautions against anyone from the Auror Department showing up at my door that night."

"And what was Harry Potter's role in all this?" Crabbe, the larger Auror asked, a touch of impatience in his voice.

Monroe raised an eyebrow at the question. "Potter? I haven't seen Harry Potter since I left his office on August first."

"You sure about that?" a new but familiar voice asked. Monroe turned his head but the person speaking was already behind him. "We have information that you saw him just yesterday, at the Weasleys' shop in Diagon Alley."

"He was at the shop when I was there," Monroe admitted, with a shrug. "But he was having lunch upstairs with the Weasley boys, their wives told me. I was just there because I recognized the name from my time at Hogwarts. It was a coincidence that Potter was there at the same time. But he never came down to see me."

"That's not what they told us," the familiar voice behind him disagreed. Malfoy moved into his field of vision. "Are you sure you want to go with that story?"

"Yeah, I'm sure," Monroe said, calmly. That was the story Harry told him to go with — it was obvious Malfoy was trying to trip him up. A magical examination of the shop could put both Harry and Monroe at the shop at the same time, but it could not prove they spoke to one another. Veritaserum might prove it, but Monroe had already taken the antidote for that, and his Occlumency shields were firmly in place.

"Hmm," Malfoy said, turning toward Crabbe, his body hiding the coded hand gesture he made toward the large Auror. He stepped out of view behind Monroe once again.

Crabbe stepped forward and leaned down, putting his face inches from Monroe's. "You think you're pretty smart, don't you?" he sneered. "Suppose we told you we have recordings of you and Potter talking at the Weasley shop. What would you say then?"

"I'd say produce them," Monroe answered. Harry was too cautious for something like that, never mind the Weasley brothers allowing Ministry bugs in their shop.

"Maybe we will, at your trial," Goyle leaned down into Monroe's face as well. "It won't go well for you if you say you're innocent and we produce that recording."

Behind them, Malfoy had silently taken out his wand and was pointing it at Monroe. He wordlessly cast the Ministry Trace spell on him.

The Trace was a spell placed on every newborn witch or wizard, a spell that allowed the Ministry to track their location and alert them whenever magic was cast by them or around them. Normally, it broke automatically when the witch or wizard reached their majority, seventeen years of age, and could not be cast on an adult wizard.

This spell, however, had been specially developed by the Department of Mysteries to allow special surveillance of witches or wizards operating undercover to locate Dark Wizards and those suspected of other high crimes. It allowed the Ministry to listen in on conversations in the vicinity of the bewitched wizard, and was effective through nearly every ward or anti-detection spell. No one outside the highest levels of the Auror Department knew the spell existed; not even the Minister of Magic herself was privy to its existence. This spell would give Draco the advantage he needed — the ability to hear firsthand what Potter and Monroe were talking about. Harry Potter's interest in this wizard had gone completely out of proportion for a mere former classmate that had been posing as a Muggle for the past twenty-odd years.

"I suppose that's a chance I'll have to take," Monroe replied, in a dry voice, looking directly into Crabbe's beady eyes. The two men stared at each other for several long seconds. Behind them, the door to the room opened and closed, and there was a muted conversation. Finally Crabbe sneered and stepped back.

"Yeah, I guess you will," he said. He looked up at Malfoy. "Any other questions for him, sir?" he asked, already knowing the answer.

"…No," Malfoy finally said, sounding disappointed. "I've just been notified that this man has been duly registered as a wizard in Great Britain, retroactive to his original entry into our jurisdiction five years ago, and the charges have been dropped. He's free to leave under his own recognizance. Turn him loose."

Malfoy walked quickly out of the room, smiling as he made his way back to his office. Everything was in place now — he would soon find out what Potter and Monroe were up to!

=ooo=

Harry was waiting for Monroe beneath his Invisibility Cloak near the Ministry's visitor entrance — a red telephone box on a little-traveled street that it shared with a pub, a few abandoned offices, and a nearby wall covered in graffiti. It had changed little in the time since Harry had first visited the Ministry, years earlier. He was under the Cloak in case someone emerged from the telephone box along with Monroe — like an Auror detail Disillusioned to follow him.

(In his office, Draco tapped one of his desk drawers, invoking a charm that unlocked the drawer for him alone. Reaching into the drawer, he took out a small cube and placed it on his desktop, then tapped the cube, linking it with the charm he had placed on Monroe minutes earlier. He would now be able to hear everything spoken by Monroe and anyone near him.)

Monroe stepped out of the phone box alone, looking around expectantly. "Harry?" he muttered softly.

"Here," Harry answered, softly, moving closer to Monroe. "Let's walk a bit — I want to be well away from this area before we talk."

(Draco smiled. So Potter was waiting for Monroe outside the Ministry! Things were working out exactly as he'd hoped.)

Monroe nodded and walked casually up the street to the first intersection, then turned west as he felt Harry's hand on his elbow, invisibly directing him to turn that way. He immediately recognized the direction. "Are we heading to —"

"Shhh," Harry shushed him. The invisible hand guided him again. "Just in here," Harry said, maneuvering Monroe into a small alley between two buildings. As they stepped into the shadows the Cloak suddenly covered Monroe and Harry took Monroe's hand, placing it on his arm. "Side-Along," he said shortly. The arm twisted away from Monroe, and he followed it —

The uncomfortable sensation of Apparition engulfed them for several moments, and they found themselves on another, familiar street, staring at a shabby door located between book and record shops on either side of it. Monroe had emerged from that door only hours earlier, evading Aurors who had arrived to take him into custody.

Monroe turned to Harry. "Are we going in?" he asked.

"In a bit," Harry said. "As soon as someone goes in or leaves — I don't want us to be seen together right now, not so soon after your charges were dropped. Malfoy didn't protest that nearly as much as I expected him to. I wonder why."

(Of course you do, Draco thought smugly. He could guess where Potter had taken them — he was heading toward Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes!)

Harry and Monroe waited near the entrance to the Leaky Cauldron for several minutes before they saw a familiar figure walking up Charing Cross Road toward them. Both men immediately recognized Dedalus Diggle, a regular patron of the Cauldron. This afternoon, however, Diggle's normally cheerful demeanor was absent, replaced with a sober expression from his recent misadventures with Ministry Aurors. A few pedestrians on the street did double takes at his robe, cloak and top hat, but they quickly lost interest as Diggle passed them. There were much stranger things to be seen on the streets of London these days. Looking neither right nor left, Diggle entered the Leaky Cauldron, with Harry and Monroe hard on his heels.

Harry pointed to the back of the shop and they wasted no time making their way into the courtyard where the entrance to Diagon Alley awaited them. Taking out his wand, Harry tapped the third up, second across from the lone dustbin standing against the wall, which began to shift and transform into the archway leading into Diagon Alley.

(Draco rubbed his hands together gleefully. Potter and Monroe were heading to the Weasley shop, he just knew it — they undoubtedly planned to resume whatever conversation they had started there just a few days earlier. This time, however, they would have one more person listening in than they expected!)

It was slow going under the Invisibility Cloak with two grown men beneath it, but Harry had insisted they stay Cloaked until reaching their destination. They moved along Diagon Alley, staying as far as possible from other visitors wandering, standing or window-shopping. It made for a meandering path, as people tended not to move aside for people they could not see.

Gringotts was in sight when Harry suddenly turned down a tiny byway some distance before and across from the Wizarding bank. They came to a halt, and Monroe looked around; nothing nearby looked familiar. "Why are we stopping here?" he asked, but Harry merely shook his head before slipping out from under the Cloak.

"I'll be back in a minute or two," he said, to apparently empty air. "Stay here until I come for you." Harry disappeared back into Diagon Alley proper.

(Draco smiled in anticipation. He's probably making sure the coast was clear at Weasleys' before they arrived there.)

Harry reappeared a few minutes later. "Our reservation is ready," he said. "I want you to stay under the Cloak, however. I'll tell the staff I expect you shortly, but that they should only disturb me when you arrive. That should give us enough time for us to discuss what I want to talk to you about. Come on."

Harry led the way through a an oaken door into a very nice dining establishment. "Potter, party of two for Mary's Room," he told the hostess. "The other member of my party has not arrived yet, but should be along shortly."

(Draco's smile faded. Mary's Room? He wondered anxiously if the Trace spell would work through the walls of that room. As far as he remembered, no one who'd been Traced had ever had a conversation in that room.)

The hostess escorted Harry (and the Cloaked Monroe) through the restaurant's main dining area to the room, where Mary, the owner herself, greeted Harry and bowed him into the room. Harry hesitated only a moment, which Monroe took as his cue and quietly slipped into the room ahead of him.

"When do you expect the other party, Mr. Potter?" Mary asked, respectfully.

"He's a busy man," Harry had said casually. "I hope he will make it within the hour. He said to go ahead and order for him, so we'll both have today's lunch special and ever-filling mugs of Merlin's Best Mead.

"Please bring the meals in when they're ready, but don't interrupt me otherwise until he arrives."

"May I ask who the other party is?" Mary inquired.

"Head Auror Draco Malfoy," Harry smiled.

(Draco's eyes widened in horror. That bastard!)

Mary bowed and left, shutting the door quietly behind her.

(How many people would hear, before the end of the day, that Harry Potter and Draco Malfoy were supposed to meet at Mary's Place, Draco wondered, quivering with fury. Potter had effectively undermined Draco's credibility in a lot of wizarding circles with that statement — fortunately not among many that mattered, but a lot of people would no longer mistrust Potter quite so much nor fear and respect the Head Auror as greatly as they did now, not if they thought there was some kind of collaboration between him and the Boy-Who-Lived.)

Harry gestured silently for Monroe to take the chair at the opposite end of the table. Harry then put a finger to his lips, motioning for Monroe to remain silent. He sat down in the chair nearest the door, took out his wand, and waved it at the door. The handle turned on its own and the door opened slightly. Harry then looked about the room as if he were quite alone. "I wonder if Draco will get here any time soon," he said, as if ruminating aloud. "He'll like today's special, I hope." Under the Cloak, Monroe was regarding him bemusedly. Was Harry speaking for Monroe's benefit?

(Bastard! Bastard! BASTARD! Malfoy thought furiously as he listened to Harry's taunting words. He knew something was going on with Monroe! Why else would he have gone to Mary's Place? On the other hand, the Trace was working through the enchantment on Mary's Room, which was good news for Malfoy — either Potter or Monroe might let something slip while they were talking, if they thought Mary's Room was secure from any kind of scyring.)

Monroe, waiting silently beneath the Cloak of Invisibility, pondered what Harry was up to. Why open the door slightly? Wasn't the point of Mary's Room to cut off all communication, mundane or magical, with the outside world? And why tell the staff here that Malfoy was his expected guest? Did Harry think Malfoy was somehow monitoring them? If he was monitoring them, Malfoy was now aware that they knew that!

Twenty minutes or so after they'd entered the room, a knock at the door announced a server arriving with two of the lunch specials. "Come," Harry said, and the server entered, staring back at the door as she did so.

"Sir, I apologize," she said as she set Harry's plate in front of him. "The door was apparently left open. I…" she trailed off, not certain what to say. Visitors to Mary's Room expected perfect privacy — the open door was a breach of that implied contract.

Harry looked back at the door as if the fact that it was open was news to him, but didn't appear upset by it. "It's alright," he told the server. "My guest hasn't shown up yet."

"Would you like me to keep your plates hot while you wait, sir?" the server asked, relieved that the customer was not making trouble about the open door.

"No, you can leave them both here," Harry said. The server nodded and placed the second plate in front of the empty chair at the opposite end. "If my guest arrives before I finish," Harry reminded her, "please show him in, but don't disturb me for anything else."

The server nodded, bowed, and retreated, closing the door carefully behind her. Harry waved his wand at the door again, and this time the inner bolt slid into black with a loud clack. Harry then spoke no less than twenty-seven charms, providing even more protection against scrying and other situations that would compromise their privacy, while Monroe waited silently for him to finish.

(Draco listened anxiously as Harry spoke the spells one by one. The Trace should be able to work through any charm, seeing as it was already within the protection established by Mary's Room and whatever wards Potter added. There was no known way for anyone to detect the Trace — you just had to know it was there. But until Harry finished with his wards, and Draco could still hear him, there was no knowing if he was going to be in on their conversation or not.)

Harry finished the twenty-seventh spell, but his wand kept moving in intricate patterns — once, twice, thrice, as he silently performed three final spells, then put away his wand. Looking toward the other end of the table, he explained. "In case you've never heard of Mary's Place, as well as being a very fine Wizarding restaurant, it also has this room, called Mary's Room, a place where people can go to have very private conversations. My wife and I use it from time to time — not so much because we need to have very private conversations as to have some 'alone time' for just the two of us."

"Nice," Monroe said, still beneath the Cloak. "But I assume this is not 'alone time' for me and you."

Harry chuckled, but only for a moment. "I have a more practical reason for being here. There's a longstanding rumor that the Ministry has a special surveillance spell it can place on wizards they want to eavesdrop on. The spell cannot be detected by any spell or device currently known, so we have no way to check for it. But I would bet a hundred Galleons that it's been placed on you."

Monroe took off the Invisibility Cloak. "That seems reasonable, especially since I was held in an interrogation room for a while before they released me. Malfoy showed up to question me before he got the news that the charges were dropped. He stayed behind me most of the time he was in the room. I suppose he could have put that spell on me then." Irritation was audible in his voice. "There has to be a way to get rid of it!"

"Probably not," Harry said. "A spell like that probably has a very complicated countercurse."

(It did, Malfoy thought, grinning once again. Their voices were still coming in loud and clear—confirmation that the Trace would work in Mary's Room, even with every spell Potter could throw at it!)

Harry touched his left index finger to his lips as his right hand silently drew his wand again. The wand traced a complicated pattern in the air in front of him as Harry completed a series of patterns. He then put the wand away again.

"That last spell I just cast was a Gibberspeak Charm — a spell similar to one I learned back at Hogwarts, one called Muffliato."

"I remember learning Muffliato sometime in second year," Monroe recalled. "But I've never heard of Gibberspeak."

"It's one of my own," Harry said. "I've kept it as secret as Malfoy thinks his Trace spell is. It can be cast on a group of people — it makes their speech unintelligible to anyone outside the group. If Malfoy can hear us now, he has no idea what we're saying."

("What the hell is going on?" Draco muttered to himself. "What are they saying?" He took out his wand again, casting several spells designed to detect and end cryptography spells. Nothing worked. Whatever spell Potter had just cast, Draco couldn't find a way to break or dispel it, at least not from this distance.)

"Assuming Malfoy can hear us," Monroe pointed out, "do you really still want to talk about whatever we came here to discuss, even if he can't understand us?"

"I don't know." Harry had a bemused look on his face. "On the one hand, it's funny that Malfoy is probably frantically trying to figure out what we're saying right now. I know my spell can be broken by brute force, but the person trying to break it has to be in my physical presence. He'll have to come here to do that, but if he shows up now everyone in Diagon Alley will know he was here to dine with me (because the staff here has undoubtedly heard by now whom I'm expecting); it will damage his reputation as a champion of the small businessman. A lot of shopkeepers think Draco is protecting them from me and my 'underhanded Muggle business practices.' If they think we're in cahoots he becomes just another Ministry Auror on the take."

"And on the other hand, as you pointed out, it's not very secure allowing him to hear anything we say that we might not want him to overhear," Harry continued, drumming his fingers absently on the table, pondering which way to go.

(Draco smacked the gibberish-emitting cube off his desk in frustration. He briefly considered sending Crabbe and Goyle to Mary's Place, to drag Potter and Monroe back down to Ministry HQ, but that would only tip Potter off that he was monitoring them somehow, and he didn't want that. He pointed his wand at the cube. "Accio cube," he muttered, and it flew into his hand. He dropped it into his special drawer and began considering his next move. Then he reached in the drawer and removed the cube, setting it on the desk before him again. Draco just couldn't not listen, even if he couldn't understand a thing they were saying.)

Monroe looked down at the food in front of him. "Do you mind if I eat while you make up your mind?" he asked. "I haven't had a bite since last night."

"I'll join you," Harry said, and they both tucked into the meals before them, eating in silence for several minutes. The special for the day was delicious, a meat and pasta dish that resembled chicken alfredo except that the meat wasn't chicken, the pasta wasn't fettuccini, and the sauce wasn't alfredo.

Monroe had almost finished off his repast when Harry looked up and asked, "Have you ever heard of a 'Source of Magic'?"

Monroe's last forkful of pasta stopped before entering his mouth. "A source of magic? Hmm, I guess I haven't. They never talked about that at Salem Institute. Where'd you hear of it?"

"It's something I worked out on my own," Harry said. "I wanted to talk to you about it, but I have to fill in some background."

"And Malfoy —?" Monroe queried.

"Draco actually helped me with some of this back then," Harry said, a small smile on his face at the memory. In fact, I'm not altogether sure he doesn't know about my thinking on the Source of Magic. But he's listening to gibberish right now, if he can hear anything at all, so I'm not worried about him overhearing this."

Monroe cocked his head at Harry. "That's a bit arrogant, isn't it?"

"Well I'm nothing if not arrogant," Harry laughed. "I'm trying to single-handedly bring about the Magical Singularity, aren't I? Do you want to hear this or not?"

Monroe swallowed his last mouthful of pasta. "Sure, why not?" he said around the mouthful. "We're already here, aren't we?"

"Right," Harry agreed, then paused to marshal his thoughts. "You know something about genetics, don't you?"

"Of course," Monroe nodded. "Most people do."

"Not most wizards, even today," Harry pointed out. "Most of them have never heard of DNA, have no idea what Mendelian genetics is, much less genomics and proteomics.

"So, back in 1991, shortly after I started at Hogwarts, I began to wonder why wizards had to perform spells with exactly the correct pronunciation and exactly the right wand gestures for them to work correctly. I even designed experiments that had test subjects say the spells with slightly different emphasis on the syllables than the right pronunciations, to see if it caused any difference."

"And it did, of course," Monroe said, smiling.

"Yeah," Harry sighed, remembering those tests with no small amount of chagrin. Hermione had teased him unmercifully after the month-long gamut of experiments he'd designed became moot after only one test session.

"So what did that have to do with the Source of Magic?" Monroe asked.

"I'll get to that," Harry replied. "After that fiasco, I had a chat with Draco Malfoy about blood."

"Blood…" Monroe repeated, thinking about how things had been, back at Hogwarts in 1991. The Slytherins had made things difficult throughout the year, bullying and harassing other students, especially Muggleborns and half-bloods. "There was some talk around that time about blood purity and how certain people, Muggles for example, and Muggleborn wizards were less pure than regular wizards."

"Malfoy, and of course his father, and quite a few Slytherins at the time, both at Hogwarts and across Wizarding Britain, subscribed to the notion of 'blood purity,'" Harry said. "I was working on trying to turn Draco from that type of thinking, so I set up a little experiment for us to run, one that I expected would render him incapable of becoming a Death Eater when he got old enough, and possibly to turn him from the Dark completely. The experiment was to determine why magic seemed to be fading in the world.

"We came up with some hypotheses about that," Harry went on. "Things like, 'Magic is fading away.' Draco hated that one, by the way. He thought it wouldn't be fair if everyone was losing magic, not just Muggleborns. His favorite theory was that wizards were interbreeding with Muggles, reducing blood purity. That was a major plank in Voldemort's campaign against Dumbledore, by the way.

"We also came up with some other hypotheses like, wizards weren't eating right, or Muggle technology was interfering with magic somehow. We even suggested that powerful wizards like Dumbledore or Voldemort weren't having children and so magic was decreasing by not being passed down."

"Some interesting ideas," Monroe noted. "It must have taken quite a while to work through all those experiments."

Harry scratched his head, looking a bit sheepish. "Well, actually, we only did one set of experiments, taking a little more than an hour, before we found enough data to confirm one of our hypotheses."

"And you were doing this just to trick Draco?" Monroe chuckled. "You must've gotten awfully lucky with that data!"

"I had a sneaking hunch it would go my way," Harry replied. "Being a wizard didn't seem to have anything to do with a complex of genes — it was more reasonable to assume that a single gene pair controlled the ability to do magic, since there are only Muggles, Squibs, and wizards, and Muggleborn wizards could be as powerful as pure-blood ones. There are only four possible choices with a single gene pair, and in half the cases you get a person carrying one wizard gene and one non-wizard gene.

"I sent Draco out to question the portraits in Hogwarts about families of wizards and how many wizards and Squibs were produced by those families. I talked to portraits too, but about spells that could be cast in the past but not today. As it turned out, that's when I found out about the Interdict of Merlin."

"Which may have been as big a blunder on Merlin's part as Einstein thought his cosmological constant was," noted Monroe, plaintively.

"It hasn't made things any easier for us," Harry agreed. "But I've thought about that a bit more, and I wonder if he did that to keep the balance between wizards and Muggles. If we had access to the same spells and potions that must've existed 800 years ago, with all that time for more progress, we wizards might be running the galaxy by now."

"Possibly," Monroe admitted. "Or wizards might have destroyed the earth by now."

Harry nodded, a sad look in his eyes. "I've thought of that, too. On the one hand, it seems a waste, but on the other, it may have kept us all alive until now. But then, Muggle technology has long had the capability of destroying the Earth as well."

"And yet we're still here." Monroe smiled. "Crazy Muggles."

Harry laughed, but for only a moment. "As I was saying," he went on, "Draco and I applied our test results to the hypotheses we'd come up with, and the one that looked most plausible was that we were losing information about magic spells because of the Interdict. Not because magic itself was going away, or because 'blood purity' was being diluted. It was a serious blow to Draco's worldview — he pretty much expected to become a Death Eater like his father. But once he knew the truth, knew that Voldemort's opposition to Dumbledore was predicated on a lie, he realized he could never become a real Death Eater. If he became one at all it would be only to keep up appearances. Ironically, he attributed this change in outlook to a Dark ritual he thought I tricked him into being a part of."

"That's what I'd expect from someone like him," Monroe said, his voice hard. "He seems like quite the opportunist. He must expect everyone else to be the same way."

"Well, I'm not going to be his apologist," Harry said, his voice firm. "But he had been indoctrinated his whole life with ideas of blood purity and the innate superiority of wizard-kind over the rest of humanity. Hell, one of his goals was to rape Luna Weasley when he got old enough! And he thought himself perfectly justified in doing so — not because he thought rape was okay, but because he thought himself and his family were above the law."

"And now that person is the head law enforcer in wizarding Britain," Monroe added, grimly. "Who the hell approved that promotion?"

Harry barked a short laugh. "Hermione did, actually," he said, "at my suggestion. 'Keep your friends close…'" he quoted, letting the rest trail off unsaid.

Monroe was silent for some time, looking thoughtful. Harry watched him for a time. Then, "What are you thinking about, James?"

Monroe shifted uncomfortably in his chair. "It's not that I'm ungrateful," he began, "But —" he looked at Harry with a very ambivalent expression. "When we first met, I don't think you wanted anything more from me than to learn where I'd heard your recognition code phrase. We obviously weren't friends then. But now—" Monroe gestured at the room they were in. "Now we're having dinner at Mary's Place, and you've told me you're trying to create a Magical Singularity, and I seem to be in your confidence now. So, I suppose I'm wondering…just…what the hell happened?"

Harry sat back and steepled his fingers, tapping them against his lips for some time before answering. "You're wondering when I began to —" Harry thought for a moment, "— trust you, I suppose." Monroe nodded.

"I haven't trusted anyone in a long time," Harry went on. "Not even Hermione, not completely, though I trust her more than anyone else on Earth."

Monroe thought about that, then asked, "What have I done, then, to earn your trust thus far?" He gave Harry an even look. "For my part, I haven't sought it out."

Harry returned his look. "I know. Perhaps that's in part how you've earned it. I haven't treated you that well these past few days."

"I've noticed that," Monroe answered, and both men chuckled.

Harry became thoughtful once again. "I suppose I was impressed with you," he told Monroe, "when you won our duel."

Monroe shook his head slightly. "I think that was mostly luck," he said, not looking in Harry's direction.

"Perhaps, but it was still impressive," Harry averred. "I've had dueling lessons from both Professor Flitwick and Professor Dumbledore. Both of them were formidable opponents, but I learned to hold my own against both of them.

"When you beat me, it made me realize that there are always other ways to solve a problem, other ways to see your way through to a solution."

Monroe chuckled. "And here I thought I was kicking your ass," he said, but it was obvious he wasn't serious. He fell silent, and the two men looked at each other for some time before Harry spoke again.

"I think we should get on with what I brought you here to talk about," Harry said. "The Source of Magic." Monroe leaned forward interestedly.

"So I had learned that there was only one thing that made you a wizard," Harry resumed. "A single allele that controlled whether you were a Muggle, a Squib, or a wizard. But that single allele, in and of itself, does not give you magical powers. Magic has to come from somewhere else."

Monroe was listening, fascinated, to what Harry was saying.

"If there was a combination of alleles," Harry continued, "a complex combination of alleles, it would be universal. Complex systems are always universal in a sexually reproducing species. They have to be, since each piece of the mechanism has to become nearly universal in a species before another variant of a gene can start to depend on that universality.

"If magic had been like that, a complex mechanism with many necessary genes and alleles, a wizard mating with a Muggle would only get about half of those genes, and half of the machine wouldn't be much good. And it would be very unlikely for a wizard, a Muggleborn, to be born to two half-wizards, to Squibs. What made you a wizard couldn't be very complicated, because we can see that people who weren't magical could produce magical children."

Harry leaned back, rubbing the sides of his face with his hands. He was getting closer to the culmination of his argument, and he wanted to be sure Monroe understood it clearly.

"But magic itself seems pretty complicated," Harry went on. "Look at how complicated the Fidelius Charm is just to cast, never mind the dynamics of how it operates! I had a spell cast on me once by Draco Malfoy, a torture curse that he thought might kill me. He magically locked me in a room afterwards, and I wasn't able to unlock the door or Transfigure the hinges to get out. I was barely able to escape."

Monroe raised an eyebrow at this. That could explain a lot of things about the way Harry talked about Malfoy, and why he was talking about these things even though Malfoy might be listening to them right now, Gibberish Charm or no.

Harry saw the look. "Right. Well, I won't get into the specifics of that right now, but he was pretty pissed off at me, and he thought I had planned the entire thing with the blood experiments to keep him from becoming a Death Eater and to distance him from his father."

"But you did do it for those reasons," Monroe pointed out. "You said so earlier."

"I did," Harry agreed. "I didn't think it would happen so fast, though. I needed more time to acclimate Draco to the idea of scientific thinking, to not being so disappointed when his pet theory turned out to be false. But I didn't get that chance.

"Anyway, I realized there are only two ways that complexity is created — through a non-purposeful process like natural selection, which has created butterflies and thinking humans, and through purposeful, creative intent — through some form of intelligent design."

"So you're thinking magic was designed?" Monroe put in, sounding dubious. "I don't know if I believe that's possible."

"Really?" Harry was surprised and a bit disappointed to hear that. He had thought Monroe would instantly agree with the idea. "I can't see how it couldn't have been, myself. Magic spells are complicated enough to do whatever we need them to do. We can modify spells, customize them to almost any degree we need to, if we work on them long enough. Or, at least until they get powerful enough to invoke the Interdict — that's our upper limit, and I believe that's what's saved us from the fate of Atlantis."

Both of Monroe's eyebrows rose at this. "Atlantis is just a legend," he objected. "No one has found the least indication of where it was located, nor any type of record dating to that time."

Harry's mouth set in a thin line, eerily reminiscent of a certain Hogwarts Deputy Headmistress. That was the major sticking point in his theory — no one had produced any concrete, empirical evidence that Atlantis really existed.

Otherwise it made perfect sense, though! "But you agree that the spells we use aren't complicated enough by themselves to build up the spell effects from scratch."

Monroe thought for a second. "Yeah, I agree. I've wondered about that myself."

"DNA is complicated enough, with three billion base pairs, to describe a human body," Harry argued. "Computer programs, taking up megabytes of memory, are complicated enough to create word processing and spreadsheet programs, and more complicated applications as well. So the words of a spell are more like a button on your keyboard than a blueprint for a spell. You push a button and the application performs a function using the programming it's comprised of."

Harry took out his wand and waved it at his plate, saying "Wingardium Leviosa." The plate floated in the air. "That's what I think the Source of Magic is," he said, as the plate slowly floated back onto the table. "It's some type of mechanism that reacts by levitating an object when someone with a specific genetic marker says 'Wingardium Leviosa' directed toward that object." He waited for Monroe's reply.

Monroe was silent for some time, resting his chin on his hand as he thought about what Harry had said, staring at Harry's plate now resting once again in front of him. At length he asked, in a flat tone, "How did you test all this, Harry?"

"One of the reasons I've been gathering ancient wizarding books," Harry replied, "is to look for references to Atlantis."

"Find anything?" In that same flat tone.

"Some," Harry answered immediately. "They identified several possible locations."

"Did you check them out?"

"Yes, as best I could," Harry said. "Mostly in the Atlantic Ocean, near the equator. There were also a few theories that Atlantis was in the Mediterranean Sea, and one that postulated it had been connected to India by an isthmus until about 10,000 B.C. I discounted the Indian legend, since Atlantis had to be isolated for the genetic marker that the Source of Magic looks for to be solely on that population."

"And what did you find in those locations you searched?" Monroe asked.

"Nothing," Harry admitted, reluctantly. "But not finding it so far doesn't mean it doesn't exist!"

"What do you suppose this 'Source of Magic' would be?" Monroe asked. "Like a Philosopher's Stone, but emitting magic rather than just transmuting base metal to gold, or turning water into Elixer Vitae?"

"Something like that," Harry agreed. "Or maybe it was found rather than designed, left on Atlantis by an even earlier civilization."

"That invites an infinite regression," Monroe objected. "You might as well say, 'God done it'."

Harry responded with annoyance in his voice. "Whatever. But until we locate where Atlantis was, we won't be able to do any testing on it, to determine its origin."

But Monroe shook his head. "I don't think that's true. I think we should do some tests to see if we can locate this supposed Source of Magic, assuming it exists."

=ooo=

Author's Note: A big thanks to EY (Less Wrong) for including a link to this fanfic at his site for Methods of Rationality, HPMOR dot NET. The chapters for that story have resumed once again and are very interesting to read!

Chapter 12: Busted!

Updated 5/4/2012

"You're going to tell me exactly what's going on with you and Mr. Monroe."

=ooo=

Harry smiled despite the expression on Hermione's face. "Hello, love. Fancy meeting you here…"

Hermione moved stiffly into the room, then pointed a finger commandingly at the door, which hurriedly slammed shut and engaged the bolt. "Don't give me that 'love' stuff, Harry. What's wrong with you? Are you trying to make things more difficult for me at the Ministry?"

"What's going on?" Harry asked, a look of wide-eyed innocence on his face. On the opposite side of the room, Monroe glanced around uncomfortably, afraid that whatever had happened, he was going to be dragged into it.

"You know bloody well what's going on," Hermione said, in a calm but angry tone. "You've got Malfoy up in arms at you again, and I suspect he'll be here any moment to try and pick up Mr. Monroe as some kind of retaliation."

"What for now?" Monroe blurted, unable to hold back.

Hermione looked at him. "There are apparently allegations that you may have some connection to the Dark Lord."

Harry laughed. "Hell, I accused him of that a few days ago at the Weasleys' shop! Malfoy's just using that as an excuse to harass Monroe!"

Hermione frowned momentarily at that. Had Malfoy somehow found out about that conversation? It didn't seem likely — the Weasleys warded their premises and homes more tightly than even Mary's Room was protected. Maybe he'd gotten a tip. She suddenly shrugged, remembering not to let Harry distract her.

"That doesn't matter," Hermione waved a hand dismissively. "He's got the legal right to follow up any leads he has dealing with Dark agents, including dead ones like Voldemort."

"Does he have the right to put Trace spells on wizards before such information comes to light?" Monroe asked. Both Hermione and Harry looked at him sharply.

"What does that mean?" Hermione asked.

"We think Malfoy put a trace spell on Monroe when he was being held at the Ministry earlier," Harry said shortly, not happy that Monroe had mentioned that in front of Hermione, who would likely press the issue with Malfoy if he showed up at Mary's Place. And thinking of that…

"We probably need to leave here anyway," Harry said. "They have to prepare this room for the next customer."

"No they don't," Hermione said. "I spoke to the owner when I first got here. I told her you were expecting me but that I'd been held up at work." Hermione crossed her arms over her chest. "She seemed to think you were expecting Draco Malfoy," she said, giving Harry a suspicious look. "I wonder why she would think that?"

"Because I told her that," Harry replied at once. "Malfoy doesn't want anyone in Diagon Alley thinking he and I are in cahoots — telling Mary that I was meeting Malfoy here make him look bad in front of all his 'fans' here."

"Yes," Hermione agreed. "And it also pissed him off, obviously, and he's decided to take it out on Monroe."

"He wouldn't even know Harry said that unless he had a trace spell on me," Monroe spoke up.

Hermione looked thoughtful for a moment. "What did he tell you before he sent you up to my office?"

"He said you'd granted me citizenship status retroactive to my entry in England five years ago, and that I was free to leave," Monroe answered.

Harry had a gleeful look on his face. "If he'd had any evidence that you were working for Voldemort," he said, grinning, "he'd have invoked it then!"

At that moment there was a pounding on the door. "Ministry Aurors!" a voice outside shouted; it sounded like Vincent Crabbe. "Open up or we'll break the door down!"

"Right on time," Harry smirked. He slid the bolt aside and opened the door. Outside were Crabbe, Goyle and behind them, Malfoy himself. "Why Draco," Harry said, feigning surprise. "What are you doing here?"

"As if you didn't know," Draco growled. He fluttered his hands at Crabbe and Goyle, waving them out of his way, then walked into the room.

"What d'you want us to do, Boss —" Crabbe asked, but the door slammed shut on them.

"Come here to warn your husband he might be implicated in a Dark conspiracy?" Draco spoke first to the Minister.

"Don't be ridiculous, Draco," Hermione replied, sounding offended. "I came here to find out what's provoked this latest round of feuding between the two of you, and what Mr. Monroe's got to do with it!"

"I already told you what we suspect," Draco answered smoothly. "That Mr. Monroe has some connection to the Dark Lord."

There were various reactions in the room to this statement. Monroe shook his head in disgust; Harry merely smiled thinly to himself.

It was Hermione, however, who responded first. "Yes, and you refused to divulge your sources or any other information about that suspicion, citing an 'ongoing investigation' into the matter. May I presume that you have learned nothing more concrete since earlier this afternoon?"

"It's still ongoing," Draco agreed. In point of fact, they had no such information on Monroe; it had been a ploy to get Monroe back into the Ministry after he and Harry had found a way to circumvent the Trace that Malfoy had put on Monroe while he was in their custody earlier today, so that he could overhear any conversations Monroe had with anyone. It was why he'd brought Crabbe and Goyle along — to take Monroe into custody so he could use Veritaserum on him and find out what he and Harry had discussed that Draco had been unable to understand.

And Hermione being here was just icing on the cake; if Monroe and Potter had been plotting anything the least bit underhanded, her presence here would make it seem like she was in on it as well, weakening her position in the eyes of the Wizengamot. Only the Chief Warlock would still be staunchly on her side, as he had always been, but even his support couldn't override Lord Malfoy's influence in the Most Ancient Hall of the wizards' court.

"So why didn't you hold him when he was at the Ministry earlier today?" Hermione asked sharply. "You told me afterward we released Monroe that some new information about Voldemort —" Draco frowned at her use of The Name "— had come to light. You said you wanted the chance to ask Monroe some questions — why didn't you tell me that while he was there, instead of waiting until after he'd been let go?"

"The information only came to light shortly after we released Monroe," Draco answered, his tone as smooth as it had been before.

"How did it come to you?" Hermione persisted. "From one of your Aurors? Was it anonymous?"

Draco saw the trap she was setting — if he said one of his Aurors had brought it to him she would demand he be questioned under Veritaserum, and there was no time for him to prepare someone for that. He couldn't say it was Crabbe or Goyle — as his "personal assistants" as well as Aurors anything they said would be suspect. "It was anonymous," he said immediately.

"So you are in the process of verifying that information?" Hermione asked, arching an eyebrow at him. Harry's smile got a fraction broader — he'd already figured out where she was going with these questions. She'd used the technique on him often enough. Fortunately, he'd always been prepared for it.

"Of course," Draco nodded, making his reply sound like that should have been obvious. But there was a cold shiver running down his spine — he knew what she'd say next —

"Then you don't yet have sufficient cause to bring him in for questioning," Hermione pointed out, exactly as he'd expected. Behind the veneer of his confident expression, Draco grimaced, silently damning the woman for these completely ludicrous reforms to their law enforcement system.

"I didn't want to give him the opportunity to escape," Draco replied, the only thing he could reasonably say at this point.

The Minister raised her hands, gesturing at the room they were in. "It doesn't look like he was running, Draco, if he's been having lunch here with Harry, as you told me."

"And I wonder how he knew that?" Monroe put in. "Since I entered this restaurant invisibly and Harry never mentioned he was having lunch with me."

Shit, Draco thought.

Hermione nodded knowingly. "Yes, I've been meaning to get to that. Draco, how did you know to tell me that Harry was having lunch with Mr. Monroe, earlier today?"

There was only one answer Draco could give. "I watched Monroe as he left through the visitor's entrance. He was speaking to someone though no one else was around. I suspected it was Harry since Monroe called his name."

"You weren't in the booth with him when Monroe left, were you?" Hermione asked. "Even if you were Disillusioned, I don't think Mr. Monroe would have failed to notice someone in there with him."

"There was no one in the booth with me," Monroe answered before Draco could say anything. "I checked around inside it while it was taking me up to the street — in case someone was in there with me."

Draco hadn't wanted to admit this, but — "There's a camera installed in the booth," he said. "I had them mounted in the Atrium and other key locations in the Ministry, including the visitor's booth, when I became Head Auror."

"And how is it I am not aware of that?" Hermione asked, archly. "I should have had to approve the cost of installing those cameras."

"I used my own gold," Draco said. "It was considered a personal expenditure — completely legal at the time." In fact, Draco had known that Hermione was working to change the policy on making personal modifications to one's office or business area — she wanted all modifications to go through the Ministry for approval, not just governmental upgrades, which were few and far between. Draco had the miniature magical cameras installed just before the policy changes went into effect. They had been his private eyes into the goings-on at the Ministry. He just wished he'd spent the extra gold and gotten the cameras with audio capability as well!

"You must've purchased those from the Weasleys," Harry said, enjoying himself very much. "Were they the kind with audio capability, or the cheaper models?"

Malfoy glared at Harry, then said reluctantly, "Non-audio."

"Then how could you have heard Monroe call Harry's name?" Hermione asked.

"I never said I heard him," Draco pointed out. "I saw his mouth move. I have a recording of him leaving the booth." Draco did not bother to point out that he'd only watched the video after the fact, that he had heard Monroe say Harry's name by other means, means he had no desire to divulge.

"And when did I say Harry and I were going to Mary's Place?" Monroe asked, accusingly. "The Minister said a minute ago that you told her that's where Harry and I were."

"It was a lucky guess on my part," Draco said. "It's the most secure place in Diagon Alley if you want to discuss something without being overheard."

"But not the most secure place in London, as you know," Harry put in. "That would be my offices and private residence at the TBC Building. That's where you should have expected me to go, if I didn't really want you to overhear anything between me and Monroe."

"That's a good point," Hermione said, turning to Draco. "So how did you know Harry and Monroe were here?"

"Because he —" Monroe began, but both Hermione and Harry put up their hands, stopping him from speaking further.

"Well, Draco?" Hermione prompted, when Malfoy didn't reply. "Do I have to have Crabbe and Goyle put under Veritaserum before you'll admit you put a trace program on Mr. Monroe?"

Inwardly, Draco was furious, but mostly with himself — he'd had to mention to Granger that her husband was meeting with Monroe, he couldn't resist rubbing that in her face; that, and the bit about Monroe's supposed connection with the Dark Lord, a connection he had not a shred of evidence to support. "I thought it would be a good contingency plan," he finally said. "In case Monroe tried to leave town."

"Why would I do that?" Monroe asked, in a tone of incredulity. "I've just been pardoned for being in Britain illegally, even though I had no idea I was until a few days ago!"

"I'll overlook what you've done, Draco," Hermione told him. "If you remove the trace immediately and promise you won't use it again without executive approval."

"And if I refuse?" Draco asked, stiffly, wondering to himself if his father could swing the votes in the Wizengamot to have him exonerated — and if his father would even try. Lucius Malfoy did not value failure these days, not even a relatively minor failure by his only son and heir to his title.

"Then I will bring up the matter to the Chief Warlock," Hermione said, in an icy tone. He may move to have House Malfoy shunned by the other Ancient Houses."

Malfoy stared at her in disbelief. "You would not dare!" he said, though his voice could barely manage more than a whisper, so shocked was he by this move on her part. "House Malfoy is one of the most Ancient and Noble Houses in Wizarding Britain!"

"All the more important that you should comport yourself as Head Auror with more regard for the law," Hermione replied, her tone still icy. "If the Wizengamot should learn that you have such a spell in your possession, they may begin to wonder whether it could ever be used on them."

No one spoke for what seemed like a long time. Finally, Draco reached inside his robe and drew out his wand. "Does everyone here agree that no mention will be made of the trace spell to anyone outside this room?"

"Yes," Harry and Hermione both said, then looked at Monroe.

Monroe sighed. "Yes," he said as well.

"Very well," Draco nodded and pointed his wand at Monroe, making a complex series of wand motions as he muttered the cancellation spell under his breath. "I presume you trust that I've removed it," he said as his wand disappeared back into his robe. "Given that there is no known detection spell that can find it, anyway."

"I'm working on it," Harry said, cheerfully, earning a sharp look from both Draco and Hermione, for different reasons. He stepped over to the door. "And now, Draco, have a pleasant day," he said, opening it and gesturing for Malfoy to leave.

Without a word Draco turned and walked out through the door. "What now, Boss?" they heard Crabbe ask as Harry began to shut the door.

"Shut it," Draco replied, his voice a low snarl. "Let's get back —" then the door closed and any voices from the outside were cut off.

"Well, that's that," Harry said, looking back at Hermione and Monroe. "I guess we can be going as well —"

"Hold on, buster," Hermione stopped him. "You're not getting off that easy this time. You're going to tell me exactly what's going on with you and Mr. Monroe."

=ooo=

Draco Malfoy strode from Mary's Place and toward the exit of Diagon Alley in a black rage, though his outward expression remained impassive. He had dearly wanted to escort someone back to the Ministry to show the merchants and customers here that he was working for their benefit, taking care of their needs.

Instead, it was only him and two Aurors who made their way back to the Leaky Cauldron, empty-handed and barely having avoided public disgrace. But no one here could know that, of course, so Draco nodded, with a thin but cordial smile, to the shopkeepers and vendors who hailed or waved at him, even as his two bodyguards waved away anyone who moved to greet him. Crabbe and Goyle were a step behind him, maintaining silence as he'd ordered.

The Leaky Cauldron went dead silent as they entered from the courtyard, and Draco felt the pressure of many eyes upon him as he passed through the inn without a word. Even before they reached the front door, the whispers began. At the door Draco stopped, looking back at them; the whispers immediately stopped. He turned and opened the door then strode out into the street.

Once outside on Charing Cross Road, he and his men vanished, reappearing perhaps a quarter-mile distant at his private entrance to the Ministry, a fish and chip shop, long abandoned. Draco had arranged this entrance when he had become Head Auror; only he, Crabbe and Goyle were aware of its existence.

The door was locked and bolted, but at the touch of his hand the bolt slid aside and the door swung open for him. They passed inside, through the long-unused shop and into a narrow hallway leading to two doors, one marked BLOKES and the other BINTS. Draco had seen restrooms signed like this in some Muggle restaurant years ago and thought they were funny.

Crabbe and Goyle followed Draco through the BLOKES door, which led into a lavatory with three stalls in it. Each stall had a handle and a coin box which read, Please Deposit One Pound. Draco stepped in front of the first stall, Crabbe the next one, and Goyle the last. In unison they took out their wands and tapped the coin box in front of them, each of which made a clack as the doors swung inward. Inside each stall was a capped flange and no toilet. Ignoring this, Draco stepped toward the tile wall, passing through it just as one did through the barrier between Kings Cross Station and Platform 9¾.

On the other side of the wall was a comfortable room, brightly lighted by a glowing ceiling and furnished with a leather recliner, a table with a tea set and several boxes of Earl Grey tea, and across the room, a stone fireplace with a finely carved mahogany mantle.

Draco was tempted to send Crabbe and Goyle on ahead, and spend a while in this room, his "quiet room," brooding, but he could do that just as well in his office. He took a pinch of Floo powder from a bowl on the mantle, tossed it into the hearth, which burst into green flames, then said, "Ministry of Magic!" and stepped into the flames.

A few moments later he stepped out of a fireplace in the Atrium, turned, and strode toward the golden elevators; Crabbe and Goyle appeared behind him, from the flames and were hard on his heels. The lift stopped at level two and the three men got off, walking down the short hallway to where the main offices of the Auror Department were located. Draco walked to his office, Crabbe and Goyle still at his heels; they probably expected to follow him into his office where he would reprimand them for letting the Potter/Monroe situation get out of control.

Instead, Draco merely said, "Go write your reports for today. I'll see you tomorrow morning."

The two men looked at one another, hiding their expressions of relief, then turned and left. Draco entered his office, tapped the doorknob with his wand to lock it, and sat down at his desk to brood over the day's events and begin plotting for tomorrow.

Reaming out Crabbe and Goyle might have made him feel better momentarily, but if there was anyone to blame for this debacle it was him, not them. He was being too reactive, not thinking far enough ahead in this private little war with Harry Potter. In truth, it was more than a game than a real war; somehow a war with Harry had never seemed like a good idea to Draco. However his father, Lord Malfoy, took the conflict with Harry seriously, and had done so ever since he'd learned that Harry had been trying to bring Draco over to the Light side. But Draco had been playing that game with Harry, not his father — he'd wanted the chance to win it himself, and get Harry to embrace his Darkness! But Father had explained again about Dumbledore's ways, and what he'd done to his mother and Father's wife, and Draco had tearfully agreed, all those years ago, not to engage Harry in future plots or manipulations without apprising him of his plans. Draco would not have been allowed to return to Hogwarts otherwise.

But that was many years ago, when he was a child and didn't know any better. Today his father let him fight his own battles; in fact, he insisted on it, for how else would Draco earn the title he would inherit one day: Draco, Lord Malfoy of the Most Ancient and Noble House.

At that moment Draco's eye fell on a parchment envelope that was lying out of place on his desk. He had been so distracted when he sat down that he hadn't noticed it.

Draco picked up the envelope. It was addressed to "Head Auror Malfoy" in a vaguely familiar handwriting, something Draco felt like he'd seen before. There was no wax seal on the back, but the flap refused to budge when he tried to open it — there must be a Sticking Charm on it. He pointed his wand at it and muttered, "Finite Incantatem," but even that didn't break the charm. After a couple more tries Draco gave up and used a Severing Charm on the side of the envelope. The letter inside was written in the same familiar script, in very straight, ordered lines on the parchment. Draco read,

To Head Auror Malfoy,

I and other like-minded folks in Wizarding Britain applaud your efforts to keep Diagon Alley a place where witches and wizards are free to shop and to ply their trades without unnecessary taxation and manipulation by greedy Muggle-loving capitalists like Harry Potter.

We have come too far in the Wizarding World to allow anyone to exert their monetary influence over us, and at the same time put us at such risk with the possibility of the return of You-Know-Who.

There have been rumors circulating throughout Diagon Alley and other places where wizards gather that Harry Potter has been talking to a wizard who was posing as a Muggle for several years before making his true presence known in our community. It is also believed that this wizard may be controlled somehow by the Dark Lord, even though he is supposed to be long-dead.

We urge you to take these rumors seriously – no one wants a return to the conflicts and terror of the 1970's,when You-Know-Who ravened about the Wizarding World, terrorizing and murdering any who stood against him. Even if You-Know-Who is truly dead, it would not stop an enterprising wizard from creating circumstances that would make it seem like he was alive.

Sincerely yours,

A concerned citizen

Draco stared at this letter for several minutes, both at the content and the writing itself. Who would write him such a letter? The writing was too regular to be normal handwriting; thus, it was probably done with a Quotes Quill. The comments about Diagon Alley led him to believe it was someone there who knew of his efforts to neutralize Harry Potter's influence there, and seemed to approve of it.

The other aspect of the letter — the references to the Dark Lord — were more interesting. The prospect of the Dark Lord returning now was unsettling, but so was the idea that Potter might fake his return in order to regain the power he once held over the Wizarding World. Assuming that the Dark Lord was dead for once and all, it would be a brilliant stroke to fake his return!

Taking out his wand, Draco tapped a box sitting on the corner of his desk. "Where did this letter on my desk come from?" he asked without preamble.

"It was a standard owl-post delivery, sir," his executive assistant responded a moment later. "I logged it in at…10:32 this morning. The owl was from the Diagon Alley Owl Office."

"Okay," Draco said, and tapped the box again, severing the connection. It was a handy little device, that box, something his assistant had presented him with shortly after she'd gone to work for him. She had pointed out that it would save time with her not having to constantly come in his office when he called for her. The news had spread and soon all the department heads and undersecretaries had them on their desks as well, replacing most of the parchment airplanes that had been in use for many years before. Draco had to admit they were handy little devices, especially since you could also connect them to any other box, not just the boxes they were keyed to by default.

It had galled him, though, that all of these boxes had come from Weasleys' Wireless Wonderland, spinning money for those, those — people, Draco thought savagely. He stared at the box broodingly, contemplating whether he'd feel better if he blasted it with his wand.

But, no — he'd just have to buy another one, filling the Weasley coffers even more, which was not a part of his plans for today. He picked up the letter again, contemplating how he might figure out who —

Draco stopped, staring at the writing on the letter. That writing was familiar to him! He spun around, reaching toward a book on the bookshelves behind his desk. The book was thin but well-bound, with the words Quotes Quills Samples along the side. Opening it toward the end of the book, Draco began comparing the writing samples in the book to the writing on the letter.

"Let's see," Draco muttered as he scanned the writings in the book. "Quote Quill, Fred Weasley, purchased 10 April 2012…no. Fred Weasley, purchased 27 August 2014, no. George Weasley, purchased 30 September 2009, hmm, no. Ron Weasley, purchased 15 April 2013 — aha! Got you!"

It was not an exact match, but it was very close, Draco decided. The Ministry kept track of Quote Quills, which were routinely used to write otherwise anonymous letters. Of course, this did not mean that Ron Weasley himself used the Quote Quill that wrote this letter, but it seemed fairly certain that he had enchanted the quill that did.

But added with the other clues in the letter, Draco suspected the youngest Weasley son had written the letter and sent it off to the Ministry using the Diagon Alley post office. Why he might have done so, and the reasons he might have to implicate Harry Potter in a plot to have You-Know-Who return, whether the Dark Lord was truly resurrected or resurrected in name only, was something Draco intended to find out.

=ooo=

After Malfoy left the room with his goon squad, Hermione produced her wand, waved the bolt shut, then spoke an even dozen wards — several of her own creation and more than enough to ensure that no one outside the room would be privy to anything that went on in the room.

"There," she said with grim satisfaction. "Now, Harry — you've been acting quite strangely since your birthday this Monday past — that is, more strangely than usual," she added, as Harry gave her a wry grin. "And I want to know why. Now."

"Aren't you hungry?" Harry remarked casually, sitting down at the table. "I thought you might at least want to order something before you locked us away in here."

"The server will take our orders at six p.m., which is in —" Hermione glanced at her watch "— forty-eight minutes. That should be enough time for you to explain what you and Mr. Monroe have been up to this week."

"Nothing much, really," Harry said, though he did not — quite — meet her eyes as he said it. "We've just been kicking around a few ideas over the past day or two."

"Before Draco showed up you said you'd accused Mr. Monroe of being Voldemort," Hermione reminded him, sounding severe. "Is that one of the ideas you've been 'kicking around'?"

Harry waved a hand airily. "That was just a momentary glitch, before I realized that James knows quite a bit about magic — and well, he'd beat me at a duel…"

"He did?" Hermione's eyes widened in surprise; she looked at Monroe in wonderment. "That must've been something to see! The great Harry Potter-Evans-Verres-Granger defeated in a duel!" She smiled wickedly.

"I got in a lucky shot," Monroe offered. "It was not that big a deal."

"That's what I thought," Harry muttered plaintively.

Hermione's expression had become stern again. "But that doesn't tell me what you're doing now," she reminded him. "Here you are, locked away in one of the most magically secure places in Britain, with the Head Auror breathing down your necks — you can see where I might think you're doing more here than discussing the latest issue of Duellists Quarterly."

"Well," Harry murmured, "fair enough. If you must know, love, Monroe and I have been talking about…the Singularity."

"Oh." Hermione rolled her eyes expressively. "That." She put her hand over her face, shaking her head in exasperation. "Harry, you and I covered this in detail a long time ago. Such a thing is never going to happen."

"Actually," Monroe interrupted. "It's nearly inevitable, with progress occurring at an exponential rate."

"Harry tried to tell me that, too," Hermione replied, folding her arms. "But then we researched how often new spells were being created over the past few centuries, and the progression is linear — in fact, it almost looked logarithmic, like it was slowly leveling off."

Monroe frowned at them. "But Muggle progress is occurring exponentially! Magic should show the same trend, even if it's slower."

"The Interdict of Merlin," Harry muttered. "That's what's causing the rate of progress to slow down."

"But wizards are creating new spells, Harry!" Hermione objected. "The Interdict only keeps spells above a certain level of power from being understood by anyone other than the inventor of a new spell — it doesn't limit the creation of powerful spells!"

"Yes," Harry agreed, reluctantly. "But once a spell is lost to the Interdict, it can't be reinvented by anyone — that is what's causing the amount of magical knowledge gained in the world per unit of time to slowly move towards zero."

"But not to actually reach zero," Hermione pointed out. "That's what you're trying to imply."

"No, I'm not!" Harry insisted. "What I'm trying to make you understand is that unless we do something about the Interdict, that eventually Muggle technology, progressing exponentially, will outstrip magic and that if a Singularity occurs, it will be technological rather than magical!"

"But that assumes that Muggle technology is progressing exponentially now," Hermione argued, glancing at Monroe. "Has anyone proved that's really the case?"

"Yes," Monroe nodded. "Ray Kurzweil proved it over a decade ago in a book he wrote called The Singularity is Near. His theory on the idea, called the 'Law of Accelerating Returns,' was built on the works of earlier scientists who perceived that progress would eventually lead mankind to become post-industrial, post-scarcity, and deathless."

"Deathless?" Hermione looked faintly worried at that. "Isn't that what Voldemort wanted primarily for himself?"

"It is," Harry admitted. "But the difference is that the Singularity — whether we're talking technological or magical — is to free people from the limitations of aging, illness, and death. Nobody really wants to die."

Hermione was shaking her head. "I've known people who've wanted to die, Harry — not because they were sick of living, but because they wanted to experience what happens beyond the physical world."

"Nothing happens beyond the physical world," Harry said, deliberately lowering his voice to avoid sounding angry at his wife. "Dumbledore believed there was an afterlife, and thought that anyone who didn't want to experience it was a borderline Dark personality, but I think he was just rationalizing what happened to his family back when he was in school. There is no evidence that a soul exists."

"None that you accept, anyway," Hermione said, archly. "That doesn't make you right."

"It doesn't make me wrong, either," Harry argued. "But any way you look at it, reasonable evidence suggests that souls do not exist."

"Then what about —" Hermione cut herself off suddenly, glancing toward Monroe. "Well, about you-know-what."

"Monroe knows about Horcruxes," Harry told her. "And I haven't studied them enough to determine whether they hold a fragment of your soul or what. What I think is, they hold a copy of your brain patterns, a copy that can still think and somehow act on the external world."

"Sounds like you don't have any real evidence to back that up," Hermione said, sounding smug. "Or would you like to present some now?"

Harry said nothing, and merely shook his head. "Didn't think so," Hermione sniffed.

What Hermione didn't know, and what Harry would never tell her, was the information he did have on Horcruxes, information he'd taken from Quirrell-Voldemort's mind before he died. Voldemort's return in his own physical body had been precluded by the actions of men like Severus Snape and Alastor Moody, who had made sure that none of his remains could be used to perform the ritual that would have restored him to full vigor.

But no such precautions had been made for Quirrell's body — when he was destroyed the first time it was discovered that his parent's graves were no longer in the cemetery where they'd been interred, and the substantial efforts undertaken by Order of the Phoenix members to find them had availed for naught. It had taken six long years for "Quirrellmort" to return from death, just as Harry and Dumbledore had found and destroyed the last of the Horcruxes he'd created.

Then Dumbledore had died fighting the resurrected Quirrell, hoping to weaken him enough for Harry to defeat him, and after the Headmaster had fallen Harry had indeed taken up the battle, fighting Quirrell for most of a day before the former Defense professor fell to the Elder Wand, the wand that Harry had won from Dumbledore without knowing its true nature.

But no one other than Harry, Dumbledore, and the man who had become the Chief Warlock after the Headmaster's death knew the truth about Quirrell. And no one ever could; at least not until Harry could find a way to break the Interdict's stranglehold on progress in Magical Britain.

"Then maybe," Harry said, quietly, "we should find out, once and for all, whether souls exist or not."

Chapter 13: Do Souls Exist?

Updated 5/19/2012
Last Updated 1/25/2013

=ooo=

"Harry!" Hermione shook her head disbelievingly. "You can't prove something like that true!"

"Really?" Now it was Harry's turn to fold his arms skeptically. "Why not?"

"Because —" his wife paused to consider how she should approach the claim. "Because it's — well, it's…metaphysical. There is no way to measure or quantify a soul."

"But Dark wizards supposedly trap a portion of their soul inside an object, creating a Horcrux," Harry replied. "How do they know if they've succeeded?"

"Because the Horcrux becomes nearly indestructible," Hermione answered. "The only way to destroy one is with basilisk venom or Fiendfyre."

"There is also a rumor that steeping a Horcrux in the blood of a unicorn will destroy it," Monroe added. "But no one has ever tried to prove that — wizards are normally afraid that killing a unicorn will bring a curse down upon them for the rest of their life, which won't be long because they've slain something so pure and good."

"That doesn't prove there's a bit of soul in there," Harry pointed out. "Only that the ritual that creates it makes it very hard to break the spell."

"In any event," Hermione turned back to Harry, "you don't have access to a Horcrux, or any real information about them — the books that contained the ritual for creating one were stolen or removed from Hogwarts long ago, and the only person we know who knew it — Voldemort — is dead. Unless you can think up a way to measure a soul somehow you're at a dead end before you even start!"

"It is a problem," Monroe agreed. "But I'm with Harry on this — I don't believe souls exist."

Hermione gave him an even look. "I never said I did. But I don't know how to go about either proving or disproving their existence, Mr. Monroe."

Harry had leaned forward, resting his elbows on the table with his head leaning against his hands. "Substrate independence," he said.

"What?" Hermione looked confused. But the other wizard in the room was nodding at Harry's words.

"Yes, I think I see where you're going," Monroe said. "Like a ghost being an accidental impression of the mind of a wizard, left behind after his or her death. Like the Portrait Ritual, which infuses the painting of a person with some of his or her memories and intelligence. Like the Sorting Hat being able to talk directly into your brain while you're wearing it, and being able to talk aloud even when nobody's wearing it!"

"But that's not the same thing!" Hermione objected. "We don't know how the Sorting Hat was created, but there are many spells and rituals that instill a semblance of intelligence in otherwise inanimate objects. And we know that wizards who have an unhealthy fear of death sometimes remain behind as ghosts when they die, especially if their death was abrupt or unnatural. But a ghost isn't a person's soul!"

"How do you know?" Harry asked, tonelessly.

"Because —" Hermione hesitated. "Because… it's not…fully self-aware. A person's soul would have all of their memories and personality."

"Dumbledore once told me that ghosts are not supposed to be here," Harry remembered. "They are supposed to move on, he said. He also made reference to the Veil in the Department of Mysteries and to the long-lost Resurrection Stone, one of the three Deathly Hallows."

"Dumbledore evidently believed in souls," Monroe said. "But I remember reading up on ghosts, and the literature is quick to point out that only wizards can become ghosts, not Muggles. That seems to leave a hole in his soul theory."

"Yes," Hermione agreed. "I've read that, too. But that only means that Muggles don't release a burst of magic when they die, and so cannot create a ghostly afterimage of themselves."

"You know," Harry remarked, leaning back in his chair and rubbing his stomach. "I'm starting to get hungry again."

"What?" Hermione looked sharply at her husband. "Don't try to distract us from the conversation, Harry! I thought you wanted to talk about this!"

"I do," Harry nodded. "But some Diracawl would be nice while we talked." He glanced at his watch. "It's just a few minutes before six."

"Do you want to wait until after we get something to eat before we continue this conversation?" Hermione shot a look of incredulity toward Monroe, who didn't react, then turned back to Harry. "Fine, then let's just sit here saying nothing until then!"

"Fine with me," Harry nodded. "I need to think a bit anyway."

=ooo=

Ginny took her drink, thanked the bargirl, and walked outside to one of the few tables the small café had along its storefront. She was still nursing the anger that had built up inside her from the argument she'd had with Dean earlier that day, and being outside might help it dissipate.

It was unlikely anyone would recognize her here, even in Diagon Alley and despite her tell-tale red hair, almost a dead giveaway for a Weasley in this wizarding community. The bargirl had been pleasant but didn't seem to recognize her as she was pouring her glass of Ogden's Old Firewhiskey. This café, known only as Darla's, was on a cul-de-sac well off of Diagon Alley proper, and was the last shop in the row; passers-by were few and far between. That was well, because Ginny needed to think.

She and Dean were arguing more and more lately. Her mother had suggested that was normal for young couples, that she and Dad had argued a lot when they were younger, before he'd learned his place in their household, Mum had added with a chuckle. Fred and George had shrugged it off, airily as usual, and their wives had told her separately that they tried to understand their husbands and the pressure they were under to do well, to be successful in Diagon Alley as their older brothers were in their jobs, Bill Weasley running Ollivanders, the premier wand shop in Diagon Alley and Charlie at the Ministry of Magic, Head of the Department of International Magical Cooperation. And Percy… Ginny drained her glass of firewhiskey then watched as it slowly refilled. She'd ordered three shots, so the glass would refill once more after this.

Harry and Hermione, Ginny had to admit, seemed like a perfect couple, even accounting for some of the things she'd witnessed over the years. Harry was not a typical wizarding husband; he did not expect his wife to be at his beck and call, like many wizards did, even in this day and age. He had never disapproved of Hermione working outside the home. Indeed, he seemed to support Hermione in whatever she did! Ginny wondered how much Hermione appreciated that fact. Not very much, she suspected, not as much as Ginny would.

"Oi, sis, what are you doing here?" Ginny looked up, surprised to see her brother Ron standing beside her. Normally she was more aware of her surroundings than this! "I didn't think you even knew this place existed," Ron said, sitting down at her table.

"I didn't until fifteen minutes ago," Ginny said, not sure whether she was happy to see Ron or not. Of all her brothers, he was the most understanding of her and her situation with Dean. They had talked about her marriage many times and Ron had always given her good advice.

Ron's one blind spot in their relationship, however, was his abiding dislike for Harry Potter. They had first met, Ron told her, on Platform 9¾ on their first trip to Hogwarts, when Mum had helped Harry avoid some kind of argument with his parents by telling him how to get through the barrier to the Platform. He'd gone up to Harry on the other side and tried to make conversation with him, but Harry had been — well, very weird, according to Ron. He didn't even want to be called Harry Potter, Ron had said; he'd put on a winter scarf even though it was a perfectly pleasant day, and then didn't want anyone to know who he was! He insisted on being called names like Goop or something silly like that.

And he hadn't liked Quidditch, Ron had hastened to point out. A wizard that didn't like Quidditch! Unbelievable! He even talked about changing the rules! But even that hadn't been enough to deter Ron from trying to be his friend. He remembered, he'd reminded Ginny, just how much she'd talked about him when Mum had told them that Harry Potter would be just about Ron's age, born a few months after he was. Ron figured, he said, he would sit with Harry on the Hogwarts Express, get to know him, try to get him to Sort into Gryffindor, the best House at Hogwarts, and he though Harry would come round to Quidditch after he'd seen it played a few times during the first year.

But then Draco Malfoy showed up. Everybody knew who the Malfoys were — Lucius Malfoy, or Lord Malfoy as he preferred in meetings of the Wizengamot, was hell-bent on becoming the de facto ruler of Wizarding Britain now that You-Know-Who was gone. And Draco was certainly his father's son, Ron had said, darkly — he'd wasted no time in bringing up Percy's rat in front of Harry, and suggested Ron tell him the story. And almost surprisingly, Harry had agreed with Ron, and told Malfoy he didn't have to tell the story if he didn't want to, and asked Malfoy to drop it. And Ron had really thought, he'd said, that he might still be Harry's friend if only Malfoy would go away, and he suggested that Harry tell him to do just that.

But then Harry Potter had said that Malfoy was welcome to talk to him if he wanted to! And that had done it for Ron, he'd walked away and written off Harry Potter as some kind of suck-up and toady to powerful people like the Malfoys. Wrongly, as he later admitted, but Ron had never forgiven him for preferring Draco Malfoy over him. Among other things, Ron had muttered; Ginny knew exactly what he was talking about. Ron had nursed a crush on Hermione Granger for years, just as Ginny had nursed one on Harry, though neither of them would ever admit it.

"So what're you doing here?" Ron asked, eyeing the glass of firewhiskey in her hand. "Shouldn't you be home making dinner for your husband?" Said with a small ironic twist to his mouth — Ron knew how she felt about the whole witches should be loving and doting to their husbands thing.

"Shouldn't you be home making Luna's supper?" Ginny retorted, knocking back her second shot of firewhiskey. Luna was, of course, a perfectly loving and doting wife, but Ron at least had the good sense not to take her for granted. Ginny and Luna had been in the same year at Hogwarts, though Luna had been Ravenclaw and Ginny (naturally, like all the Weasleys) had been Gryffindor, but they'd become good friends. Ginny liked suggesting that Ron should do more for his wife than simply not take advantage of her the way Fred and George seemed to do with theirs, even though their wives were more vocal about being treated equally by their husbands.

"It's her night to make dinner," Ron replied. That was a little joke between him and Ginny; Luna made dinner almost every night, but a couple of times a week Ron would "make dinner" by taking them out to eat. They both chuckled, then Ron put on a more serious face.

"There was something I wanted to talk to you about," Ron said. "It's good I happened to run into you." He paused a moment, looking at her carefully. "It's about Harry."

"What about Harry?" Ginny asked warily. Whenever Ron had something to say about Harry it usually wasn't' good; there was no reason to think today would be any different.

"I think that he's really trying to bring back You-Know-Who," Ron said, rushing the words out in case they got caught in his throat.

Ginny frowned. "Why would he do that?" she asked. "He nearly killed Harry the last time they fought!"

"Because without You-Know-Who, Harry Potter isn't really all that much," Ron argued. "You were a grade behind him — you saw all the trouble he caused over the next six years at Hogwarts. He damn near ruined Quidditch during our second year with all those stupid rules he wanted to add, and our third year he got Professor Lupin sacked because he was a werewolf!"

"You've always hated werewolves, Ron," Ginny pointed out quietly.

"But Lupin was a great teacher!" Ron objected. "Look at where he's at now! Nobody would have thought —" He cut himself off abruptly. "Anyway," he went on more quietly. "I think something's got to be done about what Potter's trying to do."

"And what's that, do you think?" Ginny asked, her lips set in a thin line.

"The Ministry's got to be notified," Ron said at once. "I know you don't like it," he added, seeing her expression. "I know you work for the guy and everything." It didn't need to be said what he meant by everything. "But we can't go through another wizarding war! A lot of people died in the last one!"

"Malfoy knows you don't like Harry," Ginny pointed out. "He's knows you're going to be biased."

"So?" Ron shrugged. "Malfoy doesn't like him either, does he? I don't think he's going to care what I think so long as I bring him evidence."

"What kind of evidence do you have against Harry?" Ginny wanted to know.

"For one thing, all those books Fred and George have been finding for him all these years," Ron answered. Collecting Interdicted spell books was mildly illegal; the Ministry didn't want any spell experiments involving Interdicted spells going on outside Department of Mysteries supervision.

"So you're going to turn in your own brothers to get at Harry?" Ginny demanded accusingly.

"Malfoy doesn't have to know where the books came from," Ron declared. "Only that Harry has them!"

"It's not a good idea to cross wits with Malfoy, Ron," Ginny warned. "You're not playing at Battle Magic games in school anymore."

"I know what I'm doing," Ron said, with a touch of petulance. "I was one of Hermione's Captains, you know."

"Who got outsmarted by Neville Longbottom," Ginny reminded him. Ron grimaced. That had been his biggest sore spot during the entire first year of Battle Magic.

"He didn't fight fair," Ron complained, a sullen look on his face.

"Neither did Harry Potter, from what you've said," Ginny said. "And neither will Malfoy, if you try to use him against Harry. Malfoy is going to be suspicious of any Weasley that tries to give him information against Harry Potter — he's suspect it's a trick. And if things don't work out the way you expect them to, he's going to put the blame on you."

"Malfoy won't do anything to me," Ron scoffed. "He wants everyone in Diagon Alley to think he's everybody's protector, keeping them safe from evil Harry Potter and his lackeys, the Gringotts goblins — he's got most of the shopkeepers believing he's a slumlord planning to kick them out of their shops for the least excuse."

"And you know better than that," Ginny said, scowling at her brother. "You don't have any evidence that Harry's trying to bring back the Dark Lord, do you?"

"Only what he told us a few days ago!" Ron snapped. "He practically admitted Quirrell may have had something to do with that Monroe showing up at Harry's building!"

"But that was before we found out that Monroe was a wizard!" Ginny snapped right back. "And that he has memories of being at Hogwarts!"

"But those could have been faked!" Ron objected. "Did Harry ever check for that possibility?"

"I don't know," Ginny shook her head. "But even so, Ron, you can't go to Malfoy with flimsy evidence like that!" She stood suddenly. "Look, you're going to do what you want — I know better than to tell you not to, because you're as stubborn as Fred and George are when you think you're right. But just be careful what you say to Malfoy — he's probably more obsessed about Harry than even you are."

Ron doubted that, but said nothing. Ginny wasn't going to believe anything he said about Harry until he got proof that Harry was plotting something involving Monroe, or maybe even Quirrell somehow.

"I'm going home," Ginny announced. "You should do the same, Ron — your wife's waiting for you, I'm sure. I'll — talk to you later." They looked at each other a long moment, both wondering what the other would do now that they'd had this conversation, then Ginny spun on her heel and walked away.

Ron watched her walk up the byway until she turned into the main street and out of sight. Their argument had only strengthened his resolved to expose Harry any way he could. He picked up her last drink and gulped it down, then set the empty glass back on the table and walked away as well, to go home and make his own plans for Harry Potter's downfall.

=ooo=

The aroma of fried Diracawl wafted through Mary's Room, mixing with the smell of Roopo balls, which Harry had suggested to Monroe, and Hermione's Dirigible Plum salad. The server had arrived only a minute ago with a tray bearing all three meals, placing each plate silently and accurately before the person who had ordered it, then quickly bowed and departed, pulling the door closed.

Harry leaned forward and inhaled slowly, savoring the smell of his fried Diracawl meat, mashed potatoes and gravy, and green beans. "Mmm, that smells good."

Monroe had already tasted a Roopo ball. "You were right," he nodded toward Harry. "These are delicious!"

Harry nodded back, his mouth now full of mashed potatoes and gravy. He took a sip of his drink, a mug of Merlin's Best Mead, and said, "It's been a while since I've had any, but I remember the first time I tried some, I was here with —" he cut himself off, then continued "— a friend, and he ordered them for me."

Hermione, who had said nothing since the server arrived to take their orders just at six, finally spoke. "Do you want to continue our conversation from earlier, or would you just prefer to eat?"

"Whadeber ju libe," Harry replied, his mouth full, and Hermione gave him a severe look but took out her wand and re-cast the spells that would give them complete privacy.

"I've been thinking about this soul thing as well," she said, sliding her wand back into its protective pocket within her robe. "There really isn't a way you can definitively prove its non-existence."

"I know," Harry said.

Hermione did a double take. "What? Then why did you…?"

"I've been thinking, too," Harry said, after swallowing a mouthful of potatoes and green beans. "It's hard to prove a negative, that something doesn't exist."

"But it has been done," Monroe pointed out. "Luminiferous ether, for example."

"And phlogiston, and geocentrism, and the classical elements," Harry amplified. "Even though certain theories of magic still accept Air, Earth, Fire and Water as being the basis of all matter."

Hermione was upset with herself. How could she have forgotten about such things? She had read about them years before she ever came to Hogwarts! "Granted," she said, grudgingly accepting that she could be wrong. "But what kind of experiment can you perform that would affect the soul? The only thing we know that is supposed to be able to do that is the act of murder, and you can't go around murdering people in the name of science!"

"Of course not," Harry agreed. "That would be a direct violation of my goals as a scientist and futurist." He leaned forward then, his plate of fried Diricawl forgotten. "But what constitutes a murder, exactly?"

"What do you mean?" Hermione looked shocked. "Killing someone without justification, obviously! Why would you even ask that?"

"To point out the critical factor in murder," Monroe interjected. "A lack of justification."

Harry didn't affirm or deny that comment, he only said, "When an Auror kills a Dark wizard, does he commit murder?"

"Of course not!" Hermione replied immediately. "He is acting lawfully, under the auspices of the Ministry of Magic, which grants him immunity in such cases."

"Even when using the Killing Curse to kill said Dark wizard?" Harry asked.

"Yes."

"Even if said Auror attacks without warning, without giving the Dark wizard a chance to surrender?" Harry asked.

"…Yes," Hermione said, more slowly this time. "The Dark wizard has violated wizarding law and is no longer under its protection, so the Auror has discretion as to how he can bring the Dark wizard to justice."

"And what if the Auror considers such a sneak attack to be murder, but does it anyway, for expediency's sake?"

Hermione frowned again. "I don't know if I can speak to someone's personal morality in such a situation. The Auror is justified under the law — his personal morality in that case is something for him to decide."

"So if I killed someone in self-defense," Harry continued his questioning. "Would I be justified under wizarding law?"

"Yes, if it could be shown that you really were acting in self-defense. Under Veritaserum, for example."

"And what if I were a perfect Occlumens?" Harry smiled.

"Then you would be asked to provide your memories of the incident for Pensieve viewing," Hermione answered, "and Ministry-certified Legilimenses would examine them for inconsistencies and report any to the Wizengamot at your trial."

"With enough planning false memories could be fabricated and made available to the Legilimenses," Harry pointed out.

"Which is why we'd have several Legilimenses independently review the memories, none of whom would know who else is doing so," Hermione said, sounding tired of Harry's nitpicking. "The system isn't perfect, but we can make efforts to be as thorough as possible. Perhaps you'd care to explain what your point is?"

"Only that it's extremely difficult to quantify something like 'justification'," Harry said. "What if I could create a Horcrux without actually killing someone, by making myself believe I had done so? Could I rip my 'soul' in half by sincerely believing I had done murder? What if I subsequently learn that my belief was the result of a False Memory Charm — would that render the Horcrux powerless to preserve my existence if my body were killed?"

"At the Salem Institute," Monroe said, "the consensus is that the soul cannot be healed while a Horcrux exists — it must be destroyed and the wizard who created it must be genuinely, sincerely repentant of the murder committed before the soul can be made whole again.

"Even so," he continued, "there was much debate among wizard-philosophers whether the fragment of the soul from the Horcrux could ever rejoin the soul it was torn from. Some wizard-theologians contended that the souls must meet in the afterlife in order to reconcile and become one again. Others thought that the wizard would exhibit symptoms of schizophrenia or multiple personalities until the healing process was concluded."

"So how might we use a Horcrux to determine whether it traps a fragment of a soul, or whether some other mechanism is in play?" Harry asked. "Because Horcruxes obviously work — we know that Voldemort used one —" (at least one, Harry did not say in front of his wife) "— and that it kept him alive after he tried to kill me."

"And where will you get a Horcrux?" Hermione demanded. "You told me you destroyed the one Voldemort made with Fiendfyre! There should be nothing left of anything burned with magic that powerful!"

"Yes, that's true…mostly," Harry said, slowly, deliberating whether he should show her and Monroe what he'd had hidden away for nearly two decades now. "But maybe we should finish dinner, and I can show the two of you something back at our flat."

Hermione's expression slowly turned dangerous. "Harry…what do you have in our home?!"

"Oh, it's not dangerous!" Harry hastened to say. "I killed it a long time ago."

"Killed it?!" Hermione's voice was the shrillest he'd ever heard it before today. "Harry! You promised me you wouldn't kill any more Dark wizards without telling me first!"

"It bit me first," Harry said, a bit defensively. "But don't worry, love — it's not — quite — a dead Dark wizard."

"I know I've said this before, " Monroe commented matter-of-factly. "But this should be interesting."

=ooo=

After Harry paid the bill for their meal, they walked quickly from Mary's Place to the public Floo station near the intersection of Diagon and Knockturn Alleys, paying 10 Sickles apiece for a small packet of Floo powder, enough for a single trip through Wizarding Britain's Floo Network.

"I'll go first," Harry said, opening his packet in preparation to throwing it into the fireplace they'd been assigned for their trip. "I'll have the connection to our apartment unlocked by the time you and Monroe get there."

"Fine," Hermione said curtly; she was still aggravated at learning Harry had kept something secret about (presumably) Voldemort all these years — he hadn't said who the Dark wizard was, exactly, but it almost certainly had to be that particular one.

Harry glanced at Monroe, who gave a slight shrug of commiseration. It was pretty obvious that Harry's wife was pretty ticked at him. Harry blinked acknowledgement of Monroe's gesture then turned back to the fireplace.

He flicked the bit of Floo powder into the hearth, which promptly burst into brilliant green flames, burning but giving off no heat. "TBC Building!" Harry said loudly, then stepped into the flames and vanished.

Hermione stepped up to the flames next, but instead of throwing her packet in she turned to face Monroe. "Do you know what he's going to show us?" she demanded.

"No, I don't," Monroe shook his head. "He's never mentioned anything about having any kind of Dark wizard artifact."

Hermione stared at him for a moment, then seemed to slump in relief. "It's just been a very weird week since you showed up to interview Harry this last time, Mr. Monroe. I think you've seem more of him in the past few days that I have!"

"You might be right," Monroe conceded. "But honestly, I don't know what to make of all this, either. I still don't know how I got my memories back or why they had been suppressed in the first place."

There was real concern in Hermione's voice. "Have you asked Harry for help finding out what happened? He can't resist a challenge like that."

"To tell the truth," Monroe said, a bit wryly. "That hadn't occurred to me. We've been discussing things like the Magical Singularity and the Interdict of Merlin —"

"Oh." She didn't look happy at that. "His 'secret' projects." When Monroe's expression turned wary, she waved off his concern. "Don't worry about it, Mr. Monroe — I know about them. I just didn't think he was still into that sort of thing anymore — he seemed more interested in the Muggle Singularity these days."

"I was, too," Monroe said. "At least, when I was a Muggle myself. Now the Magical Singularity seems pretty interesting, except…" he trailed off, not sure if he was about to say something he shouldn't.

"Except…what?" Hermione prompted.

"Well… magical knowledge isn't increasing at nearly the rate it should," Monroe went on. "If the Interdict of Merlin continues to impede magical progress, it will slow to a crawl, to almost no further real progress at all. That means non-magical progress will eventually outstrip the magical and the Technological Singularity will probably occur first."

"Assuming that's true, and I'm not sure it is, isn't that good for everyone either way?" Hermione asked, curiously.

"Yes, I suppose," Monroe agreed, slowly. "It might even mean that everyone would be able to perform magic, if our posthuman existence allows us to harness magic as a natural force the way wizards are able to now."

"Have you mentioned that to Harry?"

"Not in so many words."

"Maybe you should," Hermione suggested. "I don't know if he thinks it's a race between the Magical Singularity and the Muggle one, but it seems like there are reasons to work towards both. We'll be waiting for you on the other side." Hermione turned back to the fireplace and threw the packet of Floo powder in. "TBC Building!" she said, very clearly, and the emerald flames swirled about her as she disappeared.

Monroe followed her a moment later, wondering what surprise Harry Potter had in store for them this time.

=ooo=

When Monroe stepped from the fireplace where the Floo connection had deposited him, he immediately recognized where they were: standing in the waiting area of Harry Potter's office. Hermione was there waiting for him, but there was no sign of Harry. Monroe stepped forward to join her then turned around to look at the fireplace he'd just come through. It was taking up most of one wall of the waiting area: a finely-built stone fireplace with a large oak mantle crowning it. "I'm pretty sure that wasn't here the last time I came to visit Harry's office," he said, diffidently.

"It was," Hermione remarked. "You just didn't know it." Looking at the fireplace, she said, "Close, sesame!" in a loud voice.

The fireplace began to disappear with a loud sucking sound, as if it were being pulled through a small hole in the middle of the wall, until nothing remained but the wall itself. The divan that Monroe remembered sitting along that wall had somehow bubbled up out of the floor and nothing looked at all out of the ordinary.

"Handy," Monroe said.

"Not really," Hermione disagreed. "We can't use it during normal business hours, obviously. There's another Floo connection on the main floor, it's our "public" connection in the building. This one, though, is keyed so that only a small group of people arrive here instead of downstairs when they Floo to the "TBC Building."

"How did I get here, then?" Monroe asked, mildly surprised. "Surely I'm not on that list —"

"Of course you are," Harry said from the doorway of his office. "You've been very helpful the past few days — I want your help on some of the things we've been talking about."

Hermione was giving her husband a sidelong glance. "And what has Mr. Monroe been helping you with, dear?" The last word was said with a healthy measure of irony.

"Well, let's see." Harry began counting off items on his fingers. "We started by discussing paths to the Magical Singularity a few days ago, after Monroe learned he was a wizard who had attended both Hogwarts and the Salem Institute.

"Then we got into the Interdict of Merlin, which has been a real hindrance to magical progress over the past 800 years. We've got to do something about that, obviously." Harry counted off another item.

"And then there's this question of whether souls exist or not," he finished. "Which brings us to the thing I wanted to show you. Follow me." Harry led them into his office, where the passageway behind his bookshelves was already opened. But instead of walking down the short corridor to the private dining area, Harry tapped on the corridor wall itself three times. The wall melted away, revealing a small room beyond, with an elevator and a single button.

"We're going to the Vault," Harry told Hermione, in answer to the arched eyebrow she'd given him.

"Mr. Monroe is coming with us?" Hermione asked, trying not to betray the surprise she felt. As far as she knew, Harry had never told anyone except her about the Vault. In fact, this would be the first time she'd actually seen it — assuming Harry let them inside. Which she doubted he would. It was like his Sanctum Sanctorum. His Fortress of Solitude. His…well, she couldn't think of any more superhero hideouts, offhand, but it was something like that.

Harry pushed the button of the elevator, then remarked to Monroe, "It's got fingerprint and DNA recognition, so a Polyjuice potion alone wouldn't fool it."

"Sweet," Monroe said, and both men nodded, smiling. Hermione looked away and rolled her eyes. Boys and their toys!

The elevator doors opened on a long, dimly-lit corridor. They walked its length, their footsteps echoing strangely back and forth. It was quite apparent in listening to them that three separate people were moving along the corridor. At the far end the corridor suddenly dead-ended — there was nowhere else to go.

Monroe looked questioningly at Harry, who pointed at the blank wall ahead of them. "What do you think? A hidden, secret door? A portal, like the entrance to Diagon Alley? Perhaps a Portkey that I've brought with me?"

Monroe looked around at the blank ceiling, floor, and the three walls around them. "It could be any of those, of course. The Portkey seems like the most secure method, though someone might be able to Plot this area and figure out where your Vault room is unless you've made it Unplottable. I assume the area has an Anti-Apparition Jinx on it."

"And a Portkey Hex," Harry added. "So a Portkey's not the answer either. I doubt if any wizard could figure this out in any length —"

"Oh for God's sake, Harry!" Hermione said loudly. "Can we just go inside already?!"

"Alright, alright!" Harry said in a placating tone. He stepped closer to the blank wall ahead of them and cleared his throat. "This is keyed to my voice only, by the way," he said, parenthetically, "so don't try this yourselves." Harry turned to the wall and sang,

Be prepared! That's the Boy Scout's marching song!
Be prepared! As through life you march along!

In response, the doorway opened upon a spiral metal staircase. "Voilà!" he said. "The entrance to the Vault."

Monroe was chuckling to himself. Looking at Harry, he said in a sing-song voice,

Be prepared to hold your liquor pretty well!
Don't write naughty words on walls if you can't spell!

Harry blinked. Several times. "What?" he said, blankly.

"The words to that song," Monroe answered. "'Be Prepared,' by Tom Lehrer."

"It's a real song?" Hermione gasped.

"There are more words to it?" Harry looked thunderstruck.

"Yeah, a couple of verses more," Monroe said. "Haven't either of you ever heard the whole thing?"

Harry looked shocked. He looked at Hermione. "Did you know there were other words to that song?!"

"Don't ask me!" she replied defensively. "I thought it was just something your parents told you so you'd be prepared for — well, things — life — whatever!"

"Okay, never mind!" Harry said, waving off further comment, but promising himself he was going to Siri the words to that song the first chance he got. "Let's go." He stepped onto the stairs, which promptly began moving upward. Behind him, Hermione and Monroe stepped on the stairs as well.

In a few moments the three of them stood before a non-descript door with a small sign on it. The sign read,

What's the
magic word?

Harry turned to Monroe. "From here anyone who knows the secret word can open it. Care to have a go?"

"Not really," Monroe said, flatly. "Unless it's 'recognition code 927, I am a potato'."

"No," Harry said. "I already changed that after meeting you. Go on, guess."

"Harry…" Hermione muttered threateningly.

"Oh, all right!" Harry said, a bit irked at being hurried at the most important part of the whole deal. "Well, it begins with 'Klaatu'."

"Oh!" Monroe grinned. "Klaatu barada nikto!"

Nothing happened.

"You were close," Harry said, beaming. "But actually, it's —"

He turned back to the door and said,

"Klaatu barada n— necktie… neckturn…nickel… It's an 'N' word, it's definitely an 'N' word. Klaatu barada N—" and Harry coughed.

The door slowly opened and Harry stepped inside, then turned around to face them, a wide smile across his face. "Welcome to the Bat Cave!" he said happily.

Hermione was rubbing her forehead. "I knew it was someplace like that…" she muttered to herself.

Harry gestured for them to follow; Hermione and Monroe walked behind him, both looking around in the room's dim lights. There were several rows of bookshelves immediately inside the door, extending off to the left and right; on his left Monroe counted six sets of shelves forming smaller aisles between them. He could see books of all different sizes arranged in them in no particular order — at least, none that he could discern without reading the titles.

Beyond the aisles of books were several display cases arranged in a more-or-less haphazard manner; Harry wandered through them, running a hand over one or two of them as he passed. Monroe looked in the cases as he passed them, but the first case held only three silver objects that looked more like knick-knacks than magical devices. The second case had a wand in it, snapped in two pieces. Another case had a large, jagged rock inside it.

"So where's the giant penny?" Monroe asked, as Harry neared the far wall. Hermione chuckled at that, and Harry turned around to give him a bemused look.

"It's on loan to the London Museum of Magical History," he said, matter-of-factly; he seemed perfectly serious, but Monroe had to assume he was kidding. He turned back to the wall, which had four wooden drawers set into it, pulled one open, and took out a book, which he tossed to Monroe saying, "Have a look at that."

Monroe almost dropped it, but managed to hold on. The book was old and in bad shape; the cover was a faded and worn black, and had the number 1942 at the top near the outside edge. The most striking thing about the book, however, was the gaping hole in its center — Monroe could see just a bit a light showing through from the other side. Whatever had penetrated the book had gone all the way through it.

Flipping it open, Monroe found nothing but blank pages. He looked up at Harry and Hermione. "There's nothing in it," he said, not seeing anything else significant about it.

"Look on the first page," Harry suggested. Monroe opened the book again, and on the first page found the name "T.M. Riddle" written in a flowing script.

"Oh. I get it now," Monroe handed the book toward Hermione, who seemed reluctant to take it — she had seen the name, too.

Harry reached out and took it from Monroe before his wife could take it. "Yes, it's Tom Riddle's," he said to her. "And it was a Horcrux."

"But — but how can that be?" Hermione seemed astonished at that statement. "You told me that you and Professor Dumbledore destroyed his Horcrux, a gold ring with a black stone setting, at the end of our first year!"

"As it turned out," Harry told her, hefting the book, "he had more than one or them."

"More than one Horcrux?" Monroe said, incredulous.

"Yes," Harry said. "Dumbledore and I eventually figured out that he split his soul in three rather than two, because three is a powerful magical number and because the idea of splitting one's —" Harry hesitated, then shrugged and said, "well, soul, more than once is virtually unknown in Dark wizard lore. It's never even been mentioned in wizarding stories like The Tales of Beedle the Bard. Quirrell — or Voldemort, whichever you prefer — probably thought he could guarantee at least one fragment of his soul (or whatever) would never be found and he would remain unkillable forever."

"So he created two Horcruxes?" Hermione looked aghast. "Wouldn't that significantly decrease his magical ability?"

"Why would it do that?" Monroe asked, looking puzzled. Then, "Oh, do you think magic is bound up in one's soul?"

"I don't know," Hermione shook her head. "I don't know if I believe in souls, except that it's the only thing that explains Horcruxes."

"Well, we have an ex-Horcrux here, now," Harry said, holding up the book. "We should be able to examine this for residual magic, maybe conduct some experiments, and see what we come up with."

"But even if there was a soul inside this book once," Monroe argued. "Whatever you did to it released the soul, somehow? How does that help us figure out whether souls exist? And how did you destroy this Horcrux, by the way? It looks like you stabbed it with something."

"A Basilisk fang," Harry said, "from the Chamber of Secrets."

"So you did find it!" Hermione said, her tone accusatory again. "You told me the Chamber of Secrets was probably a legend!"

"I thought it was, when I told you that," Harry admitted. "But Dumbledore and I finally — well, it's kind of a long story, I'll save it for another time."

"Did you have to fight the Basilisk?" Monroe asked.

"No," Harry said, almost wistfully. A True Hero would have found the Monster of Slytherin alive and battled with it to the death. At least, that was how Dumbledore had seen things — he'd been sorely disappointed when they found only its remains. But practicalities ruled back then, and they got what they came for — a way to kill Riddle's diary. Harry hadn't known at the time that Fiendfyre would have killed the diary as well, but right now he was thankful he hadn't, because the cursed fire would have burned the book to ashes, and he wouldn't have it now.

"I suggest we put this away for now," Harry said, "and take a fresh look at it tomorrow. I need to wind down a bit after all the stuff we've been through today."

"You've been through?" Monroe laughed, then shrugged and nodded. "Well, I agree — I'm beat."

"Do you have a place to stay tonight, Mr. Monroe?" Hermione asked, in a kindly tone. "We have a guest room if you'd like to sleep here."

"Thanks," Monroe smiled. "But I'm curious if Malfoy will try to have me picked up again if I get a room at the Leaky Cauldron tonight. I don't think he would dare now, really."

"If he does, he'll probably send a squad of Aurors after you," Harry warned. "But I think you're probably safe, at least tonight — I can't imagine he's that much of a glutton for bad publicity, and that's exactly what he'd get without something really incriminating against you."

"What about that book?" Monroe pointed to Riddle's diary. "Isn't that something he could charge you for — withholding a dangerous or Dark magical item?"

Harry smiled as he idly held up the tattered diary. "He could — if it were a Dark item. But right now it's about as dangerous as wet parchment. He'd find traces of magic, sure — the Department of Mysteries might even figure out that it was Voldemort's.

"Come by the office about six p.m. — and not before," he warned. "I can make sure everyone's gone by five-thirty if I declare tomorrow a Casual Day. Everyone is free to leave anytime after thee p.m. Ginny might be a problem," Harry added parenthetically to Hermione, "but I'll tell her I'm going home at five-thirty, so she might as well go home, too."

"Alright, six it is, then," Monroe agreed. "Now, if one of you could show me how to get out of here…?"

=ooo=

Monroe Apparated to Charing Cross Road, a short walk from the entrance to the Leaky Cauldron. Both Harry and his wife had asked him to stay in their home, but he had the impression that Hermione would soon figure out what he had — that Harry had probably found the diary Horcrux after Quirrell — or Voldemort, whichever way you wanted to think of him — had been killed. In that case, Monroe supposed, there would be a long, protracted argument going on in the Potter-Evans-Verres-Granger household. And Monroe preferred to let the couple work that out on their own.

The proprietress of the Cauldron gave him a wondering look as he asked for a room — no doubt she was wondering what had gone on after she turned him in, Monroe decided, and why he was back in her inn now. But she said nothing to him, nor did he deign to enlighten her about his reasons for returning. The Cauldron was a nice, well-established public house, a place where wizards could venture forth into Muggle London or the magical Diagon Alley, and Monroe wanted to be able to choose either one depending on whether anyone decided to visit him in the middle of the night. He would be prepared for Ministry Aurors in case Malfoy decided to bring him in again despite the recent bad publicity doing so had caused him of late.

And it would be nice, Monroe reflected, walking up to his room, if whoever had put him into this situation in the first place would pay him a visit. For surely, he thought, he would not have done this to himself!

In his room, he cast a series of detection spells, to determine if there were any Muggle or magical scyring devices trained on him. The spells revealed nothing. Monroe began warding the room against any known form of magical intrusion, up to and including a Time-Turned wizard from hours or days in the future (allowing for the possibility that the Ministry could override a Time-Turner's six-hour limit).

With the room magically secure, Monroe began preparing for bed. He Scorgifyed the clothing he was wearing then placed an illusion charm on them to make them appear like a pajama top and bottom. Now a quick Finite would leave him ready for travel in a moment. A similar cleaning spell removed any particles of food remaining in his mouth and throat. He reached in his pocket and pulled out an exact duplicate of his wand, placing on the bedside table next to his bed. Anyone who managed to make it past his wards would suppose that he was unarmed if they saw that wand, indistinguishable from his own.

His mind was still going over the discussions he'd had today with Harry and Hermione. It was true: these past few days had been very interesting. Monroe got into bed, covering himself with the sheets and blankets, then cast a Cooling Charm to keep from getting too warm. Monroe closed his eyes and willed himself to fall asleep. Tomorrow was likely to be even more interesting still.

Chapter 14: A Conversation with the Weasleys

Updated 6/2/2012

=ooo=

James Monroe felt himself awaken, though it seemed he had barely settled into bed for the night. He didn't open his eyes; doing so would only confirm he was awake, and if none of his wards or trip spells were going off, he wanted to be able to drift back to sleep with a minimum of trouble.

On the other hand, something didn't feel right about the room.

Eyes still closed, Monroe began concentrating on his wards one by one, checking if they were still in place. All of them were secure — nothing had tripped any of them, including the wards he'd placed around his bed after he'd climbed in. The wards on the hallway and staircase were secure as well, which made the malaise he felt all the more incomprehensible. Why did it feel like someone was in the room if none of his wards had tripped?

"Wakey, wakey."

Monroe's eyes snapped open. Sitting on a chair beside the bed was a scowling Ron Weasley, dressed in black jeans and T-shirt. Monroe and Ron stared at each other for several seconds before Ron said, with a smirk, "Can we talk?"

Monroe glanced at the bedside table, where his wand had been. It was gone. Not surprising, he thought. "You might have given me a little more notice," Monroe replied, dryly. "We could have met over breakfast."

"I didn't want you ducking out," Ron told him. He held up the wand from the bedside table. "We're going to be talking about you and You-Know-Who."

Monroe pushed himself up onto one elbow, leaning toward Ron. "You're under the same misapprehension the Ministry is, that I know anything at all about Voldemort." He watched as Ron winced slightly at the mention of that name. "He's been dead for decades now."

"Is he?" Even in the dim light of the window Monroe could see that Ron was staring closely at him. "How would you know that?"

"It's common knowledge, that's what everyone thinks," Monroe said, sitting up all the way now. His eyes, still accustomed to darkness, could make out two more figures sitting in the shadows of his room. "Ah, I see this is a real family meeting, so to speak."

"Right," said Fred or George, from the shadows.

"How did you three get in here anyway?" Monroe wondered.

"We made an arrangement with Hannah," one of the twins replied. "She let us know which room you were staying in."

"Hmm," Monroe made a mental note not to stay at the Leaky Cauldron again. "So what are you doing here?"

"Ickle Ronnie here convinced us we should have a little conversation with you, to see what your intentions concerning Harry are."

Ron looked back at them. "Don't call me 'ickle Ronnie'!" he said, irritably.

"Okay, Ronnikins," one of the twins said. Ron shook his head, frustrated, as the chairs Fred and George occupied slid forward toward the bed, stopping on either side of Ron.

"You know, I'm a bit surprised you don't have me hog-tied, muzzled, and on the way to your shop," Monroe commented. "Seeing as how you managed to get past my wards so easily."

"We couldn't —" Ron began.

"You wound us, Mr. Monroe," Fred said, speaking over Ron. "We couldn't be that rude." Ron shot his brother a look but said nothing. "We thought we'd give you the opportunity to respond in a more — oh, neutral, shall we say — environment."

"Thanks," Monroe said, dryly. "So what are your concerns?"

"Harry's our friend," Fred began. "You haven't been here a week yet and he's already had more dealings with you than we've have with him in a year. We've had Ministry people snooping around our shops, looking for evidence against you, they said, though they haven't found anything we didn't want them to find."

"And those things they didn't find," Monroe interrupted. "Are they things you have concerns about?"

"Maybe," George said, neutrally. "The real question is, why are they so interested in you?"

"Maybe because he's a wizard who's been pretending to be a Muggle for years," Ron suggested, in a sarcastic tone.

"That's probably a good reason," Monroe admitted.

"It's a very good reason," Fred agreed.

"I'm almost surprised we haven't yet sorted out why you did that," George added.

"Because he's hiding something, obviously," Ron growled.

"I'm not hiding anything," Monroe declared. "I don't even know why I was pretending to be Muggle."

Ron snorted derision, and Monroe saw the twins glance at one another. "Are you willing to prove that?" Fred or George asked.

"How?" Monroe asked. "Shall we go ask the Ministry for three drops of Veritaserum?"

"Well, not exactly, but close," Fred allowed. "We've been working on something — similar, shall we say, to Veritaserum. Something that's not Ministry controlled or regulated."

"At least, so far," George also allowed. "We're still working out how to keep it a secret once we begin marketing it."

Monroe sat up straighter. "Are you saying you have a truth serum as good as Veritaserum?"

"Better, actually," Fred said, a bit affronted. "Why duplicate something when you can improve on it?"

"About the only real improvement to Veritaserum would be an effectiveness against perfect Occlumens," Monroe suggested. "Does your purported serum have that?"

"That would be telling, wouldn't it?" Ron sneered. "Are you saying you're a perfect Occlumens? Are you afraid to take the chance?"

"Not without knowing what other side effects there may be," Monroe replied, ignoring Ron's first question.

"Afraid?" Ron suggested.

"Cautious," Monroe corrected.

"Fair enough," George said. "How about this, then? You can take it after we try it out on Ron."

"What?" Ron sputtered, outraged. "Me? What're you picking on me for?"

"Well, you are the one who came to us with these claims about Mr. Monroe, Ronnie dear," Fred pointed out. "It seems only fair that we make sure what your intentions are in leveling these charges against the man, don't you think."

Monroe nodded. "It's fair. I agree to those conditions. And that you have to tell me how you made it past my protection spells."

Fred and George looked at one another. "Done."

"Bloody hell," Ron muttered. "Remind me not to bring you two along to my next interrogation."

=ooo=

"How do you want to do this?" Monroe asked. He was sitting on the side of his bed, still in his nightclothes. "Will I get to ask questions too during Ron's turn?"

"No," Ron said, flatly.

"Sure," Fred and George said, smiling. Ron shot them a dark look.

"You're going to get to ask him questions when it's your turn, little brother," Fred said, reasonably. "It's only fair. Now hand over Mr. Monroe's wand, and yours too. We might as well make this as even as we can." Ron did not look happy at this, but surrendered the wands without a word.

Monroe watched interestedly as Fred took out a small potion vial and George conjured a small glass filled with water. Ron was watching, too, but his expression was a bit more…worried than Monroe's. As George held the glass out in front of Ron, Fred tipped three drops from the vial into it, and George handed it to Ron.

"Down the hatch," George said.

"Bottoms up," Fred added.

"Drop dead," Ron snapped, but took the glass and slowly drained it. He stared into the bottom of the glass for a moment, then said, "I can taste it."

"You always say that," Fred scoffed. "It's as tasteless as water."

"What do you mean?" Ron looked puzzled. "This is the first time I've ever tried it!"

Monroe caught a quick smile that passed between the twins. "What next?" he asked, watching Ron carefully now. "How long before it goes into effect?"

"He's ready," George said. "Ron, tell us what we're doing here in Mr. Monroe's room."

Ron, who'd been fidgeting and looking back and forth at his brothers, had settled down and was looking straight ahead, seemingly calm and relaxed. "We're here to question Monroe on what he knows about You-Know-Who."

"Why do you think I know anything about him?" Monroe asked.

"You and Harry Potter have been acting strangely since you showed up a few days ago," Ron said, quietly. "And when we had lunch with Harry a few days ago he suggested that You-Know-Who might not be dead."

Fred frowned. "I don't remember it that way," he said, looking from Ron to George. "I thought Harry said that there was no way to test whether Quirrell was dead short of using the Resurrection Stone, and nobody knows where that is, so it's moot anyway."

"Well, it's how I remember it," Ron insisted.

"So what other evidence do you have that You-Know-Who might be alive?" George asked Ron.

"Um," Ron said, then appeared to be thinking for several seconds. "Malfoy thinks he might be, too."

"And how do you know what Malfoy thinks?" Fred wanted to know.

"I went to see him the other day, after I left the shop," Ron replied.

"What?" Fred and George both said, looking at their brother in shock. "Why would you do that?" Monroe was now listening with intense interest.

"Because I was mad at Harry and wanted to teach him a lesson," Ron said.

"Teach him a lesson for what?" Monroe asked.

"Because he's got these two Confunded or something," Ron said, pointing to the twins. "They think he can do no wrong. But Ginny's told me about a lot of his business dealings and if he's screwing the Muggles out of money, he's probably screwing us, too!"

"You don't know how Muggle business works, Ron," Monroe said. "Harry's job as CEO is to make sure his business makes money. He's a shrewd businessman, but Muggle business doesn't work like it does here in Diagon Alley. Well, it's similar, but the goblins at Gringotts only instituted seigniorage a number of years ago."

Ron looked at him blankly. Both Fred and George were shaking their heads. "What's that?" Fred asked. "I've heard Harry use the word, but he didn't explain it to us."

"What the goblins are doing is altering the amount of gold and silver in their coins, decreasing the ratio of the precious metals," Monroe explained. "Until they started doing this Galleons and Sickles were pure silver and gold, respectively. Harry's told me a little about the goblins and their money. I think Harry has said the ratio is something like 90 percent, and they continue to lower the ratio over time. They are using the gold and silver that doesn't go into coins to speculate in precious metals commodities in the Muggle markets."

George's eyes narrowed. "That sounds like the goblins are using metal that should be in our coins to make themselves richer."

"Technically," Monroe agreed. "But they are also increasing the wealth of the Ministry of Magic compared to other Wizarding communities, the ones that don't use goblins to manage their gold and silver. In the Muggle market the value of one Galleon is worth about fifty to fifty-five British pounds, not five, which is the normal exchange rate at Gringotts.

"Wizarding Britain becoming more solvent is also good for Muggle Britain as well, as long as they speculate wisely with their own gold and silver."

Fred and George looked at each other again. "Could this 'seigniorage' help us increase our profits?" Fred asked, shrewdly.

"No," Monroe said. "You can't mint coins." The twins' expressions fell. "But you can still spin money by providing better product than your competitors. I assume no one else is in the Muggle electronics business yet."

"There are a few new shops trying to copy us," George shrugged. "But they're just trying to reverse-engineer our products and we're careful to put on spellbreakers that activate if anyone tries to fiddle with them. We provide warranty work for up to a year on most of our products, but the warranty is void if you try to figure out how it works."

Monroe nodded; it seems the twins did understand something about Muggle business practices. He looked back at Ron. "Let's get back to business here. Ron, do you really think Harry has your brothers under some kind of spell?"

After a moment Ron shook his head slowly. "No, I don't. But it pisses me off that they think he can do no wrong. He's done a lot of things in his life that he can't be proud of."

"Such as?" Monroe prompted.

"Like…" Ron seemed to grope for something to say. "Well, the stuff he did at school — like trying to get Quidditch changed. Everybody hated that. And our fifth year when he incited everyone to disobey the DADA teacher that year."

"You mean Umbridge?" Fred scowled. "Nobody like her, Ron. She was trying to shut down our magical education system!"

"She was trying to revamp it!" Ron insisted. "We wouldn't have had nearly as much homework once she got things changed around!"

"Because we wouldn't have been learning anything!" Fred snapped. "Thank Merlin that was our last year at Hogwarts, and we could pull out when we did!"

"And what did your General Granger think of what Umbridge was doing?" George wanted to know, throwing a look at his twin as he asked.

"Well, she wasn't happy, either," Ron admitted, a sullen tone creeping into his voice. "But she would've kept on learning on her own, anyway. That's what she did."

Monroe opened his mouth to ask a question but Fred held up a hand. "What did you think of Hermione back then?"

Ron blinked several times. "Um, well, I really liked her, o' course. She was very nice for a Ravenclaw — she'd help anyone who would ask her."

"And you asked her for help quite a lot, didn't you?" George asked, smiling.

"Homework was hard!" Ron insisted. "I could barely keep up, even with her help!"

"But that wasn't the only reason you wanted to spend time with her, was it?" Monroe asked, seeing where the twins' questioning was going.

"No," Ron said, in a small voice. "I — I — l-l-l — liked her."

Monroe sat back, intrigued. What was Ron going to think after the potion wore off and he realized he'd spilled his guts to them? "Do you like her now?" Fred and George both stared at their younger brother, keen to hear his answer.

"I — uh — well, yes," Ron said, nodding slightly. "But I married Luna!"

"Do you still love Luna?" George asked.

"Yes," Ron insisted, nodding.

"So how do you feel about Hermione?" Fred pressed.

"I — well, I — guess I…" Ron's eyes fluttered and he slumped forward, asleep.

"Oh drat," Fred said. He looked at George. "Did that happen faster than last time?" he asked.

"I think so," George answered. He looked at Monroe. "Each time we use our serum on someone, they come out from under it faster and faster. We don't know if there's a lower limit to the duration of the potion or not. A larger dose just builds up immunity faster."

Monroe looked at Ron, now slumped forward in his chair. "How mad do you think he'll be when he wakes and remembers you quizzed him about Hermione?"

Fred and George both beamed. "Well, that's another improvement we made over Veritaserum," George said. "Once the serum takes effect you don't remember anything you've said while under its influence."

"Well, that sounds useful," Monroe agreed. "Especially when questioning close family members."

"Yes." Fred glanced at his sleeping younger brother. "He'll wake up in a few seconds and we'll begin the second round of questioning."

Monroe sat quietly, but his mind was working furiously on how to deal with this situation. There were some things that he and Harry didn't want the Weasleys to know. But if this serum was as good as Fred and George claimed (and it probably was — the Weasley twins were pretty sharp) then even Harry might have difficulty beating it. But there might be things he could do, barring Occlumency, that could keep him from spilling the beans.

Ron suddenly sat up, then looked around blearily. "Did I fall asleep?"
he asked, rubbing his eyes. "What did I miss?"

"Nothing," Fred said smoothly. "We're about to give Mr. Monroe the serum." George was holding out another glass of water, and Fred tipped three drops of the serum into it and handed it to Monroe.

"Cheers," Monroe said, and drank it down. Ron lost his bleary look and began smiling in anticipation of grilling him.

The change that came over him was very subtle, Monroe discovered. He was beginning to feel the urge to be honest. It was almost as if someone had cast an Imperius Curse on him and commanded him to tell the truth. If the Weasleys had found a way to incorporate that curse into a potion…

But you could resist an Imperius if you knew how, if you had the will to do so. And if that was what made the Weasleys' serum so effective, it could be resisted as well. Monroe relaxed, becoming calm and quiet, and waited for the questioning to begin.

"He looks ready," Fred was saying. "Let's jump right in, then. Mr. Monroe, tell us everything you know about You-Know-Who?"

"Not a lot to tell," Monroe answered. "His real name was Tom Marvolo Riddle. He attended Hogwarts from September 1938 to June 1945. He was made a prefect in 1942 and Head Boy in 1944. He won a medal for Magical Merit and for Special Services to Hogwarts in 1943. He worked at Borgin and Burkes for a while after leaving Hogwarts, then disappeared for about a decade, reappearing at Hogwarts in 1956 to ask the new Headmaster, Albus Dumbledore, for the Defense Against the Dark Arts position. Dumbledore did not give him the job, and Riddle cursed the position so that no one teaching it would hold the position for more than a year."

"All of that is pretty boilerplate," George remarked.

"What we want to know," Ron jumped in, "is what you know about You-Know-Who now, today!"

"I've just told what I know about Riddle today," Monroe replied, tonelessly.

"That's not what I meant!" Ron snapped. He looked at Fred and George. "Are you sure this stuff works?"

"It has so far," George replied. "Mr. Monroe, do you know anything about You-Know-Who's whereabouts today?"

Monroe shook his head. "He's supposed to be dead, killed in 1992 during a battle with Harry Potter."

"Is it possible he wasn't killed then?" Fred asked.

Monroe stared at him a moment. "Of course it is," he said at last. "But Harry would know more about that than I would."

"Has he said anything about it to you?" George probed.

"We've talked about Voldemort," Monroe admitted, making Ron flinch again slightly. "But only because he accused me of being him, or being possessed by him, due to my time pretending to be a Muggle."

"How did you convince him otherwise?" Ron demanded.

"He poured goblin anti-concealment water on me," Monroe answered. "Nothing happened — Voldemort didn't pop out of me, and I didn't regain my memories of why I was pretending to be a Muggle."

"Do you know what Malfoy suspects about you?" Fred asked.

"The same thing you do," Monroe answered. "That I have some connection with Voldemort."

"You seem to have a lot of people thinking that about you," Ron pointed out. "So why shouldn't we be taking it seriously?"

"I don't know," Monroe shrugged. "Maybe you should, but I can only tell you what I know."

"Right, then," Fred muttered. "So tell us what you remember of your time at Hogwarts. How long did you attend school there?"

"I attended until the end of my second year," Monroe said. "After that my parents and I decided we weren't going to deal with the craziness going on there — Dumbledore's strangeness, the problem with the Defense professor — the person that taught in my second year was a complete idiot, and Harry himself was causing quite a bit of trouble there with school activities like Quidditch."

Fred and George both smiled, remembering The Year Without the Snitch. "Yes, that was a rather unusual year," George recalled. "Were you a Quidditch fan like Ronnie here?"

"That was the worst year for Quidditch ever," Ron declared, scowling. "Potter made the game unplayable and unwatchable!"

"I didn't care that much for Quidditch," Monroe said. "But a lot of class time was wasted in discussions of the games — even the teachers would start talking about them! Our learning experience was being eroded. And we never learned anything in Lockheart's classes anyway — the man spent most of the time talking about himself instead of teaching Defense Against the Dark Arts!"

"Sounds like Monroe and Hermione would have made a good couple," Fred muttered to George, across Ron, who glared at him.

"That might be a good question," George smiled. To Monroe he said, "What did you think of Hermione Granger back then? Did you like her?"

"She was okay," Monroe replied. "She was a fellow Ravenclaw, and she was very helpful to other students who weren't as advanced as her."

"But did you like her?" Fred pressed. Ron had a taut expression on his face.

"I was not at Hogwarts to meet girls," Monroe said. "I wasn't even in my teens when I left. Hermione was nice, but she was still a girl. At Salem things were different — I was older and the girls were — well, beginning to fill out." Unconsciously Ron exhaled.

"Did you ever get married, then?" George asked.

"I don't think so," Monroe said. "I don't remember much after leaving Salem."

"What do you remember after that?" Fred asked.

"I remember getting the job at Singularity Today magazine," Monroe replied. "But by then I thought I had moved back to Britain from America."

"And you don't remember anything between Salem and then?" Ron asked, skeptically.

Monroe shook his head. "No."

Ron looked at his brothers. "He's lying, somehow."

"No," Fred declared. "The more he tries to avoid telling the truth, the more the potion compels him to do so."

Monroe nodded. "So I'm probably right — you incorporated an Imperius Curse into your truth serum."

Fred and George both raised an eyebrow. "Bravo," Fred said. "Brilliant deduction, Sherlock."

Ron looked horrified. "Why did you tell him that? He's going to turn us in!"

"Because he won't remember," George replied. "We also incorporated a Memory Charm into the potion. Mr. Monroe won't remember a thing after the serum wears off."

"What?" Ron's expression had gone horrified again. "And you were going to try that out on me? When were you going to tell me about that?"

"We told you every time we gave it to you, little brother."

"What?"

"I probably won't remember," Monroe agreed. "But I do have a pretty good track record theses days beating Memory Charms."

"Even if you do remember," Fred mused. "Going to the Ministry won't do you much good, if Malfoy suspects that you're connected with You-Know-Who."

"He might want you more now, especially if he thinks you have a better truth potion than Veritaserum," Monroe pointed out, blinking. He was beginning to feel sleepy — the last stage before the potion wore off. The question was, how much would he remember?

"Oh, we've had rumors circulating around Diagon Alley for years about a 'super-Veritaserum'," George answered cheerfully. "Malfoy will think it's just another one of those. And even if he does send Ministry folk to search our shops again, he won't find anything."

"Too bad we can't chat longer, Mr. Monroe," Fred said, a bit regretfully. "I'd really like to know what Harry sees in you."

"Maybe a kindred soul," Monroe answered, then yawned hugely. "I'm interested in a lot of the same things he is."

"Could be it," Fred muttered. "But I'm not convinced. We may have to do this again sometime."

"Sorry, I won't…yaaaaaaaaaawn…agree to this again," Monroe murmured. "Er, before I fall asleep, tell me how you got past my wards."

Fred and George smiled. "We didn't. We used a spell to hide ourselves in your room before you came up to bed," one of them said.

"What spell?" Monroe wanted to know.

"We didn't agree to tell you that," the other said. "And now, good night."

Monroe opened his mouth, but no words came out. His head slumped forward, and he began to snore softly.

"Well, that was a bust," Ron said, chagrinned, as Monroe snored. "We didn't learn anything from him." He put out a hand and pushed Monroe so he fell back on his bed.

"We learned he doesn't know anything," George said. "Even though you insisted he did."

"I was certain he had to!" Ron said, defensively.

"Sure you were." Fred turned to George. "Do you think we can find a way past his wards before he wakes up?"

"Doubt it," George said. "They are rock solid. We may have to wait until he checks out in the morning."

"Bother," Fred said. He shot Ron a dark look for the inconvenience he'd caused them. "Well, let's get hidden and wait it out."

=ooo=

James Monroe felt himself awaken, though it seemed he had barely settled into sleep for the night. He didn't open his eyes; doing so would only confirm he was awake, and none of his wards or trip spells were going off; after a few moments he drifted back to sleep.

Chapter 15: The Interdict Deciphered

Updated 6/16/2012

=ooo=

August had slouched its way into September, and September blew into October, until the most important holiday on the Wizarding calendar loomed just ahead — All Hallows' Eve, now known as Harry Potter Day. The day was cause for much celebration amongst the magicals of Britain, with dozens of parties where many of the merry-makers dressed up in Harry Potter costumes (school robes, round glasses and in some cases, wigs of unruly black hair).

However, for Harry, the day was still The Dark Lord Killed My Parents Day. Thankfully, though, time had erased much of the sadness of the occasion for him, and he no longer spent the day in hiding, as he had during most of his years at Hogwarts, where he stayed in his trunk and ate snack bars rather than go to the Great Hall for meals. Now he usually immersed himself in work at TBC Enterprises, Ltd., staying in his office until after midnight. Hermione, as Minister of Magic, usually hosted a party for Ministry personnel held somewhere in Diagon Alley — this year it would be at the Leaky Cauldron, so that anyone who didn't feel like going home afterwards could stay there for the night. All of the rooms had been reserved by October 13th this year, and other inns along Diagon Alley were fully reserved as well, indicating a fine turnout for this happiest day of the year.

"You should think about attending," Hermione gently suggested one night, not long before the day arrived. "It's been twenty-five years, after all, Harry — it would do you some good to get out with other wizards and enjoy the celebration. I know it was a sad day for you, but it also gave hope back to many people in magical Britain, knowing that you had defeated Voldemort."

"Yeah," Harry muttered, trying not to snap at his wife, who after all was trying to help him in her own way. "But you know what I think about that, love."

"I know," Hermione smiled, a bit ruefully. "Most people are committing the fallacy of the fundamental attribution error, ascribing Voldemort-killing abilities to you when it was actually your mother's sacrifice of her own life that provided the protection that saved you from Voldemort's Killing Curse, and destroyed him. Almost destroyed him, that is," she added, unnecessarily.

"Right," Harry managed a small smile. The way she said all that usually made him smile; she'd heard him say it it so many times now it must be indelibly inscribed in her memory. As it was in his.

"Well, if you aren't going to change your mind about going, what do you plan on doing tonight?" Hermione asked. "Work in your office?"

It was what Harry usually did these days. But, "I think Monroe and I are going to do some spell research," Harry finally said.

"Ah, I see." Hermione's response had been toneless, but with an undercurrent of disapproval. She wasn't sure what they were researching these days, exactly, but in the past they had been working on controversial subjects like the existence of souls, the source of magic in the world, and things she didn't quite understand, like the Singularity. These were things best suited for the Department of Mysteries, regulated and controlled by the Ministry, not for private conversations held in the home of the Minister of Magic — or worse, in some pub where anyone might overhear. She almost preferred that they meet at Mary's Place, in the specially-enchanted room there that kept conversations private, even though the cost of reserving that room made it unusable by almost anyone, and thus an item of interest whenever it was reserved these days, especially by someone like Harry Potter!

Harry had caught the disapproval in his wife's voice. "Don't worry, love," he told her. "We're not breaking any laws." At least, not so far, he added to himself. The Department of Mysteries would be mightily interested in what he and Monroe were researching, thought, if they were to find out.

The Interdict of Merlin.

That spell, possibly the most powerful single spell ever cast, more than 800 years ago, was the major reason magical research was slowly grinding to a halt, and the biggest contributor to the loss of magical knowledge over the past eight centuries. Merlin may have believed that once wizards were forced to share their most powerful spells with one another personally rather than through books or scrolls, that there would be more of a spirit of cooperation amongst magical folk, but he'd obviously had a higher opinion of the Wizarding community than was deserved. The most powerful spells were hoarded and guarded, preserved in books only the author could read, until everyone who knew the spell had died before passing it on and its secret was lost to the Wizarding world.

The Interdict had spread outward from Britain, wherever magic was practiced, until only the most desolate, inhospitable places on Earth hadn't been touched by it. Many magical cultures never even realized the Interdict was in effect until the International Confederation of Wizards established the International Statute of Wizarding Secrecy and the details of the Interdict were made public to the world, due in large part to indiscretion on the part of the British members at that time. The news was not well-received, and relations between Britain and many other wizarding communities became strained. To this day Britain, though it was once considered the most powerful wizarding community in the world, was now considered a backwater community. The Ministry of Magic, of course, did not share that opinion.

The Big Day finally arrived. Harry spent that day, a Monday, at work as usual, leaving only a little early to avoid anyone asking him on their way out if he was attending the party at the Leaky Cauldron that year. At home, he immersed himself in a book until Hermione arrived home from the Ministry to change for the party.

"Still not going?" Hermione asked from the bedroom as she changed.

"No," Harry said, still reading his book. "I don't think life in Wizarding Britain will grind to a halt, do you?"

"I hope not," Hermione agreed, smiling. "Are you and Mr. Monroe having dinner at Mary's Place?"

Harry and Monroe met a couple of times a week to continue their discussions on various matters of import to both of them. "No," Harry replied, putting down the book he'd been reading, a tome on spell research methods from one Remus Lupin. "I thought he and I would eat in tonight."

"Really?" Hermione was taken aback somewhat. "Has he tasted your cooking before tonight?"

"Ha-ha," Harry said, sardonically. "I'm having Ginny pick up something for us before she goes home."

"She's still at work?" Hermione gave him a look from the bedroom door. "You slave-driver."

Harry put up his hands. "Hey, I'm not forcing her to stay."

Hermione looked solemn. "Well, from what she's said to me, she and Dean have been going through a rough patch for the past few months."

"She hasn't said anything to me."

Well, she wouldn't, Hermione thought to herself. She knew well enough that Ginny had nursed feelings for Harry for a long time now. But Harry seemed oblivious to it, so Hermione had let that sleeping dog lie. She picked up her wrap. "You and Mr. Monroe have a nice time tonight with your 'research.' I should be home about one or so."

"Have a nice time tonight," Harry said, as Hermione walked over and pecked him on the mouth. Smiling, she rubbed Harry's shoulder then made her way down the corridor that led to the anteroom where their private Floo entrance was, taking it to the first floor so she could walk outside and Apparate to the Leaky Cauldron.

It was really too bad she couldn't get Harry out more these days, Hermione thought to herself as she tapped the door leading from the first floor Floo room, silently casting Alohomora. He was getting too wound up in his magical research with Monroe. Not really a bad thing, she admitted to herself; who knew, they might actually come up with something useful. She closed the door behind her, relocking it with Colloportus, and made her way to the exit of the TBC Building.

=ooo=

James Monroe walked briskly through the darkening streets of London, heading toward Harry's apartment above his business offices. He could have Apparated to the building in a moment, but walking gave him time to think. He'd had to do a lot of thinking lately, what with all the discussions they'd had over the past three months, three months of effort that they had very little results to show for.

Not that a lack of results was discouraging — concepts such as where magic had come from and whether man had an imperishable soul had been debated for decades and centuries; it wasn't like he or Harry were going to solve them in three months! Their discussions had given them both a lot to think about, things both Muggle and magical, and the time had passed quickly.

"Why hello!" Monroe looked up to find Ginny Thomas walking beside him, carrying a large sack from a nearby wizarding café. "I wondered if I'd see you while I was out getting dinner," she continued, smiling at him.

"Hello, Ms. Thomas," Monroe nodded, smiling as well. "What are we having tonight?"

She held up the bag. "Sandwiches from Mo's. I've got several kinds in here — Diracawl and crisps, chip buttys with bacon or sausage, and stoat rolls. Oh, and I got a couple of Dirigible Plum and sprout sandwiches, in case you or Harry are feeling vegetarian today," she added.

"Sounds tasty," Monroe commented, a hint of irony in his voice. They arrived at the TBC Building and he opened the door for her, then followed her across the lobby to a hallway were they would take the private Floo connection up to Harry and Hermione's apartment.

Just at the hallway entrance they ran into Hermione herself coming out. "Oh, I see dinner's here," Hermione said, smiling at them.

"Hi, Minister," Ginny said with a grin. She always called Hermione "Minister" when they first greeted one another. "Off to the party?"

"Yes," Hermione nodded. "I tried to get Harry to go this time, but he still won't…" She turned to Monroe. "I don't know if Harry has told you what today is…"

"I've gathered," Monroe replied. "It's all over wizarding London — Harry Potter Day. This is the first time I've actually been around, of course — they didn't celebrate it in America. What's-His-Name wasn't that big a deal over there, though it made a lot of people happy when Harry took care of him."

Hermione nodded perfunctorily, as if distracted, then smiled at Ginny. "Are you and Dean coming to the Cauldron for the party tonight?" she inquired.

"I wish," Ginny said, ruefully. "Dean's working late tonight." She pointed upward. "He's still up there, somewhere. I brought a couple of sandwiches for him, though he sometimes gets so busy he works right through supper."

"Ah," Hermione put on another perfunctory smile. "Well, you both are welcome if you decide to attend — we'll be going until well after midnight, if history is any indication. And you as well, Mr. Monroe — if you can get Harry to come with, or even if you can't, we'd love to see you there."

"I'll keep it in mind," Monroe replied, with a nod of thanks. "If we finish our discussion early it would be interesting to see what a Harry Potter Day party is like."

"I'm off, then," Hermione waved at them then continued across the lobby and out the main doors, as Monroe and Ginny walked down the hallway, stopping in front of a door marked Building Maintenance.

Ginny slid her wand out and tapped the door knob, muttering "Alohomora," as the knob made a loud click. Monroe opened the door for her and they stepped inside the room containing only a stone fireplace with a walnut mantelpiece. Taking a pinch of powder from a bowl on the mantle, Ginny tossed it into the fireplace. Emerald flames blazed forth from the hearth and Ginny stepped into them, saying "Potter-Evans-Verres private entrance!" and disappearing.

Monroe duplicated her actions, appearing several seconds later in the anteroom of the Potter residence. Ginny was waiting for him at the door. Together they walked down the hallway adjoining the antechamber with the Potter residence.

Harry looked up as they walked in, then marked his place in Spell Research Methodologies and Practices and put the book aside. "Good," he said. "I'm starving! What did you bring us today?"

"Mo's," Ginny replied, setting the bag on the dining room table and taking out several wrapped sandwiches and bags of chips and crisps. "I got something for Dean, too," she told Harry.

"Aren't you two going to the party at the Leaky Cauldron?" Harry asked, curiously. "I thought you went every year."

Ginny shrugged as she pointed her wand, summoning bottles of butterbeer from the kitchen. "He wanted to work tonight," she said, indifferently. "I wasn't going to argue with him."

Monroe and Harry glanced at one another. That phrase was one Ginny said more and more often these days; she and Dean were seldom seen together these days, at work or anywhere else. Neither of them had mentioned anything to her, however — to Harry it was part of her personal life, and while he and Ginny had been close for a while back in Hogwarts, it had never developed into anything. Monroe, for his part, considered it none of his business.

"So what are you two going to talk about tonight?" Ginny asked, changing the subject.

"More of the same, probably," Monroe put in.

"In other words," Harry elaborated, "whatever comes to mind, most likely."

Ginny nodded, looking thoughtful. "D'you mind if I listen in for a while?" she asked. "I'll bring Dean his sandwich later, when he's more likely to be hungry."

Ginny had never stayed before. Harry glanced at Monroe, who made a It's-your-call shrug. Harry glanced at his watch. "It's nearly six," he said. "He's probably hungry by now." He sat down at the table across from Monroe, who'd already taken a seat there.

Ginny handed Harry a wrapped Diracawl sandwich, his favorite. "He might be," she admitted. "But unless he's starving he'll want to finish his work first, and he might forget all about food until he gets home. I'd rather bring him his meal when he's hungry enough to eat it right then."

Harry nodded with a shrug; Ginny knew Dean better in that regard than he did. Harry himself usually paid little attention to food, especially during these discussion meetings with Monroe. The discussions were always much more fascinating that wondering where or when they'd be eating on those nights. "What were we talking about the other night?" he asked Monroe.

"The Interdict," Monroe replied. He knew Harry remembered exactly what they'd been talking about; he rarely forgot anything about their discussion, being able to pick up precisely wherever they'd left off when they ended a discussion for the night.

"Which is what?" Ginny asked, looking at them curiously. She had picked up a Dirigible Plum and sprout sandwich and a butterbeer for herself. "I remember reading about that in school, but it's been too long…"

"It was the last spell cast by Merlin," Harry explained. "He is supposed to have cast it in response to the other wizards of his time not working hard enough to prevent the end of the world due to misuse of magic. It's been in absolute force for the past 800 years, unchanging and invincible."

"Oh," Ginny set down the bottle of butterbeer she'd just taken a drink from. "So why are you and Mr. Monroe talking about it?"

"We're looking for a way to beat it," Harry smiled.

"Unsuccessfully, so far," Monroe added, wryly.

"But why even try?" Ginny wondered, looking a bit alarmed. "The Ministry can't be happy about that!"

"What they don't know won't worry them," Harry retorted.

"But surely your wife knows!" Ginny pointed out. "What does she think about all this?"

"Oh, she doesn't like it, not one bit," Harry shrugged. "But unless she hears that we actually tried to break the Interdict, or something of that nature, there's no law that says we can't discuss it."

"For all the good it's done us," Monroe muttered, chewing on a bite of his sandwich. "We've talked about it for months, on and off, and haven't come up with anything. I'm about ready to go back to disproving the existence of the soul."

Ginny looked back and forth between the two men, frowning. "Disproving the existence of the soul? You've got to be joking!"

"Oh come on," Harry gently chided her. "You have to know I don't believe in stuff like that!"

"I — I thought that was just part of your Muggle persona," Ginny replied. "Harry, you're the one who kept me from being taken over by that — that book."

"I know," Harry nodded. He'd been thinking about that recently as well. When Ginny began attending Hogwarts at the beginning of Harry's second year, she'd found an extra book among the ones her parents had gotten for her at Flourish and Blotts. Harry had later heard, through Hermione, that there'd been an "altercation" at the bookstore between Mr. Weasley and Lucius Malfoy. Hermione and her parents had been there as well; they'd gone with her to see Diagon Alley and happened to run into the Weasleys.

"It was all very interesting," Hermione had reported to Harry afterwards, before the Sorting and Start of Year feast had begun. Mr. Weasley is very interested in non-magical people. He even collects electrical plugs and other things, like batteries and Muggle kitchen utensils." She giggled. "He kept calling electricity 'eckeltricity,' though — it was so charming!

"But then," and her voice had gone serious, "he and Mr. Malfoy were standing almost nose-to-nose, arguing. Mr. Malfoy had taken Ginny's cauldron full of books and was making fun of them — they'd had to buy most of them second-hand — and Mr. Weasley was trying to get them back. They almost came to blows, but Mr. Malfoy finally handed the cauldron back to Ginny and walked out of the store."

Harry and his mother Petunia had gone to Diagon Alley a few weeks earlier, a few days after he'd turned twelve and his letter came with his list for supplies and books for that year. Most of the books on the list were by someone named Gilderoy Lockhart, and Harry later learned that every student at Hogwarts had to buy those same books, no matter what year they were in. He'd taken an instant dislike to Lockhart, who'd somehow managed to get all of his books on the schoolbook buy list for every student in school, which was probably making him a hill of gold. Later, at the Hogwarts feast, it had become quite obvious why that had happened — Lockhart was the Defense professor that year! Such shameless egoism earned Lockhart Harry's instant enmity for the entire school year.

"I remember," Harry told Ginny. "You spent almost the entire year with that diary in your possession, until I found you in that abandoned bathroom, nearly unconscious, and took it away from you."

Monroe had been listening to this exchange intently. "But what about —" his tongue suddenly locked against the roof of his mouth as Harry raised a finger in warning.

"We don't know what was going on with Ginny and that book," Harry said, his words making it clear that he wasn't to say anything about what he knew to Ginny. "And we may never know, unfortunately."

But Ginny had caught Harry's motion and Monroe's sudden silence. "You do know something," she snapped at Harry, accusingly. "What did you do with that book, Harry?"

Harry looked at her for a long moment, seeming to weigh something he might or might not say. Finally he stood and walked slowly from the room, returning with a dark gray stone box. He set it on the table next to Ginny and gestured for her to open it.

Ginny stared at the box, looking almost afraid to open it, but she finally reached out and slowly opened the lid. "Oh, Merlin," she breathed, when she saw what was inside. "It's that book, Harry! But what happened to it?" She lifted the tattered, ripped diary from the box, looking at the hole punched through its center.

"I had to kill it," Harry replied.

=ooo=

"Kill it?" Ginny looked at him, puzzled, turning the diary over in her hand. "What in Merlin's name are you talking about? Why would you kill a book?"

"It wasn't an ordinary book," Harry said, quietly.

"I gathered that," Ginny said, dryly. "But what about it?"

"You remember that I told you afterward that the book was cursed with Dark magic and that it was negatively affecting you?" Harry reminded her. Ginny nodded, waiting. "Well, it was Dark magic, but that wasn't the full story."

"Go on," Ginny prompted, impatiently.

"T.M. Riddle, the person the book originally belonged to, was Tom Marvolo Riddle, the man who became Lord Voldemort," Harry said, speaking quickly so he couldn't back out halfway through.

Ginny sat back in her chair, staring at Harry in disbelief. "And you never told me that, in all these years?" she nearly shouted at him.

Harry covered his face, half in shame, half so he wouldn't have to look at Ginny. "It wouldn't have helped you either way," he said at last from behind his palms. "I had the book locked away in a special box in my trunk. I never showed it to anyone — not even Hermione."

"She doesn't know about it then?" Ginny asked. It made her happy in some way to think Harry had told her something she hadn't confided to his wife.

"I showed it to her a few months ago," Harry admitted, and Ginny managed not to look disappointed at that news. "But I never told her where it came from — she never knew you originally had it. You never told anyone about it while you had it, did you?"

"No," Ginny shook her head. "It was my most private secret. I wrote a lot of things into it, and it answered me! Did you know it could do that?"

"I found out, eventually," Harry said. "After I had it for a while I took it out of its box for a thorough examination. At one point I had a smudge of ink on a fingertip, and when I touched a page with that finger the ink vanished after a moment. I put a few drops of ink on the page and they vanished, too. I thought that explained why all the pages were blank, so I wrote something in it like, 'My name is Harry Potter-Evans-Verres' on the page. And it told me, 'I'm Tom Riddle, pleased to meet you,' or something like that."

"And Tom Riddle was Vo— You-Know-Who," Ginny said, slowly. "What did he do, create a diary with his memories in it, like a portrait?" She was peering at Harry very curiously. "Come on, Harry, tell me! I want to know the truth!"

Harry looked quite undecided on what to do. Only a handful of people in Wizarding Britain knew the truth about Tom Riddle. And he'd promised Dumbledore he would never tell anyone else about him and what he'd done. But Ginny had been directly affected by what Riddle had done — didn't she deserve to know the truth?

"Riddle," Harry said, hesitating, "found a way to put a part of himself in the diary. It's more than a portrait, it's — more like a bit of him, his — his soul, if you want to call it that."

"But you don't believe in souls," Ginny pointed out.

"Which doesn't negate what Riddle was able to do," Harry retorted. "It's very Dark magic — so Dark, in fact, that it was never even mentioned at Hogwarts once Dumbledore became Headmaster. I only found out about it in my sixth year, when I finally told him about the diary and he made me show it to him. He said we had to find a way into the Chamber of Secrets, to learn more about the book. It took nearly my entire sixth year to find out where the entrance was — ironically, it was in that same toilet I found you in during your first year. We went down there and found the skeleton of the Basilisk there, and the Headmaster had me use one of the fangs to stab the book. It spurted black ink-like liquid, almost like I'd stabbed a small animal in the heart, and we heard a screaming sound. And that was it. Dumbledore wanted the book but I told him I was keeping it."

"Harry." Monroe, who'd been listening to all of this, had a bemused expression on his face. "I have a question."

"Shoot," Harry said, glad to be distracted for a moment from this heavy conversation.

"If this diary was a you-know-what," Monroe said, avoiding the word Harry hadn't used yet, "when do you think Riddle made it?"

"What is 'you-know-what'?" Ginny asked.

"I know when he made it," Harry replied, ignoring her question. "He told me while I was writing to him in the diary. He made it during his fifth year, probably sometime in 1943."

"Do you think he made it after he opened the Chamber of Secrets?" Monroe asked evenly.

Harry suddenly looked interested. "Yes, he did! He tried to tell me some cock-and-bull story, about someone having opened the Chamber and students being attacked by a monster until a girl was killed, but it didn't quite ring true. Dumbledore told me that Hagrid was blamed for the murder of Abigail Myrtle back in 1943 and expelled from the school, confirming what Quirrell had told me earlier, during my first year, but neither of them mentioned anything about any other students being attacked."

"I'm remembering what you told me a few weeks ago, about what Quirrell told you about Voldemort and the Monster of Slytherin," Monroe continued with his chain of logic. "You also said that Parseltongue was personal magic of some kind, not the ability of snakes to speak and understand a language."

"Yeah," Harry nodded, following where Monroe was going, and growing more and more excited by the moment. "Yeah! So the Basilisk couldn't have been intelligent on its own! I can't effing believe I didn't make that connection years ago!"

"What connection?" Ginny asked, anxiously. Obviously both men were excited by something they had just figured out. "And you never told me what 'you-know-what' means!"

"Okay, look," Harry turned to her, his gaze boring intently into hers. "You deserve to know this, because you had to deal with what Riddle's diary put you through, but you can't tell anyone what I'm about to tell you. Not Dean, not your brothers, no one. Can you do that, Ginny? And be honest," he warned her, "because I'll know if you're lying."

Ginny nodded slowly. "I won't tell anyone," she promised.

Harry, looking into her eyes, believed her. "Okay," he said, and took a deep breath. "Riddle's diary was a Horcrux."

"A what?" Ginny shook her head blankly. "I don't know what that means."

"It's an object that's had a part of a wizard's soul put into it," Harry explained. "As long as that object exists, that wizard cannot be permanently killed. The Horcrux anchors the wizard to the material world. Even if you destroy his body, he remains stuck here. Eventually that part of him that's still here can interact with the world again, especially with the minds of other people. That's how Voldemort was able to take over Quirrell and have him come to Hogwarts to teach Defense, something Dumbledore never let Riddle himself do."

"And that's how the diary was able to affect you," Monroe went on, saying what Harry didn't want to say himself. "Riddle's mind was in the diary, and it was able to manipulate it to reply to you and Harry when you wrote in it."

Ginny looked horrified. "So — so — that d-diary was trying to take over my body?"

Harry nodded, not looking at her. "It almost did, too, before I took it from you. Riddle tried the same thing on me, but I was able to resist him. And I just realized —" Harry looked at Monroe, anger in his face. "I think Dumbledore may have figured out about the diary, and that's why he wanted it destroyed. He didn't want me learning about what Riddle knew —"

Monroe nodded. Ginny was looking confused again. "Knew what?"

"Knew that Horcruxes could pass on spells to another living mind," Harry said, both grimly and with excitement continuing to bubble within him. "I killed Riddle's diary without knowing that I could have gotten everything he learned from the Monster of Slytherin! Dammit!"

"But at least we have a way around the Interdict now," Monroe pointed out. "We just need to find another Horcrux."

Ginny shuddered involuntarily. "Why would anyone want to risk something like that?" she shouted. "You just told me those things can take over your mind!"

"They can if you don't suspect that's what happening," Harry clarified. "But I can resist them — a Horcrux won't be able to take me over. I just wish we could find one from Salazar Slytherin himself."

"But that's not very likely," Monroe averred.

"I know," Harry agreed, glumly. "It's unlikely anyone before Riddle created more than one of them, even Slytherin himself. And he probably didn't expect the Heir of Slytherin to destroy his Horcrux after learning all of its secrets."

Harry was silent for some time. Then, "But, still…"

"What are you thinking?" Monroe asked, wondering what had occurred to him.

Harry didn't say anything right away. "I don't know," he finally admitted. "It seems like a long shot, but… something's making me think Slytherin was smarter than that. His Basilisk Horcrux might not have told Riddle everything that he did, only what he wanted him to know."

"You think —" Ginny was staring at him with dread. "You think Slytherin did create more than one of these…Horcruxes?"

"Yeah," Harry nodded. "Or, I think it's worth checking out, at least, to see if I'm right about that."

"And how are we going to do that?" Monroe inquired.

"We're going down into the Chamber of Secrets."

Chapter 18: Monroe's Head

Updated 8/3/2012
Last Updated 4/15/2013

=ooo=

As Harry leapt from the seventh-floor windowsill the twin cylinders attached to his broom ignited. Both solid-fuel rockets, they pushed Harry forward as a Levitation Charm kicked in, balancing most of Harry's weight. The rockets only provided about 40 pounds of thrust apiece, and only for 10 seconds, but that was enough to carry him over the nearest wall of the school grounds.

From that point the wards against flying objects were no longer in effect so, using the broom's innate flying ability, Harry tipped himself downward and spiraled to the ground. He landed not far from the road that led to Hogsmeade, but he had no intention of going there or letting anyone see that he was now outside the castle. He stuffed the broom back into his mokeskin pouch and Disapparated, heading toward London.

He appeared outside the TBC building, startling a passerby who almost walked into him. Harry excused himself and stepped aside, leaving the man looking around, wondering where he'd come from. Harry was frowning as he walked into the entrance to the building. He should have arrived in the small anteroom with the Floo connection up to his apartment. That meant someone, probably the Aurors who were searching his business, had established an Anti-Apparition Jinx on the inside of the building. And that meant they were probably expecting him or Hermione to show up, to find out what was going on. Well, he was here, but he wasn't going to show up until he was sure Malfoy and his goons could find no way into his private residence from his business offices. If he did, Harry knew, Malfoy would probably exercise the loophole that would let him check the residence if such an entryway was found. Just as if Harry were nothing more than a Death Eater.

Harry entered through the revolving doors. There were no Aurors waiting in the lobby for him, which meant that Malfoy put more importance on finding a secret entrance than he did on people entering the building. Harry began checking for wards and protections that the Aurors would have layered on top of his own spells. He found a ward that would notify the caster whenever someone entered the building; someone would have to come down and check to see who he was and where he was going. That was fine, because Harry wasn't going to be here when that someone arrived.

A minute later one of the elevator doors opened and a young Auror dressed in Muggle business clothing stepped out and scanned the lobby. He walked almost to the entrance, then walked over to each of the doors leading down side corridors and cast a spell over each one. He then fished a small phone from his pocket (it was one from the Weasley electronic store) and spoke into it.

"No one down here," he said, "and none of the side doors have been tampered with. Whoever came in must've gone back out."

"Alright," a soft voice replied. "Come back up and continue your search, Hoskins."

"Acknowledged," Hoskins said, then dropped the phone in a pocket and re-entered the elevator, which had remained open. The elevator doors slid closed.

Harry took off his Invisibility Cloak, smiling. He'd been right to wait until someone checked before he broke the magical lock on the door that led to the Floo connection to his private vestibule. If he knew Malfoy's logic, he would probably consider that Floo connection to be a business to residence link, since it was inside the TBC Building. The corridor, however, was not being rented by his business; it was part of the building floor space that was considered a common area, like the lobby. The room itself was little more than a crawlspace, magically extended to the size of a small room. No one but a wizard could see the door leading to that room, though Malfoy probably hadn't checked for that bit of magic, minor as it was.

There was a magic lock on the door leading to the corridor where his special room was, and Harry expected that the charm would alert the caster if it was broken. A quick detection spell told him that there were no extra spells on the door itself, or the doorway. That was good; it meant he could try a device he and Dean had been working on in his lab a few months ago, before he moved everything to his personal lab. Reaching into his mokeskin pouch, he pulled out a small cylinder about six inches long and a quarter-inch in diameter. He placed one end against the door and quietly said, "Beam me up, Scotty," then pushed the cylinder through the door.

When the cylinder was about halfway through he stopped and said, "Energize!" and let go of the cylinder. The tip of the cylinder began to expand, becoming a door almost as large as the one he's pushed the rod through. Harry opened the door, seeing a short corridor with another door at the other end. He stepped through the doorway, closing the door behind him, then stepped out the other side, now on the other side of the warded door.

Harry closed the door he'd just stepped through and said, "Energize" again. The door shrunk back to a small cylinder, and Harry pulled the cylinder out of the door and dropped it back into his pouch. Whistling the theme to "Star Trek," he strolled down the corridor to the door where his special Floo connection was located, a door marked "Building Maintenance" for anyone who could see the door and read what was written on it.

Harry tapped the door with his wand, saying "Alohomora," then grasped the door handle, giving it a moment to recognize him. The door clicked and he pulled it open, stepping inside. Once inside, he pointed his wand at the doorknob and said, "Colloportus Malfoy!" to magically password lock the door. "Let's see Malfoy figure that password out," he muttered to himself, grinning.

Taking a pinch of Floo powder from the mantle, Harry tossed it into the fireplace saying, "Potter-Evans-Verres private residence!" and stepped into the green flames. He immediately began spinning and a moment later stepped out of the fireplace in the antechamber to his and Hermione's apartment. From here he could make sure no one could get into his apartment until he reactivated this Floo connection.

Harry turned the Floo damper to the off position, then took out his wand and cast the spell disconnecting this fireplace from any other connection. It took almost a quarter-minute to speak all of the words, but at the end he was rewarded with a dull green flash from the fireplace. It was completely unhooked from any other Floo now, and just another normal fireplace.

That left everyone unable to get inside his apartment, but also him stranded inside, unable to get out. Well, almost, Harry smiled to himself. He walked down the corridor from the anteroom to the apartment proper, meaning to continue on through to an outside window. But, staring at his comfortable chair, Harry felt a sudden weariness come over him, and he dropped into the chair, rubbing his face tiredly.

This dancing around with Malfoy was getting tiresome. It had gone on for years, with Harry mostly a step ahead of Malfoy's plots but only just ahead — he never had any long stretches of time to deal with things he wanted to work on, like figuring out what the Source of Magic was and how it worked. He and Monroe had been that close to finding Slytherin's Horcrux, which would be a truly amazing discovery and could be a significant source of forgotten spells from over eight hundred years ago, the time of the Founders. Properly controlled and warded, Harry was sure they could keep Salazar Slytherin from possessing anyone. But surely the Ministry wouldn't see things that way, if they found out about it!

And that probably included Hermione, Harry considered. Even though she was a lot more worldly now than she'd been when she first came to Hogwarts, she still thought of herself as Good and things like Horcruxes and Dark magic as Bad. And never the twain shall meet…

Harry sighed, slapped his knees and stood. He needed to put in an appearance at his business office, get that situation controlled, then get back with all haste to Hogwarts and Monroe, who for all Harry knew was still standing outside the Room of Requirement trying to get in.

Pushing that admittedly humorous situation from his mind, Harry made his way to the laundry room, a spacious, well-lighted room equipped with a top-of-the-line Muggle style washer and dryer. While there were several spells that magically cleaned and pressed clothing, they tended to feel better if they went through an actual wash-dry cycle. Harry stared into the window behind the dryer: a nice pastoral landscape was visible "outside" it, although window was actually inside the building, well away from any outside walls.

This window, however, had an activation spell on it that allowed Harry to cause it to open, revealing a small walkway beyond that led to an actual outside window near the top of the TBC Building. This was his and Hermione's alternate escape path should someone manage to make it inside their apartment with numbers too great to fight and in the eventuality they couldn't get to their safe room. Harry closed the faux window behind him, locking it with the Colloportus Malfoy spell and password, and walked the forty or so yards to the real outside window of the building.

He pulled the broom out of the pouch once again, then realized he might have grabbed a couple of refills for the rocket cylinders while he was at home. Well, it probably wouldn't matter — he couldn't use either the rockets or the broom itself to get back inside Hogwarts; the rockets were pants for precision flying. Harry charmed the window to open for ten seconds, then close again, and leaped off the ledge into empty air, hoping and expecting that Malfoy's Aurors hadn't cast any anti-flying spells around the building.

They hadn't. The broom flew straight and true, taking Harry to the top of the next building, where he would make his way down to the street and walk back over to the TBC Building, this time waiting for the Aurors to find him in the lobby.

=ooo=

Ginny Thomas watched, a carefully neutral expression on her face, as a dozen Aurors meticulously took apart her and Harry's office spaces. Another dozen Aurors were going over the rest of the office space that took up the majority of this floor of the TBC Building. They had been at it for nearly an hour now, and as expected there had been no incriminating discoveries. Did they not realize that Muggles worked in this space as well? Maybe they did—Malfoy had probably ordered checks for anything that might violate the secrecy laws as well as prohibitions against owning Dark books or artifacts.

Dean was with another detail of Aurors that had found Harry's lab area — an area that was now mostly empty of any magical items; Harry had not wanted to take the chance they would show up one day (like today) and arbitrarily declare something he was working on Dark, forcing an investigation in front of the Wizengamot. It was unlikely that the Wizengamot would rule in Malfoy's favor unless the item was clearly Dark, but Harry hadn't wanted to give Malfoy the satisfaction of hauling him before the wizards' court in the first place.

Malfoy himself was standing nearby, overseeing the search. His expression, too, was carefully neutral, but Ginny thought she saw his lips quirk every so often when one of his minions (as Harry called them), Crabbe or Goyle, would whisper something to him. Ginny pretended to ignore Malfoy, but watched him from a corner of her eye. She wished Harry would show up and take charge of this mess! She never liked dealing with Malfoy; he made her uneasy on some indescribable, visceral level.

And, there was someone she very much wanted to talk to, to tell him to stop fanning the flames between Harry and Malfoy, before he started a fire that no one could put out.

A dozen feet from Ginny Thomas, Draco stood watching his men systematically take apart Potter's business operation, piece by piece. At the rate they were progressing, the entire office space would be carefully checked for Dark magic within another two hours, and if there were any secret entrances to the Potters' private residence his men would find it. That, of course, was the real reason they were here — Draco didn't expect to find anything worthwhile in Potter's business offices — that would be pure sloppiness on Potter's part. His apartment, on the other hand, took up three whole floors of space in this building — that was plenty of room to hide loads of Dark materials in!

"Nothing in the lab so far," Vincent Crabbe reported, speaking so softly Draco barely heard him. "They think there's at least one more lab on this floor, they'll let us know when they find it. So far Thomas still isn't cooperating with them."

"He won't," Draco murmured in reply. "He's Potter's man through and through."

A young Auror — Hoskins, Draco finally recalled his name — came up to them. "Someone has entered the lobby again, sir. Shall I check it out?"

"That's why I had you cast the detection spell, Hoskins," Draco said, impatiently. "Yes, go check it out."

Crabbe didn't quite hide a smirk as the young Auror ran off toward the elevators. "He hasn't quite got the hang of working for you yet, has he?"

"I hear I'm an acquired taste," Malfoy drawled, loud enough that Ginny heard him.

Yeah, you'd be an acquired taste, Ginny thought. Just like at Fortescue's if they started serving dung-flavored ice cream. She'd seen the young Auror assigned to lobby duty run for the elevator, and her fingers were crossed that Harry was in the lobby. Come on, come on, she thought, anxious to be gone from this place. She had things to do and people of her own to ream out…

A couple of minutes later the elevator doors opened and Ginny breathed a sigh of relief — Harry had finally shown up. He had on his best outraged businessman face, striding up to Malfoy without so much as a glance at anyone else on the floor. "Malfoy, what the hell are you doing conducting a search of my business offices on the weekend?"

Malfoy gave his long-time adversary an obtuse look. "What, would you prefer I show up while you have an office full of Muggles and start Obliviating them before I cut them loose? If anything I was doing you a favor, Potter."

"Right," Harry shook his head disgustedly, still playing the part. "You haven't found a damned thing, have you?"

"We won't know until the final reports are in," Malfoy shrugged. "You might as well settle in for a bit, my teams are being very thorough."

"I'm sure they are." Harry walked away from Malfoy and up to Ginny. "Sorry this had to happen to you," he said in a low voice. "Is Dean here?"

Ginny nodded. "He went with one of the teams to check out your labs. I haven't heard about any 'findings' so far. We you busy? I thought you'd be here before now."

"I was out of town," Harry said. "Monroe and I took a trip up to Hogwarts today, to have a look at the Chamber of Secrets. We found some pretty interesting things going on down there with Slytherin's statue." Harry's eyes flicked over to see Malfoy glancing their way. "Sorry, tell you more later. I can take over here if you need to go."

"I do have some stuff to do before Dean comes home," Ginny agreed. "Oh." She seemed to suddenly realize something. "You were with Monroe? Where's he at now?"

"He's doing some — research for me," Harry said, vaguely. "He'll be okay for a while." Assuming he ever got inside the Room of Requirement, Harry added to himself. "You go on, take care of business. We'll be okay here. I'll send Dean home as soon as they're done with him."

"Okay," Ginny said, and went to her desk and took her purse out of one of the drawers. "If you're sure you don't need me…" she said, giving Harry one last chance to have her stay.

"Go," Harry said, taking her arm and walking with her to the elevator. The young Auror, Hoskins, who'd accompanied Harry back from the lobby, moved warily in front of the elevators as they approached.

"Erm, I'm supposed to escort anyone leaving out of the building," he explained. "Head's orders."

Harry turned to Ginny. "I'll leave you in Mr. Hoskins' capable hands, then," he said, with a small bow. Ginny smiled at him, then her face went neutral as she followed the young Auror into the elevator.

As the doors closed, Harry sighed and walked back to Malfoy. They both stood silently for some time before Harry softly muttered, "There are no secret entrances to my apartment."

"We'll just see about that," Malfoy muttered, equally softly.

=ooo=

James Monroe turned away from the window Harry had just leapt from. There had been no scream and crash, so Harry's broom contraption must have worked. Hopefully he would be back soon.

He faced the blank wall. His task now was to get inside the Room of Requirement — which he'd never heard of until a few minutes ago, and for which he had rather imprecise instructions on how to get inside; you had to need to get in, apparently. What had Harry said? You think what you need, and walk back and forth in front of this wall three times doing that.

Yeah, that was clear as mud, Monroe thought, unhappily.

But he had no choice but to try it. He certainly didn't want to be caught standing here if a student or — Merlin forbid — a prefect or teacher walked by. He'd have some explaining to do, especially since Harry was no longer around to run interference with Headmaster Longbottom. It would be difficult to explain why Harry left and he had stayed; he certainly wasn't going to tell Longbottom he was trying to get into the Room of Requirement!

"So," Monroe said softly, looking at the wall. "Let's see what you've got for me." But what did he need? Originally he and Harry were coming here so Harry could tell him in private what he and the huge Slytherin statue had talked about — in Parseltongue — when they were in the Chamber of Secrets. Is that what he needed, then? And how could the room give him that if Harry wasn't even here?

Well, he had to give it a try. Monroe concentrated on the phrase, I need to know what Harry and the Slytherin statue talked about, I need to know what Harry and the Slytherin statue talked about. He repeated that phrase over and over in his head as he paced back and forth in front of the blank wall.

On his third pass, Monroe stopped suddenly as a low, grinding noise began to cause the floor to slightly vibrate. He spun around to face the blank wall once again, only to find it was no longer a blank wall.

A large, polished oak door had appeared in the wall, complete with brass hinges and a huge brass handle for a doorknob. Monroe stared at it in wonderment for some time before realizing he should clear out of the corridor. He grasped the handle and pulled the door open, stepping inside and pulling it closed behind him.

The room inside was not what he'd expected — but then, it was hard to know what he should expect, never having been here before. Dimly lit by low-burning braziers on the walls, Monroe could barely make out four figures standing in a semicircle before him. "Who's there?" he asked, hesitantly, wondering if he had walked in while someone else was in the room. But there was no reply, and as he continued slowly forward, Monroe saw that the four figures were actually four man-sized statues.

The statue on his left was of a tall, stately woman in a long, flowing dress, with the image of a diadem on her head. Next to her was an even taller man, imposing looking, with shoulder-length hair and a full beard, his hands resting on the hilt of a long sword. The next statue Monroe recognized as Salazar Slytherin; he looked quite similar to the statue in the Chamber of Secrets except that this statue wore a pendant marked with a stylized "S" around its neck. The final statue was of a shorter, stout woman with a pleasant face, holding a cup in her hands. Looking back and forth at the four statues staring at him, Monroe murmured "What do we have here?" Why would the Room of Requirement show him this, a group of the four Founders?

"A question," a soft voice suddenly spoke. Monroe turned to his left, where the voice had come from. There was no one behind him, but the woman with the diadem on her forehead seemed to be staring directly at him now.

"Did someone speak?" Monroe said aloud, watching the statue carefully. If these statues were like the one of Slytherin in the Chamber, perhaps he had found something quite unusual here. There were dozens of talking portraits scattered throughout the castle; indeed, many wizarding families had at least one or two in their houses. He remembered seeing a portrait of Albus Dumbledore in Harry's apartment once, though the old man was sleeping at the time.

But talking statues? He'd never seen anything like them anywhere, either in Wizarding Britain or in America when he was at the Salem Institute. "Can you speak?" he asked the statues again.

"We can." The statue of the tall, imposing man spoke, though there was no movement of its mouth. "We are…the Founders of Hogwarts," the voice went on, slowly. "Ravenclaw…Hufflepuff…Slytherin… and Gryffindor."

"I think I only needed to speak to Slytherin," Monroe told the voice. He wasn't sure if he was hearing the voice in his ears or his head. "Why are all four of you here?"

"We are the Founders," the voice rumbled, as if that should answer the question.

Monroe decided to hit the nail on the head right off. "Are you Horcruxes?"

"We are the Founders," Gryffindor's voice said again.

"We are not Horcruxes," the stately woman's voice spoke right after Gryffindor. "We are the spirits of the Founders, preserved forever in the very stones of the castle we built."

"I don't want to nitpick," Monroe said, diffidently. "But that could be considered the definition of a Horcrux. It is a fragment of a wizard's soul stored in an object, animate or inanimate, to anchor that soul to this existence."

"That definition is imprecise and incomplete," Ravenclaw's voice spoke, giving Monroe the impression she was being imperious. The Greek wizard who created the spell believed it could only be accomplished by murder, a crime so heinous that it would cleave a soul asunder. We did no murder when we preserved ourselves thus."

"When did you do this?" Monroe asked, feeling a sense of excitement beginning to build inside him.

A new voice spoke, a woman's voice, warm and caring. "The castle was barely raised when we chose to make ourselves part of it forever, to watch over the children and those charged with their education.'

"We have seen much in the time that has passed since then," Slytherin's voice spoke at last, a thin, hollow voice, but at least it spoke in English rather than Parseltongue, Monroe thought, relieved. "Much has changed."

"Indeed it has," Monroe agreed. "Much has been learned since those days, and much has been lost."

"Aye," Ravenclaw's voice agreed. "There is much that is no longer taught to our students, much they must discover on their own in the world."

"Perhaps," Monroe murmured. "But there are some things we can no longer learn — things that have been lost to the Interdict of Merlin."

"Merlin," Slytherin's thin, hollow voice repeated. "He was a very bright boy, as I recall. A bit taken with the Muggles, perhaps more so than necessary, considering their place in our world, but he was in my House. What is this 'Interdict' you speak of?"

"It is a spell he cast just before his death," Monroe answered. "It prevents powerful spells from being learned by any wizard except directly from another wizard. All the ancient powerful spells of your time can no longer be learned because of it."

"Why would any wizard do such a thing?" Ravenclaw's voice betrayed the shock her living mind might have felt, if she were still alive. "Wisdom is wizardkind's greatest treasure and its greatest gift!"

"Merlin may have felt caution was more important," Monroe said. "He thought that wizards would someday destroy the world as their magic became more and more powerful."

"We had hoped other schools like ours would be established one day by our students," the voice of Hufflepuff said, wistfully. "Has that been accomplished?"

"There are other schools," Monroe replied. "A few in Europe, three in a new land called the Americas, and several more in the East. But there are none as great as Hogwarts," he added. "You can thank the Interdict for that."

"Unacceptable," Gryffindor growled. "We built Hogwarts as a beacon of light in the darkness — it should not be the best example of our craft, but the first one."

"I agree," Monroe said. "Perhaps the Founders can help me begin that dream anew."

"What can we do?" Slytherin rasped. "We are but shadows within the walls of the castle we built!"

"You may be able to help more than you know, if you remember the spells that helped you raise Hogwarts, for example," Monroe answered. "You can teach them to me, and I can teach them to the students of Hogwarts. From there we can spread them across the world, to other wizards who have the same dream you had for your school."

There was silence for a time. Then, "We can," the voice of Ravenclaw spoke. "But there is much for only one man to learn."

"Well, I hope to have some help show up shortly," Monroe said. "Between the two of us we should be able to remember quite a bit."

=ooo=

Once Ginny was outside the wards the Aurors had placed in the TBC Building she Apparated to northwest London, to an older neighborhood she visited infrequently these days. She arrived on the edge of an unkempt square, unnoticed by the inhabitants of the neighborhood, and she stood still for several moments, seeming to stare not so much at the buildings in her line of sight as between them. Which indeed she was, as she was looking at a building that almost no one living today could see. She reached up and drew the shawl draped over her shoulders up over her head, then threw the bottom edge of it across her lower face. No use giving anyone peering out of their windows a chance to see who she was. That, and weather was cold this evening, with an icy breeze nipping at her nose and ears.

She walked across the road surrounding the square and across the pavement in front of a row of shabby-looking houses. If anyone had been looking out of their windows just then, they would have seen a shawl-draped woman walking across the lawn between two houses, then seem to disappear between them, which might have appeared odd to some, though most people would shrug and dismiss the idea from their minds.

But Ginny had not walked between the houses; she was now on the front steps of number four, Grimmauld Place, and she reached up and tapped the doorknocker, a bronze lion's head, three times. After several seconds of silence, the door creaked slowly open. A small house-elf stared up smilingly at her. "Welcome, Miss Ginny," Jumpy said to her, bowing deeply. "You are here to see Master Ron and Mistress Luna, you are?"

Ginny nodded, "Yes," she said, a bit shortly. She was here to see Ron, mostly, but there was no use in upsetting Luna if she didn't have to. "May I come in?"

"Of course, of course," the elf stepped back, allowing her entry to the Weasleys' home. Not much had changed in the long hallway of this old home. Portraits of the Weasley family hung along the walls and the golden chandelier still hung from the ceiling, casting its feeble light down the hall. At the back of the ground floor was the inaptly named "front," or living room, and Jumpy padded off to announce her arrival. Ginny could hear him muttering her name to whoever was in the room.

A moment later Luna appeared, smiling brightly as she saw Ginny. "Hello!" she said happily. "I'm so happy to see you again, Ginny. Why don't you come into the parlor?"

"Hello, Luna." Ginny was smiling as well in spite of her unpleasant mood. There was no reason to take out her anger against Ron on Luna, though, so she followed her sister-in-law into the living room and sat down in the chair Luna offered to her.

"Jumpy, would you bring us some tea, please?" Luna asked the young house-elf waiting in the doorway. "I'm sure Ginny would like something while she's here."

"Yes, Mistress," Jumpy bowed deeply again and disappeared down the basement steps where the kitchen was located.

"How have you been?" Luna asked Ginny as they waited. "I haven't seen you for some time now at the shop."

"I've been busy," Ginny said, tiredly. "I just came from work — Malfoy got a wild hair up his arse and decided to search Harry's business because of suspected Dark items being held there."

"Oh, dear," Luna looked concerned. "I hope there's nothing to find there!"

"There's not," Ginny said, smiling. Luna always took such things so seriously. "Malfoy's just harassing Harry, as usual."

"Oh, that's too bad," Luna said, commiserating with her. "I like it when Harry visits the shop — he always seems to liven things up around there."

"He does," Ginny agreed, emphatically. Her brothers still talked about Harry and Monroe's duel — and of course Monroe's arrival in Wizarding London had shaken up more than just the Weasleys.

But her reason for visiting was to set things straight with Ron, not to exchange banalities with Luna. She was tired of him going to Malfoy with the things she talked about with him. Even if the letters were anonymous (and they undoubtedly were) she could tell where Malfoy was getting his information from. She hoped Ron would get home soon so she could get this over with.

Jumpy returned, laboriously carrying a tea set over his head, with curls of steam rising from the teapot. He set it down on a table in front of Luna and Ginny, and began to pick up the tea kettle when Luna stopped him. "I'll take care of it, Jumpy," she said, pleasantly. "Will you go down and make sure supper will be ready when Ron gets home?"

"Yes, Mistress," Jumpy nodded obediently, then nodded to Ginny and scuttled off to the basement again.

"I like it when Jumpy calls me 'Mistress,'" Luna said conversationally as she poured the tea into her and Ginny's cups. "It sounds so formal and elegant, doesn't it?"

"It was nice of Harry to buy this house for our family," Ginny replied, though she didn't care too much for the old place itself, or that Luna seemed to enjoy living here. "I think Ron was the only one of us…brave enough to live here." She might have said stupid enough but that wouldn't have been appropriate in front of Luna; her mother Molly had never been sure they'd gotten all the pests out of this old, decrepit building. All the buildings in this square seemed odd for one reason or another — they had never figured out why there was no number twelve, for example.

"Oh, did I never tell you?" Luna looked surprised (which she almost always did anyway, with her protuberant eyes) "After Ron and I got married I insisted that we live here. He had told me about all the fascinating creatures your family had found here when Harry bought the house for his family, and I wanted to write a book on the types of creatures one might find in old houses like this."

"I didn't know that!" Ginny said, surprised. Luna handed her a cup of tea with the amount of sugar and cream that Ginny liked. "Thank you," she said, waiting for Luna to pick up her own cup before sipping from hers. "Mmm, very nice," Ginny lifted the cup toward Luna, who smiled agreeably. "So have you been working on that book, then?" she asked, curiously.

"Oh, off and on," Luna said, vaguely. "It's difficult to find the time while I'm working at the shop and taking care of Ron."

Ginny's expression darkened. "Maybe you should make time for yourself, Luna. Ron can fend for himself if he needs to."

"I know," Luna agreed. "But I've always had someone to take care of, it feels so natural to me. Daddy was lost when Mummy died; I began helping him with the Quibbler by writing articles for him from time to time, until I began going to Hogwarts."

"I remember hearing about some of them," Ginny agreed, sipping at her tea. It was hard to keep her foul mood intact while she was around Luna, but if Ron didn't show up soon all of her anger at him was going to dissipate before she could ream him out properly for his transgressions. "Do you know when Ron's going to be home, by the way?"

"He didn't say, exactly," Luna said, unconcerned. "What are you upset with him about?"

Ginny blinked, a bit surprised at the question. Luna always did have a penchant for asking blunt questions in a completely straightforward, innocent way. "I — didn't say I was upset with him, did I?"

"No," Luna replied, "but when you come over you're usually upset, either with Dean, Ron, or one of your other brothers, and since you haven't begun complaining about him and asked about him just now, it seems like he's the one you're upset with."

"Hmm," Ginny said, setting down her tea. "Well, I'd rather discuss it with him directly, Luna, but I am upset with him."

"It's about Harry, isn't it?" Luna asked, then picked up a small tray from the tea tray. "Scone?"

Ginny silently accepted a scone from the tray offered her, wondering how much Ron had told her of their conversations. Before she could ask, however, Luna spoke. "It's too bad that Ron and Harry don't get on as well as they should. I suppose that's because Harry married Ron's first love."

"Did he tell you that?" Ginny demanded, becoming more angry at Ron than ever now. Why would he tell his wife something like that?!

"Oh, no," Luna shook her long blond locks. "Ron loves me very much, he would never say something like that to me. But it's as plain as the nose on his face how he feels about Hermione."

That wasn't something Ginny was going to deny. But her real interest was — "So, what has he told you about Harry lately?"

Luna chuckled. "Oh, he's said that Harry and his friend James Monroe are planning to break the Interdict of Merlin, so that all the ancient spells can be learned again, and how that could cause a magical World War that will destroy everything, just like Merlin predicted eight hundred years ago. He's said that they want to bring about something called a Magical Sanctuary —"

"It's called the Magical Singulariy," Ginny put in.

"Oh yes, that then," Luna said. "Ron said that if that happened we'd all be sucked into the Source of Magic, whatever that is, and disappear. He's also said Harry plans to prove that souls don't exist, so that Horcruxes can't really exist, either."

"Ron's told you about Horcruxes?" Ginny asked, breathlessly.

"Oh, no, of course not. We learned all about them when I was in Ravenclaw," Luna replied. "We just never told Professor Flitwick or any of the other teachers what we knew about them — Flitwick always looked very nervous whenever one of the upper years would make an oblique reference to them." Ginny smiled at that, at the same time wondering how many students in the other Houses knew. Harry had said Dumbledore thought it was a deep, dark secret that very few knew of, and no one at Hogwarts was supposed to know, not even the other teachers. The old headmaster might have been quite surprised to learn just how many Ravenclaws knew about them. "Of course we never said anything to the other houses — the Slytherins would have immediately begun plotting to make their own, and the Gryffindors and Hufflepuffs would always have been trying to find them and destroy them."

"I guess that's true," Ginny admitted. "So… did Ron ever tell anyone else about what he thought Harry was doing? Not," she hastened to add, "that I think he was doing those things, but that Ron thought so."

Luna laughed softly. "Ron can be such a hot-head…well, I'm sure you already know that, of course, but he knows how well-liked Harry is in the Wizarding community — the Boy-Who-Made-Good, I suppose we could call him now, with his big ivory tower and employing so many people, both Muggle and wizard."

"Harry has enemies, too," Ginny pointed out. "Malfoy being the biggest one at the moment."

Luna nodded. "And there are probably wizards who dislike him as well, for whatever reasons they think are valid. Ron tells me there are shopkeepers in Diagon Alley who resent him for keeping the rents there so high. I'm not sure why they think that, though, since the Ministry controls rental rates in Diagon Alley."

"Hmm, that's right," Ginny agreed, remembering that now. "I'd forgotten about that. But has Ron been telling other people about these things, or writing them down?"

"I think the only time I see Ron with a quill in his hand is when he's writing down his hours at the shop," Luna smiled. "Ron's never been much for writing down things."

"So you don't think he's been writing to the Ministry about what Harry and Monroe have been doing?" Ginny pressed.

"The Ministry?" Luna's already protuberant eyes grew even wider. "Oh dear me, no — he hates Draco Malfoy, even more than he ever disliked Harry. I suppose the poor dear is just frustrated that Harry is so much more successful than he is." Luna took her last sip of tea, then swirled her cup and poured the last bit of tea into her saucer. She glanced into the cup, reading the leaves. "My immediate future looks good," she said, dreamily, "I'm not too sure how things will go after that." She reached out for Ginny's cup. "Would you like me to read your fortune?"

Ginny shook her head, setting her cup down only half-finished. "I think I should be going — Dean will be home in a little while, I hope, and I should get ready for him, he'll be tired after spending the last few hours watching Malfoy's men search our offices."

"Very thoughtful of you, dear," Luna reached over and patted Ginny on the arm. "I'll tell Ron you visited, he always likes it when you visit, even if you yell at him." Both women stood and Luna walked with Ginny down the hallway to the front door. "Nice to see you again, dear," she said, giving Ginny a small hug. "Why don't you come by sometime when you don't feel like yelling at Ron. We can have dinner."

"That sounds nice," Ginny smiled, then threw her shawl over her head once again and walked down the steps to the front walk. From there she Apparated directly to the front door of her apartment building, went inside and walked up to her apartment and let herself in.

"Dean?" she called as she entered. There was no reply. She took her phone out of her purse, checking for any texts or voice messages he might have left her. Nothing there, either. She would have to hurry if she wanted everything ready for when he returned.

Ginny walked into their bedroom and up to the small writing desk she kept in there for writing family and friends. She sat down at the desk, closed her eyes and seemed to meditate for several seconds. An expression of cold, vacant detachment came over her features, and she took out her wand, pointing it at a small drawer in the desk. The drawer slid halfway open, and a piece of parchment stationery and a Quotes Quill from Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes, one that Ron had enchanted and had never been used, floated out of the drawer, coming to rest on the desk in front of her.

Ginny began speaking in a low, inflectionless voice, and the quill jumped up on its tip and began to write.

To Head Auror Malfoy,

Once again I feel I must let you know of Harry Potter's activities, activities that are undermining the safety of Wizarding Britain.

The details are sparse, but Potter has been to Hogwarts to visit the Chamber of Secrets, with the permission of Headmaster Longbottom. He may have discovered something about the statue of Salazar Slytherin that ties in with his efforts to undermine the rule of the Ministry and Wizengamot. As Head Auror, it is your duty to stop him from destroying our government and our way of life. As a concerned citizen, I urge you with all speed to prevent him from doing this.

Ginny left the letter unsigned, as usual. A parchment envelope floated out of a slot and dropped to the desk next to the letter. Ginny spoke Malfoy's name as the address and the letter folded and inserted itself into the envelope. Ginny looked at the window and it slid open of its own accord, just as an owl from the London Owl-Post office flew in the window, landing on the desk and hooting at her impatiently.

The letter lifted in the air and slid into the mail pouch attached to the owl's leg. A Sickle floated out of another drawer in the desk and disappeared into the coin pouch on the owl's other leg, and it spread its wings and immediately flew out of the window.

Her expression still vacant, Ginny undressed and put on her nightgown, then slipped into bed and closed her eyes.

Chapter 20: A Conversation with the Founders Pt 2

Updated 9/15/2012

=ooo=

Harry stepped into the Room of Requirement, staring at the four statues of the Founders that faced him in a semicircle as he moved to the center of the room. He recognized each of them in turn: the tall, elegant figure of Rowena Ravenclaw; the broad, imposing Godric Gryffindor; the brooding Salazar Slytherin and the friendly, matronly Helga Hufflepuff.

There was a table in front of the four statues, with several books lying open on it. Glancing down at them, Harry read only nonsense words. The spells in this book were protected by the Interdict of Merlin. Harry glanced back at Monroe, who had conjured another chair near the door and sat down again, content to let Harry talk to the Founders on his own, then looked at the four statues again. "You are the Founders, I take it," he said.

"We are the Founders," the voice of Rowena Ravenclaw answered. "You are James Monroe's friend Harry Potter. We remember you from the days you attended Hogwarts."

"You do?" Harry smiled in surprise. "I'm sorry I didn't have a chance to meet you then. I didn't realize I made that much of an impression here at Hogwarts."

"Your humility does not seem genuine," another woman's voice, Helga Hufflepuff, spoke. "You achieved many great successes while within our walls. We would be unsurprised to learn you achieved much success outside them as well."

"I have," Harry agreed. "You're right, and I apologize for my disingenuousness. There are things I have failed to achieve, however, which is what brings me here to talk with you."

"The Interdict of Merlin," a thin, hollow voice spoke, and Harry recognized it as Salazar Slytherin. "Your friend Monroe has spoken to us of it. Merlin was our student, yet he dared presume himself to be greater than us!"

"He was greater," Harry argued. "He united the wizards in a common cause, bringing them together in order that they might guide and govern themselves by law rather than by rule of might. Your greatest contribution to wizardkind, beyond this castle, was to divide students against one another by sorting them into four Houses named after yourselves."

"That was not our intention!" the voice of Godric Gryffindor spoke forcefully. "We wished students to benefit from their natural strengths, and that is best encouraged by like minds!"

"And yet much knowledge has been lost over the years," Harry pointed out. "Even between those of 'like minds,' because of the Interdict."

"We wish to remedy that," the voice of Ravenclaw answered.

"I do as well," Harry concurred.

"We have been reading spells from these books that your friend Monroe has been showing us," Helga Hufflepuff said. "He will be able to teach them to others, and they will be able to teach them as well."

"That will help," Harry agreed. "But it would be better if we found a way to break the Interdict altogether. Then magical knowledge could not fall into obscurity because no living person knows a spell by heart — spells could be relearned from books, which is what books were meant to be used for in the first place."

"The Ministry probably won't like that," Monroe spoke from behind Harry.

Harry replied over his shoulder. "That didn't stop you from learning Indicted-protected spells from the Founders, did it?"

"No, it didn't," Monroe agreed. "But then, I'm a knowledge junkie."

"So am I," Harry turned back to the Founders. "Can you help me break the Interdict?"

"We do not know the spell Merlin used," Ravenclaw answered. "And we cannot cast spells ourselves; our minds are preserved within these walls, but magic is created by living beings, not stones."

"I understand that," Harry said. He didn't think it was true, but he wasn't going to argue the point. "But you can still help me and James think through what the Interdict must do to prevent written spells from being comprehended unless they have passed from one mind to another."

"We can try," Ravenclaw answered, and the voices of the other statues murmured their assent.

Harry picked up a book. "Then perhaps we should return to these spells," he said. "Maybe they will show us a way to defeat the Interdict."

=ooo=

"Well, well," Fred Weasley said scornfully. "Look what the Kneazle dragged in."

Draco Malfoy walked up to where Weasley was seated, in front of the main counter at Weasleys' Wizard Wheezes. He'd been bound securely to the chair, his arms pinned to his sides with heavy ropes and his wand confiscated, but he still wore a sneer of disdain when he saw the Head Auror. They would see how long that sneer would last, Draco thought, when his Aurors began questioning him about the letters that had been coming into their offices.

"What have you done with my brothers?" Fred demanded, looking up at the Head Auror. Malfoy ignored the question and nodded to Vincent Crabbe, who then stepped in front of Weasley, blocking his view of Maloy

"You know why we're here," Crabbe said in his surprisingly soft voice, not asking a question but stating it as a fact.

"No clue," Fred replied. "Unless you can't sleep. For that I can recommend a good sleeping potion, one that will give you very interesting dreams. And where are my brothers?"

"Your brothers are being questioned separately," Crabbe answered. "As are your wives. And I think you do know why we're here — it's about those letters to the Ministry written with a Weasley-charmed quill," he continued. "They've given us some pretty interesting information on what Harry Potter's been doing for the past few months. It looks like your brother Ron's been sending them to us."

"Pffft," Fred snorted. "Ron's no friend of Harry's but he'd never rat him out, even if whatever's in those letters happened to be true, which I doubt."

Crabbe smiled. "So you know what's in those letters?"

"Nope," Fred shook his head. "But I know Harry."

"Yeah, that's what we're hoping," Crabbe said. He pulled a small vial from his robe. "Can you guess what this is?"

Fred's eyes narrowed. "Veritaserum," he muttered. "But you can't give me that without my permission unless I'm charged with a crime." He tried to look around Crabbe. "Are you charging me with a crime, Malfoy?"

"Not at the moment," Malfoy replied casually. "But if you don't agree to take the Veritaserum then we'll charge you with obstruction of justice, begin a full-scale investigation into you and your family's activities, and give you the Veritaserum anyway."

"Nicely played," Fred said sarcastically. "I suppose I should remind you at this point of the Mental Privacy Act of 2012." It was the same law Ginny had referred to although she had used the legal description rather than the popular name. "If you can't charge me with anything because of what I say under Veritaserum, it's illegal for you to keep any records of our conversation beyond your own memories."

"I'm acquainted with the law," Malfoy said evenly. Pretty much everyone being questioned under Veritaserum referred to it these days. "But you'd better hope we find out you're squeaky clean when we start questioning you."

"Bring it on, then," Fred said.

Malfoy gestured at Crabbe to continue. The big man took out his wand and conjured a glass filled with water, then uncorked the vial and let three drops of the liquid inside fall into the glass. He held the glass up to Weasley's lips, being careful not to spill any. "Let me know when he's ready," the big Auror said to his assistant, then stepped back to wait for the potion to reach full effectiveness. He glanced back at Malfoy, who nodded and left to check on the other interrogations going on. Once they had completed the questioning, Malfoy would gather his men to compare the results. And from there, he hoped, he would have enough evidence to bring in Potter for trying to break the Interdict, a change to the balance of wizarding power that could have far-reaching implications, not just in Britain, but around the world.

=ooo=

"No, I don't know anything about letters sent to the Ministry," Luna Weasley replied, with a vaguely pleasant smile at the Auror questioning her. "I wouldn't think my husband would, either. He doesn't like Harry very much, but I can't imagine Ron wanting to inform on him to the Ministry; if there was anything to expose I would have known and suggested my father interview him for The Quibbler. My father appreciates my insights in these matters, you see."

Auror Willem Hoskins stared at the woman bound to the chair in the back office of Weasleys' Wireless Wonderland, where they had taken the three women for separate questioning. He'd been warned that she could a bit — off. That warning was proving to be true.

"Alright, then," Hoskins said, trying to make himself sound stern and authoritative. "We're going to question you under Veritaserum —"

"Oh, that should be interesting," Luna smiled brightly. "I've never tried that before."

"Do you understand that if you refuse we will charge you with obstruction of justice and —"

"But why would I refuse?" Luna asked, her already protuberant eyes growing even larger in surprise.

"Er, you might be lying?" Hoskins suggested.

"Well, I suppose that is possible, but I have no reason to lie," Luna said. "You know, it would be fun to try an experiment."

"An experiment?" Hoskins said, confused. "What kind of experiment?"

"You ask me the questions you were going to ask before giving me the Veritaserum," Luna suggested, "and then ask them again afterwards, and we'll see if my answers change."

Hoskins blinked in utter confusion. That might actually be interesting in some ways —

The junior Auror assisting in this interview gave him a disapproving look. "Hoskins, are you really thinking of doing that?! I want to go home and get some sleep, not conduct some experiment that a potential criminal wants us to do!"

"I'd like to get some sleep, too," Luna said matter-of-factly. "But it looks like the Ministry had different plans for all of us."

"She's right about that, Daniels," Hoskins said to his partner.

"Just give her the Verita and let's get on with this," Daniels, though still a junior Auror, was Hoskins' senior at the Ministry by about 5 minutes (they'd both graduated from the same Auror Training class) growled. Hoskins nodded and conjured a cup with water in it, then added the three drops of the colorless, odorless potion and held it to the woman's lips to drink.

=ooo=

"This isn't going to do you any good," Verity Weasley said, as the Auror removed the glass from her lips. "I don't know a damn thing about any letters about Harry Potter being sent to the Ministry."

"Then you shouldn't be arguing with us about answering these questions," the Auror, a ten-year veteran of the Auror Department, snapped back at her.

"I wouldn't be arguing if it wasn't three in the bloody morning!" Verity shouted. "You might have come by or owled us to report in for questioning, not break down our doors in the middle of the night and take us prisoner!"

"You're not a prisoner," Elric Powell the Auror said calmly.

Verity looked around at the cords binding her to the chair. "This may be your idea of a fashion statement but it's pretty damned uncomfortable, if you ask me."

"We have our reasons," the other Auror, a younger but equally no-nonsense fellow who regarded Verity with suspicion mixed with a vague feeling of attraction — her nightgown was quite revealing up top, and her housecoat barely covered her ample bosoms.

"I can guess," Verity snapped. "We're Weasleys, so you automatically suspect us!"

Which was in fact true to a degree, but neither Auror was going to confirm that aloud. "Just calm down," Powell told her. "When the Veritaserum kicks in we'll ask our questions and that'll be that. Do you want to argue with us or do you want to get this over with?"

"Right," Verity said, bitterly. "Have at it, then."

=ooo=

"State your name," the Auror said to him.

"Ronald Bilius Weasley," Ron said, dully. The Veritaserum had sapped away any inclination he might have to withhold any relevant information to questions asked.

Gregory Goyle watched Ron Weasley for several moments, contemplating his own presence here. He'd expected Mr. Malfoy to take this one; the evidence clearly pointed toward him. Goyle had been surprised when he found his name in the space opposite Ron Weasley as the lead interrogator. He'd pointed this out to Crabbe, and from what Vincent told him before they left to do these interviews, the Head Auror didn't think Ron Weasley was the only person responsible for those letters to him.

"Did you write letters to Head Auror Malfoy with information about his activities over the past few months?" Goyle asked.

"I — yes," Ron answered.

"How did you obtain that information?" Goyle asked.

Ron blinked. "I — I hear things. People talk. You know."

"What people?" Goyle persisted. "Be specific."

"Well, my brothers and their wives talk about Potter all the time," Ron said, frowning. "They think he's perfect, but he's not really, he's just like anyone else. They don't think he'd steal someone's girlfriend, but he would."

Goyle's lips set in a thin line, an almost-smile. It was known that Weasley had a bit of a crush on Hermione Granger, back in the day. They had even dated for a while during seventh year, after she and Potter had some kind of falling out. There were rumors about her and Mr. Malfoy, too, but nobody mentioned them anymore, at least not where Draco might have ears present.

"Did you talk to anyone else about Potter?" Goyle asked. "Anyone at all?"

"My sister and I discuss him over lunch sometimes," Ron said. "But she thinks he's perfect, too — she's always defending him."

"Do you remember who told you he was trying to break the Interdict of Merlin?"

Weasley remained silent, looking confused. Goyle repeated the question.

"I — don't remember," Ron said at last.

"When was the last time you saw your sister?"

"Yesterday, at lunch."

"Did she say anything to you about Potter?"

"I don't remember."

"Was there anyone sitting near you that you might have overheard?"

"No, I don't think so. We were sitting outside a café near our shops, just off Diagon Alley proper. We were the only ones sitting outside."

This was a bit frustrating, Goyle thought. "So what do you remember your sister saying about Potter?" Sometimes, even with Verita, you had to ask a question more than once before any information bubbled up in the subject's head.

"I don't remember," Ron said again.

"But you remember writing the letters to Mr. Malfoy?"

"Y-yes."

"Do you or don't you?"

"Yes, I remember. I definitely, definitely remember doing that."

Goyle rubbed the side of his face. A very clear memory surrounded by vague ones was sometimes an indication that a False Memory Charm had been used on the subject multiple times. Some people didn't retain false memories layered one on top of another very well. "Check him for False Memory Charms," he said to the younger Auror with him, Erickson.

Ericson nodded and waved his wand over Weasley's head several times. He looked up at Goyle, frowning. "If he was charmed it was done very well, the detection spells are inconclusive, sir."

"Ergh," Goyle grunted. Ericson was young but he'd received an Outstanding for his Charms N.E.W.T. at Hogwarts and his detection spells were top notch. That result was not what he wanted to hear. They would have to wait and see what the other Weasley interrogations turned up, especially Ginny's. Ministry intel on her and Ron Weasley showed they talked relatively often, at least once a week for an hour or more. What didn't make sense was why Ginny Thomas would try to pin those letters on her brother, if she was the one responsible. The Weasleys were supposed to be a tight-knit family; something like this was atypical for them.

But his was not to reason why, Goyle knew. He just followed the boss's orders. He took out his wPhone and ran the voice-to-text app. "Interrogation of R. Weasley complete. Please advise further orders." He selected Mr. Malfoy's contact and sent the message. It was nearly a minute before there was a response from Draco's phone, sent to everyone out on the mission.

All lead interrog Aurors report to Ministry HQ at 0400 for debriefing. Junior Aurors remain with subjects.

"You got that?" Goyle asked Ericson, who nodded glumly. "Don't worry, it shouldn't take long to sort things out," he told the younger Auror, who shrugged noncommittally.

Goyle checked the time on his phone: 3:38 a.m. That gave him plenty of time to get back to the Ministry and get his interrogation report written for the meeting, in case Mr. Malfoy wanted notes. Which he would, because if he decided to bring someone in based on the results of the interrogation, they'd be going out yet again before they were finished for the night.

=ooo=

At 3:38 a.m. on Sunday morning the Auror Department offices were dark and empty, as was normally the case on early weekend mornings. Malfoy ran a tight ship, but not so tight that his men had to work through the weekends to get their assignments done. If he worked, they worked; but if he was home enjoying time with his wife and their families, his men did too.

At 3:39 a.m. the Auror Department experienced a sudden influx of personnel. Nearly a dozen men were appearing, one right after another, and moving quickly to their individual offices to prepare their reports for the meeting in less than 20 minutes. Everyone knew the Head Auror would expect nothing less than complete preparedness when it came time for their reports.

Malfoy had the eight senior Aurors on the interrogation team gather in the conference room for the debriefing. The men all looked tired, he noted; there was usually idle banter before meetings but this time the men were scanning the notes they'd made or sipping hastily-made tea from the department's snack area.
Malfoy was tired as well. He hadn't participated directly in the interrogations; if he brought someone in because of these questionings he didn't want charges of conflict of interest leveled against him. It was likely to happen anyway; the Weasleys filed complaints against the Auror Department almost perfunctorily whenever they were questioned.

At 4:02 a.m. Malfoy called the debriefing to order. "I know it's late," he said, by way of an apology, the only one everyone there knew they'd hear from him. "I want to see if we have anything we can take action on before we wrap things up for the night. Mr. Crabbe, if you would give us your summary of the interviews…"

The big Auror, whom Malfoy had chosen to gather and correlate the reports, put down his cup of tea (which looked quite miniscule in his large hands) and stood. "Just to review our activities over the past few hours," he said, handing out copies of his summary to the others, "I interviewed Fred Weasley, Kevin Whitby interviewed George Wealsey, and Greg Goyle interviewed Ron. As for their wives, Elric Powell interviewed Verity Weasley, Doran Merryweather interviewed Angelina Weasley, and Willem Hoskins interviewed Luna Weasley. John Dawlish and Stuart Ackerly interviewed Ginny and Dean Weasley, respectively." Crabbe glanced over at the last Auror mentioned. "You all right there, Ackerly?" Acklerly had Portkeyed in with Dawlish but the older Auror had led him to a chair in the conference room and he hadn't moved since then.

"Dean Thomas hit him with a Confundus Charm as we entered their apartment," Dawlish spoke up. "I conducted both of the interviews."

Crabbe cleared his throat before continuing. "None of the interviewees admitted to any knowledge of the owls to Mr. Malfoy except, as expected, Ronald Weasley. However, as Mr. Goyle reported, Weasley himself seemed unable to say who had told him about what was written in them. Other than his brothers and their wives, the only person he has regular contact with is his sister Ginny."

Malfoy looked at Dawlish, who had interviewed Ginny Thomas. "You reported nothing unusual during your interview, and Mrs. Thomas didn't give you any further leads. How did she act during the interview?"

John Dawlish stood. Though not as big as Vincent Crabbe and older by several decades, the man still looked imposing. "She was pretty pissed off, of course." There were chuckles around the room. "I pressed her and her husband pretty hard for details about anything they might have overheard, in their office or from other wizards about Potter; Mrs. Thomas said her brother Ron was the person who'd mentioned them to her. Her husband didn't know anything, either from Weasley himself, his brothers or Potter."

"And that puts us in a catch-22," Malfoy muttered. When he saw the blank looks some of the other Aurors were giving him he added, "It's a Muggle term, it means we're chasing Kneazle tails." Chasing a Kneazle's tail was common saying meaning you were caught in a situation you couldn't get out of.

"What about Pensieving Ron Weasley's memories?" Dawlish asked Malfoy. "I read in the summary that Ericson checked him for False Memory Charms, but the results were inconclusive. We probably need to delve deeper into his memories."

"Possibly." Malfoy appeared distracted, thinking of something else. After nearly a half-minute he took out his wPhone and dialed a number. It rang three times before a sleepy voice answered.

"What is it, Draco?" the Minister of Magic asked, a bit testily. "You know it's four-something in the morning, don't you?"

"Sorry, Minister," Draco said, not really meaning it. "Did I wake you?"

"What do you think?" Hermione snapped. "What do you need?"

"Is Harry with you?"

A moment of silence. "You called me to ask if Harry's here? Why didn't you call him?"

"I guess your number came to mind first," Malfoy lied. "Anyway, is he there?"

A sigh, then silence for some time. Malfoy could hear movement through the phone. Then, "…he's not here right now…"

"Uh-huh." Malfoy paused for a moment, letting her think. "Where do you think he is?"

"This goes right back to calling his phone, Draco," Hermione said, covering her concern with annoyance. "If you'd called him first you'd probably be talking to him right now."

"So you have no idea where he's at?" Malfoy dug at her a little more, then held the phone away from his mouth while he stifled a yawn.

Hermione was talking when he put the phone back to his ear. "…expect me to keep track of my husband every second, Draco. You're the one that doesn't trust him!"

"Just thought I'd check, Minister, sorry for the disturbance." Malfoy hung up before she could retort. "Potter's not at home," he told the other Aurors. "But I think I know where he's at."

"Where's that?" Dawlish wanted to know.

"At Hogwarts. The last letter I got said that he had gone to Hogwarts to visit the Chamber of Secrets. That's probably where he was when he found out we were searching his offices. I expect he went back there afterwards. And that's where we're going now." Malfoy turned to Crabbe and Goyle. "You two are with me. Dawlish, you're going too. The rest of you bring in the Aurors still at the interview sites."

"What if Potter isn't at Hogwarts?" Vincent Crabbe asked.

"If he's been there, we'll figure out what he did while he was there and pick up his trail," Malfoy decided. "We'll question anyone who talked to him, including the Headmaster, and find out what they know. Make it happen."

The Aurors got busy with preparations to go to Hogwarts. There were warrants to fill out, Portkeys to authorize and enchant, both for the Hogwarts team and the interview teams. Crabbe called out assignments to the senior and junior Aurors, who quickly followed his orders.

In less than a minute everything and everyone was ready. Malfoy and the senior Aurors on his team vanished, heading toward Hogwarts. The remaining Aurors headed out to the interview sites to bring in the junior Aurors who had stayed with the interviewees. The Auror office was once again empty.

=ooo=

Moments later four Aurors appeared just outside the gates of Hogwarts in a whirl of wind and flashing colors. Malfoy frowned.

"I don't see anyone on sentry duty," he commented. "What's Longbottom thinking —" A loud snore interrupted him.

He stepped forward and peered through the gates. Off to one side, slumped forward in a rocking chair large enough to accommodate two full-sized men, was a large sleeping form, dressed in a huge mokeskin coat and furry boots the size of dustbins. He wore no hat but a large tangle of salt-and pepper hair and a great beard all but covered his face. He snored loudly again.

"Hagrid," Malfoy said loudly. "Wake up!"

The snoring ceased and a moment later the half-giant slowly opened one eye. "Eh?" he grunted. His open eye scanned the grounds between himself and Hogwarts. "Did somebody say somethin'?"

"Over here, Hagrid," Malfoy said, annoyed at how slowly the old oaf was responding. What kind of security was he supposed to provide for the school? "Let us in."

Hagrid finally opened both eyes, and stared sleepily at the group of Aurors standing outside the gates. "Eh? Izzat you, Malfoy?" His eyebrows knitted in disapproval. "Kinda early ter be showin' up at Hogwarts, aincha? Breakfast ain't even being served yet."

"We're here to execute a search warrant," Malfoy stated, holding up the parchment document.

"Fer what?" Hagrid wanted to know, then chuckled. "Didjer lose one a' yer men or somethin'?"

"The search warrant is for Harry Potter," Malfoy said, then pointed at the gates. "Now let us in or I'll have my men arrest you for obstruction of justice."

"Awright, awright, hold yer thestrals." Hagrid heaved himself to his feet and fished an enormous key ring out of a pocket of his coat. Fingers the size of a chair leg unerringly found a large steel key that he slid into the lock holding the chains around the gates. The lock opened and the chains slid free. Hagrid pulled open the gates, allowing the four Aurors entrance. They began walking toward the school, but Hagrid spoke again. "Hang on a minnit, I'll walk up with yeh." He quickly slid the chains through the gate again and fastened them with the lock, then gestured impatiently up the path to the school. "Well, go on, then, yer in sech a great tearin' hurry."

They walked the rest of the way in silence. Hagrid stopped at the base of the stairs leading up to the entrance, which opened as the Aurors trudged up the steps. Headmaster Neville Longbottom appeared.

"Head Auror Malfoy," he said, cordial but not overly friendly. "To what do I owe the honor of this rather early visit to our school?"

Malfoy, already annoyed by Hagrid's attitude, didn't bother with being cordial. "We have a warrant to search the school for Harry Potter." He held up the warrant for the Headmaster to see. When Longbottom reached for it Malfoy pulled it back out of his reach.

"Only four of you?" Longbottom smiled. "It's going to take you a while. What makes you think Harry is even here?"

"I have intelligence to that effect," Draco said, curtly. "Also, I understand you had the Weasley brothers install some security spells after you became headmaster."

Neville was no longer smiling. "Where did you hear something like that?"

"You'd be surprised what Veritaserum can get people to reveal," Draco replied evenly. "Are you going to deny it, Headmaster? Not telling us the truth can be seen as an obstruction of justice."

"Fine," Neville said, annoyed. "There are several security spells to help me locate people within Hogwarts." The Weasleys had set up the spells, at significant cost, when Neville took over the Head's position at the school. They'd told him they'd learned about the original security system of the school when they'd attended, and had managed to recreate most of it, with a few bells and whistles of their own. "Harry was here yesterday afternoon, but he must've left long before we closed down the school for the night."

"That's what we're here to find out," Malfoy said. "Do you know when he left?"

"Step inside," Neville said. "We'll find out." He and the four Aurors walked into the Entrance Hall. Neville glanced upward, addressing the ceiling. "Security, when did Harry Potter arrive at Hogwarts yesterday?"

A cool female voice, similar to the one at the visitor's entrance to the Ministry, spoke. "Harry Potter arrived here at 1:47 p.m. yesterday afternoon."

"When did he leave?" Neville asked.

"He left at 6:49 p.m.," the cool voice replied. Neville gave Malfoy a told-you-so look.

"What about the person who was with him?" Malfoy persisted. "James Monroe."

"How do you —" Neville began, then decided not to press the issue. Obviously Malfoy knew quite a bit about what had been going on here at Hogwarts yesterday. Was someone here at the school feeding him information? Or did he have some kind of "hook" into the security spells the Weasleys had set up for him? If he'd questioned them under Veritaserum it was entirely probable, Neville had to admit. Instead he asked, "When did James Monroe arrive at Hogwarts yesterday?"

"James Monroe arrived here at 1:47 p.m. yesterday afternoon."

"And when did he leave?"

"He has not left yet," the voice answered.

Longbottom looked surprised, but Malfoy smiled. "Why doesn't that surprise me," the Head Auror said, rhetorically. "Where is he now?" he asked the Headmaster.

"Locate James Monroe."

"James Monroe cannot be located," the security system's voice responded.

"Curiouser and curiouser," Malfoy muttered. "Can it tell us his last known location?"

"Where was James Monroe's last known location?" Neville asked, curious himself how someone could still be here and yet be invisible to the supposedly infallible security system. The Weasleys had told him it could locate anyone within the school, whether they were living, dead, disguised by Polyjuice or Animagus magic or even hidden within trunks supposedly impenetrable to detection magic.

"On the seventh floor of the castle," the voice answered.

"Oh," Malfoy said, nodding. "Of course." He knew what was on the seventh floor. And so, from the look on his face, did Neville Longbottom. "Follow me, men," he said to the other Aurors. They set off up the grand staircase, heading toward the seventh floor, with the Headmaster following closely behind them. Their warrant was for Harry Potter, not Monroe, but Neville wanted to find out, even more than they did, just what the man was doing up in the Room of Requirement without his permission.

=ooo=

"Wow," Harry said. He stepped away from the statues of the Founders, closing the last book of pre-Interdict spells he'd been looking at. "Just, wow."

Monroe, who was massaging the temples of his throbbing head, nodded painfully. "Yeah," he agreed. "I think we overdid it, though."

"Who cares?" Harry said, opening the book again. "I can read all these spells now! And frankly, they're astonishing."

Harry and Monroe had spent the past several hours going through the old spell and potions books, having the Founder statues read them aloud so they could learn and understand them. Monroe had a few hours head-start on Harry, having been in the Room of Requirement longer than he had, but Harry, spurred by the prospect of gaining the old knowledge, knowledge that he hoped would bring with it a way to hasten the beginning of the Magical Singularity and perhaps the end of the Interdict itself, had pushed hard with the Founders, continuing on even when Monroe stopped to rest his brain. His own head throbbing as well, Harry had nevertheless committed spell after spell, ritual after ritual, to memory.

It hadn't hurt when one of the Founders read the Memory Enhancing ritual to them, and both Harry and Monroe decided to try it on themselves. The 40-minute ritual included drinking a potion, which the Room thoughtfully provided, and repetition of a series of chants, written in ancient runes, that gave both of them an eidetic memory. It also produced a blinding headache in each of them, a headache that would not respond to pain-relief spells, being a side-effect of the ritual itself. But they could now precisely recall each of the spells they had memorizes as well as any spell they had ever learned, along with most of the other memories of their lives, both magical and mundane.

"Some very powerful spells," Monroe said. "Permanent Transfiguration. Summoning spells that work across any distance and transport the object to you like Apparition. Spells to extend life and youth three or four times the normal limits of a wizard's lifetime. Magical cures for vision and hearing problems — you would never have to wear glasses again, Harry."

"And spells to multiply food and jewels," Harry added. "I could buy one meal and never have to buy one again, assuming I only wanted to eat that one meal over and over again. I could have clothes covered in emeralds and rubies if I wanted. I wonder if there's a spell to multiply gold and silver?"

"Which came first," Monroe asked rhetorically, "the Philosopher's Stone or the gold-making spell? Flamel made his Stone in the late 1300's or early 1400's. Historical records indicated his wife Perenelle died around 1412; he must have created the Stone by then and used it on her, pretending she died. He finally faked his own death six years later, in 1418. If Merlin died casting the Interdict around 1160 or so, as is commonly believed, the Interdict had been in effect 260 years by the time Flamel disappeared. It's possible that a lot of advanced magic disappeared from wizarding knowledge in that period of time; Flamel may have been the last man able to piece together enough of the ancient, powerful magic handed down orally to create the Stone."

Harry nodded, but he was only half-listening. He was thinking about his other books, the ones hidden in his Bat Cave. He really wanted to get some of those books — hell, all of them — here in this room and have the Founders read them to him.

What he'd really like to do, what he desperately wanted to do, was to find a way to bring these statues to the Bat Cave and spend as much time as he needed going through those books, learning everything that was learnable from them. But, realistically, that wasn't going to happen, he knew. He and Monroe had already crammed several books worth of Interdict-protected spells in their heads, each, and they had to get out of here, get some rest, and figure out what they should do next with the knowledge the minds of the Founders had given to them. The headache the Memory Enhancing ritual had given him was beginning to fade, it felt like, and he hoped some sleep would relieve it even more.

"As much as I'd like to stay and continue learning more Interdict-protected spells," Harry said to Monroe. "I think we need to go home and get some rest. It's nearly morning — Hermione will probably wonder where I've been all night."

Monroe looked up at Harry. "Are you going to tell her where we've been?" he asked.

"No," Harry replied, earnestly. "She's already worried that Malfoy is looking for a way to discredit me with the Wizengamot using my relationship with the Muggle business community, both in Britain and globally."

Monroe snorted. "I'd think most members of the Wizengamot have their fingers in some Muggle pies themselves, anyway!"

Harry nodded. "But only indirectly, for the most part, so they rationalize to themselves that they're not really collaborating with Muggles — they think of it as 'taking advantage of a situation,' not collaborating or even partnering with them."

"And what are we going to do with this new magical knowledge we've gained?" Monroe asked, more pointedly. "Do you still intend to break the Interdict?"

Harry was silent for several moments. "I don't know," he said at last. "It may not be a good idea to break the Interdict."

"Because…" Monroe prompted, after a few moments of silence.

"Because there are people who may not be able to handle spells as powerful as we've seen in these books," Harry said, gesturing toward the table.

"Are we able to handle them?" Monroe pondered. "Do you still feel like playing God?"

Harry looked at Monroe sharply. "What makes you ask that?"

"You told someone once that every time someone cries out in prayer and you can't answer, you feel guilty about not being God."

"I don't remember saying anything like that in front of you," Harry said, though he had said that.

"It made a big impression on Neville," Monroe explained. "He discussed it with several people in his House, and they talked about it as well. I asked him about it directly during a quiet moment in one of Quirrell's battle exercises." He smiled. "Having an eidetic memory is pretty cool, huh?"

Harry gave a non-committal shrug. Maybe he did still want to be God. But he wasn't going to say so aloud, even in front of Monroe. Some things in your life you learned not to wear on your sleeve. "Are you ready to go?"

"Sure," said Monroe. "I think I remember how to get back in here, if we come back. Which I think we —" He stopped talking for a moment. "Did you hear something?"

"Like what?" Harry asked. "We're the only ones here."

"Outside the wall," Monroe said, walking toward the wall where the door had been. He stopped before the door appeared. "I thought I heard something."

Fap, fap, fap. The sound of a hand slapping the wall. Harry and Monroe looked at one another. Tap, tap, tap. The next sounds were sharper, like someone tapping the wall with something. Like a wand.

"James Monroe, are you in there?" Neville's muffled voice came through the wall. "We know you haven't left the castle."

We? Harry took out his wand and pointed it at the wall. It was time to use one of the spells he'd learned, a powerful detection spell. "Kitore salyudak," he canted softly. The wall seemed to fade before his eyes, revealing Neville on the opposite side. There were four Aurors standing behind him: Malfoy, his two regulars Crabbe and Goyle, and John Dawlish. "Crap," Harry muttered.

"What did you see?" Monroe asked. "Was that the Headmaster?"

"Yeah, and he's got four Aurors with him," Harry said.

"Only four?" Monroe looked both surprised and amused.

"Maybe they don't think I'm with you," Harry said. "He only asked for you, not for both of us. Malfoy probably would have brought a whole squad of Aurors if he thought we were both here."

"He might have anyway," Monroe suggested. "We don't know where the rest of them are right now."

=ooo=

At that moment one Auror, Stuart Ackerly, appeared outside the apartment building where Dean and Ginny Weasley lived, and where junior Aurors Hal Perkins and Rene Aberjon were currently waiting for further orders. He trudged tiredly to the door and cast the recognition signal spell to alert the Aurors inside that another Auror wanted entrance.

There was no answering signal. Ackerly tried again, then a third time, with the same result. He cursed under his breath at the inconvenience. If Perkins and Aberjon had dozed off he was reporting them, mates or not! He waved his wand unobtrusively at the door, unlocking it, then entered. Protocol required calling for a backup when the recognition signal wasn't answered, but there was nobody back at department HQ, and he wasn't about to wake anyone else up. If he caught the two juniors asleep he'd put a false memory of answering the signal in one of them and let them explain why Auror Ackerly had caught them having a kip!

Ackerly walked silently up to the Thomas' apartment, listening for any sounds that might tell him what was going on. He heard nothing. Trying the door, he found it open. That, too, was not according to protocol, especially in a Muggle apartment building. Ackerly slipped inside, looking around the apartment's living room. In the middle of the room there was a chair, a tall, light-skinned black man tied to it, slumped over unconscious. That was Dean Thomas, Ackerly knew; he frowned at the man who'd managed to Confund him as he and Dawlish entered the apartment several hours earlier. Of Perkins or Aberjon there was no sign, so Ackerly continued into the kitchen, where Ginny Thomas had been interrogated.

What Ackerly found there made him gasp. In the chair in the middle of the kitchen floor Junior Auror Perkins was slumped forward; his arms, tied behind the back of the chair, kept him from falling over. In a corner of the kitchen another body lay sprawled on the floor — Ackerly could see it was Aberjon. He automatically cast a spell toward Aberjon, a spell that told him the man was dead.

Rushing over to Perkins, Ackerly knelt down so he could see the man's face better. He pointed his wand at the man and cast Rennervate on him. "Hal!" he said urgently, as Perkins came to, groaning. "What the hell happened here?"

"Weasley…" Perkins whispered. He looked up at Ackerly. His entire body was trembling. "Get out," he said hoarsely. "Run away."

Ackerly shook his head, confused. "Run, why, Hal? Why should I run?"

"Trap," Perkins said, straightening up. "Run."

"Run from who?" Ackerly persisted, looking around for the trap Perkins warned him of. "Is Ginny Weasley still here?"

"No," Perkins shook his head. His right hand came out from behind the chair. It held his wand. "Avada Kedavra!"

Ackerly fell over dead, a confused expression still on his face. Perkins shook his head in anguish even as he turned the wand on himself and repeated the Killing Curse. There was a flash of green and the apartment was silent once again.

It was several minutes before anything else happened; one of the chairs in the kitchen suddenly tipped over. It flowed and writhed, changing from a kitchen chair to the body of a man. The body of John Dawlish.

Chapter 23: Interview with the Dark Lord

Updated 12/7/2012

=ooo=

Harry watched in silent horror as his friend James Monroe dropped lifelessly to the floor of the apartment. He involuntarily strained against the Body-Bind spell that held him, but could not break it wandlessly. And it was good that he could not do so — he did not want to show his horror, his grief, to the person that had just murdered his friend.

Harry's eyes locked on Ginny Thomas, who still held the pose she had taken when cursing James to death. Her eyes were on him now, and those eyes, Harry could see, felt nothing for what she had just done.

But it wasn't Ginny Thomas who had killed Monroe, Harry knew; it was someone much more dangerous, more cunning and ruthless, than anyone Harry had ever known in his 36 years of life. It was Voldemort.

Voldemort was back.

Harry had once accused James Monroe of being Voldemort, but he hadn't really believed it. He believed Voldemort had been dead for almost 20 years, killed in 1998 when Harry and Dumbledore destroyed the second Horcrux he'd created and Harry defeated him in combat. He should not be alive now. How, and why, he had surfaced again was something Harry would have to discover.

Before he killed him again.

"You didn't have to do that," an icy cold voice crackled from Harry's throat. "You're back for me, not him."

"Mostly correct, Mr. Potter," Ginny's voice agreed. "I've been waiting a long time for my revenge." Her arm dropped to her side, and she turned to look at Harry. Her eyes were as cold and soulless as Voldemort's had been, the last time Harry gazed into them. "But you should not presume to dictate the terms of my revenge to me. Mr. Monroe's death, while collateral in one sense, is also a necessary part of my plan."

"So now what?" Harry asked, still in the ice-cold tone he hadn't used in many years, not since he'd learned to control the dark aspect of his character. Would he have a chance to learn the Dark Lord's plan? "Do you plan to kill me next?"

An amused smirk twisted Ginny's lips. "Of course not. After all the years I've waited for this, do you suppose I'd simply kill you without sufficient suffering on your part in repayment of the debt you owe me?"

"I'm not sure what to think," Harry answered honestly. "It's always been hard to read you, Tom." That was true enough, and perhaps Harry shouldn't have admitted it, but he hoped using Voldemort's real name would distract the man enough to give Harry a slight edge.

But the Dark wizard seemed to ignore the jab. "I've been careful not to give any indication I was alive," Ginny's voice said, quietly. "It was only because of you and Monroe stumbling into a way to beat the Interdict that caused me to show myself today. Otherwise, things might have continued the way they were for years while I consolidated my power in the Wizengamot and Ministry, until I had circumstances arranged just the way I needed them to be for my return."

"What circumstances?" Harry asked, wondering if Voldemort was in a bragging mood. It was unlikely — one of his rules was Don't brag, but if Harry had already disrupted his original plan he might be willing to disrupt things even more.

Ginny's arm waved dismissively. "We'll get to that in a bit."

"Very well," Harry said, after a moment. "Then let's go back to my original comment. You didn't have to kill James."

"He'd served his purpose," the Dark Lord said, stepping next to Monroe's body and reaching down to feel for a pulse. He looked up, seeing Harry watching him, and added. "You can never be too cautious these days, even with the Killing Curse. There are more ways to avoid it than you might think. Even if it works, the person might come back anyway."

"I suppose you'd know that," Harry muttered darkly. "Do you think James had a Horcrux?"

"No," James's murderer replied. "He was too 'good' for that. But I'm sure you realize now, Mr. Potter, that you don't need to do murder to create a Horcrux."

The statues of the Founders in the Room of Requirement were proof of that, Harry knew. But none of the spells they had passed to Harry would let him move his memories, his personality, into an inanimate object, to imbue it with his…soul…if you wanted to call it that. But —

"I'm not interested in that type of immortality," Harry said, with a slow shake of his head, the only motion his body could still muster.

"Neither was I," Voldemort agreed, with a thin smile. "But murder does make for the best Horcruxes, even if the act is technically unnecessary."

"Yes, Horcruxes," Harry said. "Did I miss one of them, then?"

Ginny's possessor was looking calculatingly around the room. "It would seem so," her voice replied in a distracted tone. She suddenly bent down, picking up Monroe's body in a fireman's carry and moving toward the front door. She set Monroe down on his feet, then allowed him to fall forward to the floor with a thump.

"How did I miss it?" Harry asked, watching Voldemort's actions with growing concern. What was he doing with James's body?

"Come now, Mr. Potter," the Dark Lord said, studying the position of Monroe's body on the floor. "You're the one with the perfect memory, even if you're only half as smart now as you were before. You already have enough information to figure out where at least one of my other Horcruxes is."

Harry was silent for several seconds, remembering everything he and Voldemort had said to one another over the years. Remembering wasn't the problem, of course; he could remember everything he'd ever said, ever read, even ever glanced at casually as he walked down the street. What was important now was the meaning hidden in some of those words, and that was going to be more difficult now that his intelligence was halved.

To hide the fact that he was coming up with nothing, he instead asked, "What are you doing with Monroe's body?"

"Setting the stage a bit," Ginny's voice answered. One of her arms waved at him. Harry, still unable to move his body, felt himself rise in the air a short distance and float over to the front door.

Stepping to the middle of the room, Voldemort took out Harry and Ginny's wands. "Now that you've killed Monroe —"

"Why would I have killed Monroe?" Harry interrupted. "He and I have been good friends for months now."

Voldemort laughed. It was a strange, unnatural sound coming from Ginny's mouth. "You became unhinged when you learned that Monroe found a way to beat the Interdict of Merlin."

Harry laughed as well, in derision. "Why would I do that? I've been trying to beat the Interdict before I ever heard of James Monroe!"

"Exactly," Voldemort agreed. "You wanted to be the one to defeat Merlin's magic-limiting spell, not him. After Ginny arrived, you saw an opportunity to kill Monroe and blame her for his death."

"That's preposterous," Harry said, flatly. "Ginny's been with me a long time —"

"And you were upset when she told you she was in love with Monroe," Voldemort spoke over him, after Monroe left to get food for the three of you. "That's why you killed him the moment he stepped through the door."

Voldemort smiled at the look of shock and confusion on Harry's face. "Don't worry, Harry, you will believe everything I'm telling you has transpired, and you will tell the Aurors willingly. Now, let's what kind of duel you and Ginny might have had."

Voldemort began an elaborate back-and-forth duel across the room, throwing Blasting Curses, Stunners, Disarming Charms, somehow casting Shields simultaneously so that the curses deflected off them, slamming into the walls and floors, breaking and shattering them.

When Voldemort finished the room was in a shambles; walls blasted down to plaster, the divan ripped apart, the carpet smoking in several places. Harry could hear screaming in some other part of the building, probably in response to the explosions from the mock-duel Voldemort had staged.

"There," Ginny's voice said, dropping a wand next to Monroe's outstretched hand. "That should do nicely. Now you and I can go somewhere and talk."

Voldemort picked a torn sofa pillow off the floor and touched it with Harry's wand. "Portus," he said, then pressed it against Harry's arm. A moment later he felt the normal hook-behind-the-navel sensation of Portkey travel, and they were in the anteroom of his and Hermione's apartment.

Voldemort waved a hand at Harry, floating him down the corridor to the living room of the apartment. Harry's eyes were darting back and forth in consternation — his home was a shambles, as if there'd been some kind of fight here as well.

Voldemort floated him in front of a chair that wasn't blasted apart, then momentarily released the Body-Bind. Harry flopped into the chair, but before he could jump to his feet he was Bound again, though his head still had movement. Voldemort conjured a chair and sat down across from Harry, regarding him impassively. "Any questions, Potter?" he asked, smiling maliciously.

"First, a comment," Harry replied. "I see you're still afraid of me, Tom."

Ginny's face colored a bit but didn't lose the smile. "You shouldn't mistake a prudent caution for fear, Mr. Potter. I don't need you leaping at me at odd moments due to your loss of cognitive ability, leading you to believe you have any kind of chance of escaping. Anything else before I explain your situation to you?"

Harry sighed. "How about the obvious question, then? Why aren't you dead? And don't give me the obvious answer, please. I'll deduct Potter points for that."

Voldemort chuckled. "I see you remember my old motivational system for getting students to think for themselves."

"Yeah, I remember pretty much everything," Harry retorted. "Especially now. But I'm still waiting for you to answer."

Ginny's body leaned back and folded her arms across her chest, a very un-Ginny-like gesture. "I'm afraid my answer must be the obvious one, however — you did not find all of my Horcruxes."

"That seems unlikely," Harry disagreed. "Once I showed your diary to Dumbledore and we realized what it was, Dumbledore deduced that you would not be content to create a single Horcrux. The two most powerful magical numbers are three and seven. Splitting your soul into seven would make it dangerously unstable, so we concluded that you split it into three."

Voldemort was silent for some time, staring at Harry. "Did you ever question old Slughorn about the conversation I had with him about Horcruxes?"

"Dumbledore did," Harry answered. "He was not very forthcoming about it — he told the Headmaster he refused to tell you anything about them."

Voldemort nodded. "He was loathe to discuss it at first, Dark as it was, but the old fool couldn't help but boast of his deep knowledge on the subject, especially to an up-and-coming young wizard such as I was at the time. I'm sure he expected me to be quite an asset to him in his later years, after retirement, when he believed I'd be Minister of Magic."

"Both your diary and the Gaunt ring were destroyed," Harry pointed out. "The diary in my sixth year and the ring the year after, and we finally defeated you once and for all!"

"Or so you thought," Voldemort added, softly.

"So there are more Horcruxes," Harry said, voicing his worst fear.

"At least one more," the entity possessing Ginny agreed. "Would you like me to tell you where it's at?"

Harry laughed, a raw, scornful sound. "No, I suppose I should work that out for myself, Tom." It was impossible to think of the person in Ginny's body as her anymore.

"I have all but told you where it is already, you know," Tom pointed out with a sardonic smile. "I was going to say that you probably don't remember, but that would be incorrect now, wouldn't it? The problem you have now is deducing which of the many things we talked about refers to it, and where you might find it today."

"Assuming I'm going to be alive to do so," Harry muttered.

There was irritation in Voldemort's response. "Have I not already said I have no plans to kill you, Mr. Potter? My designs for you, as hastily as they have been conceived, require that you, Mrs. Thomas, and even your wife remain alive and that you all play your assigned roles in the drama that will shortly unfold."

Harry tensed, a reaction that fortunately wasn't very noticeable as he was Bound at the moment. It must be late, yet Hermione was not home. Or at least, she had not yet burst into the room, wand blasting spells at the person holding him against his will. A late night at the office? Harry dearly hoped so, he might still be able to find a way to turn the tables on Voldemort.

That did not seem like a reasonable goal at the moment, however.

"Perhaps we should discuss just what those roles are going to be," Harry suggested. "Just for the sake of argument, as it were."

Voldemort did not reply for some time, he simply sat looking at Harry, rubbing Ginny's chin thoughtfully. "That does violate my rule against divulging my evil plots," he said at last. "But as you will be False-Memory Charmed into believing what I want you to believe, along with Ginny Thomas and your wife, it might be interesting for once to tell you just what is going to happen to all of you."

Voldemort stood. "And speaking of your wife," he added. "Perhaps she should join us at this time." Without another word he turned disappeared down the hallway where their bedroom was, leaving Harry alone and anxious about what had happened to Hermione.

Harry immediately began trying to break the Body-Bind spell again. This one didn't feel as strong as the previous one had, but it still wasn't responding to his wandless counter charms. The Founders had given him some powerful dispelling charms, but they were all meant to work with a wand, and Voldemort still had his.

He needed to think of a way out of this mess, but that was the problem: the ritual that had given him a perfect memory had also taken away half of his intelligence, his ability to think logically and plan accordingly. He had access to all of his memories, but using those memories to solve problems wasn't nearly as easy anymore.

At least he knew that Voldemort didn't plan to kill him, Ginny or Hermione, Harry reflected. Whatever happened to him, even if he was False-Memory Charmed, he might be able to use some type of memory trick, like his recognition code mnemonic, to help him remember that he'd been given false memories.

There was movement in the hallway Voldemort had walked into earlier and this time Harry could not repress the gasp of surprise that was ripped from him as he recognized his wife floating before the Dark Lord. She was curled in a fetal form, arms hugging her drawn-up legs, and everywhere Harry could see exposed skin it appeared cyanotic. "What the hell did you do to her, Riddle?!" Harry shouted angrily.

Voldemort made no reply, but simply floated Hermione's body next to the chair where Harry was Bound. Dust and debris on the floor blew away, leaving a relatively clean spot for her, and she slowly sank to the ground. Even turning his head, Harry could only see part of her from his vantage point in the chair — the armrest blocked the rest of her. She did not appear to be breathing. "I thought you said you needed her alive," Harry rasped, fearing the worst.

"It is a Hibernation Charm," Voldemort said, sitting down across from Harry once again. "I set a trap in your 'Bat Cave' for when she returned home, having removed several items from there beforehand."

"You've been in the Bat Cave?" Harry frowned. "That's not possib—"

"Oh, please," Voldemort said, almost wearily. "Have you forgotten who I am, Mr. Potter?"

Harry hadn't forgotten, of course, but he hadn't expected Voldemort to suddenly reappear, either. "Whatever," he said, dismissively. "You need to remove that spell from Hermione immediately, before it harms her!"

"The spell is perfectly safe for up to a half-year on the average human," Voldemort pointed out. "On wizards it can last for up to a year before fat reserves are depleted and the body begins consuming its own muscle mass. Your wife has been under the spell for only a few hours — she will be fine while I describe the scenario I've devised for you, Ginny and your wife." Voldemort smiled thinly. "Unless you'd prefer I simply put your false memories in place right now?"

"I'm listening," Harry muttered, grimly.

Voldemort sat back with a satisfied smile. "I do admit this scenario is a bit rushed — your and Monroe's actions at Hogwarts forced my hand to some extent, but it's also true that had you not found a way around the Interdict, it might have been years before I made my move against the Ministry."

"The Ministry again?" Harry shook his head. "That didn't come off so well the first time." Voldemort had made an effort in Harry's seventh year to wrest control of the Ministry from then-Minister Rufus Scrimgeour, who had gained control the year before as Cornelius Fudge was pushed out by Lucius Malfoy, who found he had become so corrupt that he was taking money from other pureblood wizards as well as Malfoy.

Before Voldemort could succeed, however, Harry and Dumbledore had located his ring Horcrux and destroyed it, and they and Order of the Phoenix members confronted him as he and a number of Death Eaters stormed the Ministry in an all-out effort to take it from Scrimgeour's control. Voldemort killed the Headmaster during the initial confrontation, but Harry, using Dumbledore's wand, was able to defeat him afterwards.

"That is true," Voldemort agreed, "but this time I won't be quite so straightforward as I was the last time. In any event, the Ministry will be distracted by a major accomplishment this time — they will be celebrating the arrest of Harry Potter for practicing forbidden magic — and murder."

"Murder," Harry snorted. "Do you mean Monroe? I know you used my wand to kill him. But a lot of people knew we were friends, they'll question why I would suddenly kill him without reason."

Voldemort put an arm on the armrest of his chair and leaned his face against his palm. "Because when you woke up in the apartment earlier Ginny was there but Monroe was gone, and she told you she was in love with him and had decided to leave Dean, and you, and be with him."

Harry had to laugh at that in spite of the cold chill that statement sent up his spine. "Ginny's not that mental. She and Dean are going through a rough patch but they'll work it out eventually. And she's never shown the slightest indication she's interested in Monroe. Or was," he added, soberly, remembering that Monroe was dead now.

"She'd been wanting to tell you for some time," Voldemort went on as if Harry hadn't spoken. "She's still fiercely loyal to you but she was worried about what you and Monroe have been doing these past few months — trying to find the Source of Magic, trying to break the Interdict, and even trying to figure out how to initiate a Magical Singularity. All of these things would cause massive disruptions to the wizarding world, not just in Britain, but worldwide. In fact, she's the reason why her brother Ron has been writing the Ministry with information on your activities, trying to spur Head Auror Malfoy into investigating what you've been doing."

"But that's really been your doing, hasn't it?" Harry said, in a hard voice. He glanced to his side where his wife still lay curled up in a ball, barely breathing. "Hermione's been up my back about it as well — subtly, because she doesn't know most of the details, only that Monroe and I were discussing those subjects, but she's been afraid that Malfoy was going to start leaning on her to explain what I've been doing. He already tried to raid my business, as you know, and find something incriminating there."

"He'll be here later tonight," Voldemort told him. "Ginny will have sent him a message offering to give herself up for the murder of the three Aurors in exchange for information about Harry Potter's illegal magical activities, and as a witness to his murder of James Monroe, in order to gain leniency for her punishment at Azkaban. Malfoy will come here to take her into custody. Fortunate for both you and her that the dementors are no longer used there."

Harry glanced to his side once again. "And how does Hermione figure in all this?"

Voldemort smiled. "As a participant, hardly at all. She knew none of what was going on between you, Ginny and Monroe beyond your magical investigations, but was unaware of your illegal actions.

"However, with you and Ginny being sent to Azkaban, she will undergo a breakdown and resign as Minister of Magic. She will appoint Draco Malfoy as interim Minister, and within a month or so he will be elected Minister in his own right." Voldemort sat back, waiting to see what Harry would make of that.

"So Draco ends up as Minister," Harry said, slowly. Given what Voldemort was capable of, it wasn't hard to draw the conclusion— "You'll possess Draco at some point, making you the Minister of Magic," he finished.

Voldemort applauded softly. "Very good, Mr. Potter. I see you retained enough intelligence to work that out on your own."

Harry made a gesture of indifference. "That will probably make Lucius happy, but I can't imagine you'll be happy with the paperwork and drudgery of that position. Dark Lords make rather poor bureaucrats."

Voldemort chuckled. "I shall consider myself warned. Other than that, what do you think of my plan?"

Harry didn't answer. Alarmingly, it seemed plausible enough, given that the False-Memory Charms were good enough to fool the improved Veritaserum the Ministry used these days. Harry had to assume Voldemort had taken that into account. "It might work," he finally admitted, trying to put doubt into his voice.

"It will," Voldemort answered immediately. "I have all the details worked out precisely. Malfoy will enter this apartment, ostensibly alone, because of an agreement with Ginny, but he'll have Crabbe and Goyle with him, Disillusioned, after he allows Ginny to cast detection charms before giving up her wand to him.

"But her wand, touching his hand, will trigger a spell that will allow me to slip out of Ginny and into him, undetectably, and I will lie dormant for several hours before asserting my dominance over him. By then he will have you and Ginny on your way to Azkaban, and Hermione, heartbroken by the loss of her husband and one of her closest friends, will resign as Minister of Magic. Since no one even believes the Dark Lord could have returned once again, no one will be the wiser. And I will begin consolidating my position as Minister using Lucius's money and influence, weakening and corrupting the Wizengamot until it becomes useless as a political tool, leaving the Ministry the supreme law of the land."

"For what it's worth," Harry said, in a cold, grim tone, "I think you'll fail."

A thin smile spread across Voldemort's lips. "And what leads you to that conclusion, Mr. Potter? Wishful thinking, perhaps?"

That wasn't far from the truth, but— "You don't have the patience to be Minister, Tom. You're more of a puppet master than a puppet — you prefer to be behind the scenes, directing your minions' actions rather than interacting with the dozens of people you'll need to deal with to be Minister."

Voldemort's expression had changed from cynical amusement to thoughtful contemplation. "I do not necessarily agree with your assessment," he said, quietly. "But you do make salient points that I will consider after the Ministry is mine." He stood. "For now, however, we will finish up here and get you and Ginny on your way to Azkaban."

Voldemort stepped next to Hermione and pointed his wand at her, moving it in a quick but complicated pattern. Her body glowed faintly yellow for several moments. "Your wife is now free of the Hibernation Charm. It will take several minutes for her body to warm to a temperature where her body will be relaxed enough to unfold, at which time I will administer a Warming Potion and a Sleeping Potion. I do not wish her to awaken until after Malfoy and the Aurors have arrived and taken you and Ginny into custody."

Harry had listened to Voldemort's monologue in silence. "When are you going to False-Memory Charm Hermione?"

"It is already done," Voldemort replied. "I took care of that after placing her under the Hibernation Charm. Ginny has had her memories altered as well — she will be under their influence after I leave her body for Malfoy's. That leaves only you, Mr. Potter. Prepare yourself."

Voldemort pointed his wand at Harry. A jolt of nausea hit him and memories began flooding into his brain. It was not like being in a Pensieve, where you experienced another person's memories as if you were standing there with them, but like being force-fed thoughts. He was in Ginny's apartment with her, she was telling him she planned to leave Dean and run away with Monroe to America, she had to go because she'd killed the three Aurors who'd come into her home to question her and Dean. She'd done it so she could rescue Monroe and Harry from Hogwarts, primarily Monroe. Harry felt shocked and betrayed, and when Monroe entered the apartment Harry had pushed Ginny aside and angrily murdered Monroe with the Killing Curse. A fight ensued between him and Ginny, which he won, Stunning her and Portkeying them to his home in the TBC Building, where he found Hermione under a Hibernation Charm. He revived her, but was then knocked out by Ginny using a second wand she'd secreted on her person.

Harry was concentrating on his recognition code mnemonic, hoping that somehow it would trigger his memory of the actual chain of events, which would only be suppressed by the False-Memory Charm, not erased. But it was unnecessary — both sequences of events were still easily remembered.

Voldemort was frowning. "Interesting," he said, staring into Harry's eyes; he could no longer move his head or even close his eyes. "You remember both your own memories and the ones I've implanted. Why?"

Harry knew why, but he wasn't going to say anything if —

"Of course," Voldemort said, chagrin in his voice. "The Total Memory Ritual allows you to recall everything, even memories that should be repressed. I had not counted on this." The wand was still leveled at Harry. "It may be, Mr. Potter, that I will be forced to kill you to keep you from talking, and make Ginny responsible for your death. Not really my first choice, since I prefer that you end your days in prison, but I may have no choice."

Chapter 24: The Monroe Connection

Updated 1/25/2013

=ooo=

"I have to say," Harry remarked dryly, though his blood had gone cold at Voldemort's last words, "that killing me would be a very bad choice." He tried to move his head but Voldemort's enchantments still held it firmly in place. At least he could speak…

Voldemort looked amused. "I would expect no other response from you, Mr. Potter," he remarked, his wand still pointed at Harry.

"Because you're not thinking it through," Harry continued. "Killing me is going to unravel your entire plan." He just hoped he could support his own reasoning — the ritual that had given him perfect recall of all his memories had taken away half his intelligence; rational thinking was no longer as easy as it had been for the past 36 years of his life.

"No, Mr. Potter," Voldemort disagreed, shaking his head slowly. "You are quite incorrect. It will be quite simple to integrate your death with the others that have occurred over the past two days." He gestured toward the curled-up figure of Hermione Granger-Potter-Verres-Evans, who lay unconscious on the floor next to Harry's chair. "When Hermione awakens in a few minutes, she will reach for the wand that is hidden on her person and attack whomever is nearby, believing they were her attacker. The person she attacks will be you, Mr. Potter, as you attempt to bring her back to consciousness after awakening from a Stunning Charm Ginny Thomas managed to cast on you before retreating from your apartment. The curse will be lethal at close range, though she will not cast the Killing Curse, of course — she is likely incapable of casting that spell in any case. Afterwards, regaining her full faculties, she will realize that she's unwittingly killed you and will turn herself over to the Ministry and resign her position as Minister of Magic.

"Her resignation will clear the way for Draco Malfoy to temporarily become the Minister of Magic, after which he will be elected to the position in his own right, given the Most Noble and Ancient House of Malfoy's financial resources and notable lack of ethics in matters of politics. Ginny Thomas, meanwhile, will have made arrangements to surrender personally to Draco Malfoy, and they will meet at her private apartment. At that time I will possess his body and alter Ginny's memories to conform to the new scenario." He inclined Ginny's head toward Harry, inviting a response.

"It sounds pretty plausible," Harry admitted, and found that he could move his head again. He rolled it to either side, loosening his neck muscles. "But it's not going to work."

"Come now, Mr. Potter," Voldemort said, a hint of disappointment in his voice. "You're going to have to do more to convince me than simply disagreeing with me."

Harry lifted his head, gesturing toward his apartment at large. "There is an undetectable detection spell on this apartment that sets off an alarm at the Ministry if someone dies in here. Malfoy and the entire Auror Office are going to converge on this place with wands drawn, expecting the worst. They know only I, Hermione, and a few close friends have access to our residence, and if they suspect I'm here, they'll come down on this place like a herd of nundus."

Voldemort stared at him for several seconds, then slowly smiled. "Very clever, Mr. Potter. Your mind is as opaque to me as ever; this supposedly 'undetectable' charm may or may not be in place here in your apartment — I would have to leave immediately after your death or risk being caught by the Aurors. It will upset my plans if Malfoy arrests Mrs. Thomas before she is ready to meet him."

Harry nodded. Was Voldemort going to change his mind about killing him, or would he come up with another scenario where Harry would end up dead?

"There is another option, of course," Voldemort mused. "I can simply Obliviate all of your memories, leaving your wife to take the blame."

"Assuming that would even work on me," Harry countered, "With the enhanced memory I have now. If a False-Memory Charm didn't work, what makes you think an Obliviate will?"

"You are not helping yourself, Mr. Potter," Voldemort pointed out. "If I cannot Obliviate nor False-Memory Charm you, I can still curse you with a spell that would prove fatal in a short but not immediate amount of time, giving me an opportunity to depart in a more leisurely fashion." He smiled evilly. "Perhaps even a Blood-Chilling Charm…"

Back near the end of their first year at Hogwarts Hermione had been accusing of casting a Blood-Chilling Charm on Draco Malfoy during a duel that was supposedly held in secret in the trophy room of the school. Draco had been found there, near death from the effects of the charm, and had been taken to St. Mungo's after being stabilized. The fact that Professor Quirrell had found Draco and stabilized him before Flooing him to the hospital wasn't lost on Harry at the moment. The Defense Professor at Hogwarts in the years before Harry started there was always a suspect in any strange or illicit activities, and that year had proven to be no different.

"Very funny," Harry murmured, unsmiling. "The problem is, without Harry Potter's own testimony, the scenario you've envisioned is so unlikely that no one will believe it without significant corroboration."

"Your testimony would confirm the allegations made by Ginny and Hermione," Voldemort countered. "But it is by no means essential. The Wizengamot will accept the results of Veritaserum interrogations, just as they always have."

"They probably would," Harry conceded. "But the Auror Office under Minister of Magic Hermione Granger is much more discriminating these days. They will want confirmation, not merely testimony, especially testimony that could be given under false pretenses. Malfoy and his Aurors will scrutinize every detail of this case before they come to any conclusions — the idea that I would kill someone like James Monroe in a jealous rage is so out of character for me that they will have to suspect something like memory tampering or the Imperius curse has been used on Ginny or Hermione." One of the benefits of a science-aware Malfoy in the Auror Office had been his drive to do the best job he was capable of, even if it was only to make himself look good. The Auror Office had ironically benefitted from Malfoy's self-interest.

"By that time," Voldemort pointed out, "I will have had my meeting with Head Auror Malfoy, and he will no longer have any doubts about the credibility of Mrs. Thomas's or your wife's testimony."

"But that's not up to Malfoy alone," Harry countered. "The three most senior Aurors must now reach a consensus on the validity of the evidence when a wizard has been killed. Even if Malfoy considers the matter closed, two other Aurors will have to back him up before the case go to the Wizengamot."

Voldemort looked bemused. "So they are finally learning to think before they act," he muttered, almost to himself. He focused on Harry once again. "So, Mr. Potter, if killing you isn't an option, and false memories can't be implanted in your brain, do you have any suggestions?"

"You could counter the Memory Enhancing ritual," Harry said at once. "So that the False-Memory Charm would work. That is," he added, with a trace of hesitancy, "assuming you have a counter curse for the ritual. It was pre-Interdict magic — it could be irreversible."

"No magic is irreversible, Mr. Potter," Voldemort said. "It's merely a matter of what you are willing to sacrifice to achieve the desired outcome." He stood, pacing back and forth several times before looking at Harry once again.

"It can be done," he said, quietly. "But the cost will be significant, especially for someone going into Azkaban, to which you will undoubtedly be sentenced."

"What is the cost?" Harry asked, calmly.

"You will be weakened physically," Voldemort replied. "You will be only half the man you are now as far as your strength and endurance are concerned."

"And what of my intelligence?" Harry asked, keeping any hesitancy from his voice this time.

"Unchanged," Voldemort told him. "It will not return to what it was before, if that's what you were hoping, Mr. Potter. Dark rituals are not very forgiving when it comes to restoring lost abilities."

So, he could get rid of the memory enhancing magic, so Voldemort wouldn't be forced to kill him, but he would only be half as smart and strong as before. Not a very good tradeoff, Harry thought to himself, but it would still give him time to figure a way out of this. If he could.

"If my only other choice is death," Harry said plaintively, "I think I'll take my chances."

Before Voldemort could reply, however, they both heard a soft gasp, like a baby taking its first breath. Harry turned his head, straining to see over the edge of his chair, but was held fast by the Body-Bind spell still on him. Voldemort stood, crouching beside him as he put a hand over Hermione's mouth. "She is beginning to come out of the Hibernation Charm," Voldemort said. "A rather inopportune moment, unfortunately." He stood, taking out his wand, and made complicated patterns in the air above her. Returning to his chair, he regarded Harry silently.

"What did you do to her?" Harry asked tensely.

"Just a Sleep Charm that will take effect as she becomes conscious," Voldemort replied. "We don't need her awakening during the Memory Enhancing counter-ritual, and it will take some time to perform that."

Harry nodded, mollified. There was only one other thing he needed from Voldemort before he threw himself under the bus of lost intelligence, strength, and freedom. "Before we do the ritual and you have the Wizengamot throw me and Ginny into Azkaban, I want you to tell me something."

Voldemort tilted his head slightly, looking interested. "Mr. Potter, you know one of my rules is 'don't brag,' yet I sense you are about to ask me to do just that."

Harry would have shrugged except his shoulders were immobilized. "You're going to False-Memory Charm me, and I suspect Obliviate me as well — I don't know how I'm going to manage to remember anything you tell me, given that I'm literally going to be only half the man I was a few days ago."

"You underestimate yourself," Voldemort replied, which was something Harry hadn't heard in a while. "However," the Dark Lord continued, "I can make sure that whatever I tell you will be beyond your reach after the counter-ritual is completed and your memories are appropriately modified. What is your question?"

"Where and how did you manage to survive unnoticed since you were supposedly defeated back in 1998?" Harry asked. "And why," he continued, "did you kill James Monroe? If you'd left him alive you could have modified his memories to provide additional testimony against me."

"That is more than one question, Mr. Potter," Voldemort noted matter-of-factly. "However, as I am already violating one of my rules in telling you anything at all, and the questions you've asked have a related answer, I believe I can provide a suitable response."

Voldemort sat back in his chair, spreading his arms in a gesture of here-I-am. "As to where I have been these past 18 years," he said, smiling. "I have always been here."

Harry stared at the Dark Lord for a full half-minute before replying. "Inside — Ginny? You're…lying."

Voldemort's expression was opaque. "Am I, Mr. Potter? Is that fact so difficult for you to grasp?"

"It's impossible to grasp!" Harry shook his head. "After I took your diary away from Ginny Dumbledore made sure there were no lingering — traces — of you inside her. I've had the diary since then, and when Dumbledore and I destroyed it in my sixth year that should have been the end of that Horcrux!"

"That was the end of that Horcrux, Mr. Potter," Voldemort agreed. "Your mistake was not destroying it immediately upon finding it. I had already had most of that school year to forge a bond with Miss Weasley. After all," he smiled knowingly, "the function of a Horcrux is not merely as a phylactery — I am almost surprised you haven't yet learned that."

"There's a surprising dearth of material on the subject," Harry said, tightly. "You've made sure of that. The book you stole from the Restricted Section of the Library — the scroll from Borgin and Burkes. I presume those were your sources? The rest is vague hints and rumors spread among dozens of other books and scrolls, but nothing giving real information or instruction."

"Indeed," Voldemort nodded confirmation. "It would have been a fool's errand, trying to remove every reference to Horcrux from every library in Wizarding Britain, for that might have fostered suspicion needlessly; as it was, it did not escape old Dumbledore's attention. But then, he never trusted me."

"With good reason," Harry muttered.

There was silence for some time between them.

Harry finally spoke. "Do you intend to tell —"

"Have you not already guessed, Mr. Potter?" Voldemort's eyebrow went up in mild surprise, but was replaced by a cruel smile. "Ah. I forgot — your mental faculties are not up to what they were just a few days ago. Let me explain, then.

"Even Dumbledore did not know the full extent of a Horcrux's powers. He had the one book in the Library that gave instruction on its creation, but that author's knowledge was derivative," Voldemort continued. "The scroll at Borgin and Burkes, however, explained all — to those who could avoid the curses that had been laid upon it. Neither Borgin nor Burke had ever tried to read it, though it sat on the shelf in their shop for years before I came to work for them. I suspect even Dumbledore himself would have had trouble discovering its contents, had he known of its existence."

"You can stop patting yourself on the back any time," Harry muttered.

Voldemort chuckled. "You must allow me to enjoy my bragging at least a little bit, Mr. Potter. After all, this is the first time I've done so since manifesting my presence openly in Mrs. Thomas's body."

"Whatever," Harry snorted. "Get on with it."

"Well, to the heart of the matter, then," Voldemort went on, briskly. "Creating a Horcrux is a two-part process. The first part is to enchant an object using a ritual. It has never been given a name, but we might call it the Horcrux Ritual. Most of the spell can be performed ahead of time — it requires several hours to prepare the object — but it is sealed with the life of a human."

"I knew that much," Harry told him, still revolted by the idea itself. "Though the statues of the Founders at Hogwarts said murder wasn't necessary."

"Probably true," Voldemort agreed. "A death was probably incorporated in the original ritual because it evoked strong feelings and emotions, and that strengthened the caster for the next part of the process."

Wait a minute. "Hold on," Harry was staring at Voldemort, perplexed. "Why would you say that? Committing murder is what is supposed to split the wizard's soul, so they could bind part of it into the object to create the Horcrux."

"Oh, surely, Mr. Potter, you don't believe all those stories about souls and so on, do you? I thought you were more intelligent than that."

=ooo=

Harry's mouth opened, then closed, several times before he shut it at last, then sat staring at Voldemort in disbelief. "I don't suppose I do," he said at last, slowly. "But if you performed the ritual, and more than once, then you must believe that is what's happening when you — kill — the v-victim when you cast the spell."

"Tom Riddle believed it," Voldemort said, with an almost sheepish expression on his face. "But it has been a long time since those days, and I have gained quite a bit of knowledge and…insight…since then. Some of that relates, indirectly, to your friend Monroe. However, if you've heard enough, I can begin the ritual to remove your memories and be on my way to meet with Draco Malfoy."

"No," Harry said softly. Whatever he could do to delay that would be to his advantage. "Go ahead."

"The next part of the process," Voldemort continued, as if resuming a college lecture that had been interrupted by an impertinent student, "is to place part of yourself into the enchanted object. That is done by evoking the Patronus Charm and causing it to move into the enchanted object, making it into a Horcrux."

There was another stretch of silence.

"Okay," Harry said, disbelievingly. "Now you're just messing with me."

"I assure you I am quite serious, Mr. Potter," Voldemort said, a trace of irritation in his voice. "We have too much to discuss for me to 'mess with you,' as you put it."

"But that can't be right!" Harry demanded. "The Patronus is a spell of the Light! Dark wizards can't even cast it!"

"That is a useful fiction, Mr. Potter," Voldemort declared. "One that has been told and repeated time and again for centuries, if not millennia. "You have heard, no doubt, that a wizard thought incapable of casting the Patronus will succeed when the need is great; for example, when confronted with a dementor?"

Harry nodded. Dumbledore had told him that in his first year. "But… to cast a Patronus right after killing someone… are you saying you actually did that?" Voldemort nodded. "But what — what happens to the Patronus afterwards…?"

"It becomes part of the Horcrux, and completes the ritual," Voldemort explained. "Have you never considered what a Patronus really is, Mr. Potter? It is an image of your innermost being, made corporeal by your magic. It can even speak with your voice."

"But not much," Harry protested. "Not more than a sentence or two."

"It is only an image of you," Voldemort said. "But it is still you. That is what you bind up in a Horcrux — not a bit of your imaginary soul, but an image of who you are. It is more than a ghost, which is nothing but an afterimage of a dead wizard. It is more than the living portraits that wizards create, seemingly possessing intelligence but which are not really sentient, or conscious."

Harry was nodding slowly. The idea had surprised him, because he had believed Voldemort incapable of casting a Patronus, but for some time he himself had been unable to cast one. That had gnawed at him, cut into him, made him feel…wrong…on several levels. The first Dementor he stood against had nearly ended him, that day in January of 1992, had taken nearly everything from him that made him human. He'd remembered for the first time his mother Lily's desperate plea to save her son, and the fool's bargain the Dark Lord had offered her: herself to die, and her son to live. Except that James was already dead, and Lord Voldemort would have no reason to keep the bargain after Lily was gone. With desperate hate she tried to cast the Killing Curse on Voldemort, but he cast the spell more quickly than her, and she had died.

Remembering that had broken Harry, had left him empty and falling into hate and despair. Worse, when he'd fallen his wand had landed near the true-forged titanium cage that held the Dementor, within inches of it, and it had continued to feed upon him through his wand, though he was far from the Dementor itself, until Professor Quirrell had Flitwick Summon Harry's wand to him. But even that did not dispel the black anger, the hate, the desire for killing and blood and death that held him even as Dumbledore's phoenix, Fawkes, attempted to sooth him with phoenix song and Dumbledore forced chocolate down his throat. But he would not be soothed, he remembered; he'd fully intended to kill everyone there once he'd recovered the strength to do it — even Dumbledore. Perhaps even Quirrell, if the Defense Professor had opposed him. It would be difficult, but not impossible, especially if they weren't expecting him to do anything but lay there eating chocolate.

Then Hermione had kissed him. That completely unexpected action brought him back from the precipice he'd teetered on, willing himself to fall into and give himself over to the Darkness. Instead, he'd pushed her away, shouting "I told you, no kissing!" A moment later the phoenix song finally touched his ears, and he was Harry again.

Then, after he'd recovered, he went back to the cage where the Dementor was, and destroyed it. His corporeal Patronus was not in the form of an animal, but a man, the human animal, the rational animal, and when he (and it) had comprehended what the Dementor was, it could stand before him no more.

Harry jolted when Voldemort suddenly spoke quietly. "You've been quiet for some time, Mr. Potter. Remembering your own Patronus?"

How could he have guessed that, Harry wondered. Had his Occlumency guards slipped momentarily? "Just… wondering how Hermione is doing," he said at last, feeling like it was a lame deflection, though she had just been in his thoughts. "It's been a while since you…"

"She is breathing normally now," Voldemort volunteered. "I can see her chest slowly rising and falling. She is merely sleeping now, until I awaken her."

"I have a question," Harry said suddenly, to take his mind off Hermione and keep the conversation going about Patronuses and Horcruxes. "Why did you kill if you knew it wasn't necessary for the creation of a Horcrux?"

The Dark Lord sat back, regarding Harry silently for some time. "You remember the spell I cast for you a few times during your first year, the stars." It was a statement, not a question.

"I remember it." Standing in the middle of starry space, surrounded by the universe. Harry had searched for that spell in hundreds of old books of magic over the years. He'd wondered it if had been a spell Voldemort learned from Salazar Slytherin's Monster, but why would Slytherin care about such a spell?

"Have you ever wondered where Lord Voldemort found such a spell?"

"The Monster," Harry answered immediately. It was a guess, but it he'd never come across it in any of the books he'd combed through. Slytherin's Monster seemed the logical alternative.

But Voldemort shook his head. "I learned it from Monroe."

"What?" Harry said, automatically, to cover his confusion, but his perfect memory suddenly recalled there was another, older Monroe. "You mean David Monroe?"

"Indeed."

"You killed him too, I'd wager."

"In a manner of speaking," Voldemort replied, cryptically. "He also killed me."

Harry blinked, then smiled humorlessly. "Not well enough for it to take, apparently. I'm surprised you would even admit such a thing."

"At one time I would not have," Voldemort agreed. "But I've…grown…since my days at Hogwarts. My first time at Hogwarts, that is, when I was a student there. What do you know of David Monroe?" he suddenly asked.

"He was the last heir of the House of Monroe," Harry answered. "According to Ministry documents Moody once showed me, he reappeared in 1971 after being gone for 25 years. Before that the House of Monroe had been thought destroyed, by you murdering all of its heirs, and your movement of 'Death Eaters' were increasing in numbers and power. His father, Blaise Monroe, was one of the few voices in the Wizengamot that would speak openly against you, and he was found murdered shortly after David returned to Britain, before the elder Monroe had the opportunity to openly admit David was his son."

Voldemort was nodding. "Yes. I had thought myself rid of them until the younger Monroe returned and claimed his place in the Wizengamot as Lord Monroe. After twenty-five years, I had thought him dead and forgotten."

"He was a student at Hogwarts about the same time you were, wasn't he?"

Voldemort smiled, but the expression held no mirth. "He was, if anyone could be described thus, my nemesis at school. He started a year after I did, sorted into Gryffindor, and we took an instant dislike to one another.

"Blaise Monroe was his father, but his mother was a Muggle that Blaise had a brief affair with. We Slytherins delighted in pointing out that he was a bastard. In return, he made it his business to meddle in our plots and activities." Voldemort seemed almost to brood as he said this. "He somehow learned that Tom Riddle framed Rubeus Hagrid for the opening of the Chamber of Secrets, in 1943. When he went to Headmaster Dippet, however, the headmaster believed Monroe was trying to unfairly discredit me — given the choice between myself and Hagrid, Dippet preferred to believe that oafish half-giant opened the Chamber, not me."

"So you got away with the death of Abigail Myrtle, and with the knowledge Salazar Slytherin placed within the Basilisk," Harry finished.

Voldemort smiled a self-satisfied smile. "Monroe swore he would make sure I would never again ruin anyone as I had ruined Hagrid. His skill at magic was close to mine but most of his time at Hogwarts was spent in my shadow — I heard he was nearly chosen as Head Boy in his seventh year but Aldous Lupin was chosen over him, probably at Dippet's request. I, meanwhile, was working at Borgin and Burkes, acquiring various and sundry items of interest for those two old cheats — until I came across the scroll in their possession describing the powers and abilities of a Horcrux.

"I had already created two Horcruxes, the diary of T.M. Riddle and the ring of Marvolo Gaunt, and I had no intention before then of spreading myself any thinner, for three is a magically powerful number." Voldemort leaned forward, staring intently at Harry. "But that scroll taught me things about Horcruxes that no other book or scroll contained, and its author suggested a rather ingenious use for the Horcrux Ritual, one I confess I would never have thought of on my own."

Harry leaned forward as well — or rather, he tried to, though the Body-Bind spell only let him incline his head toward Voldemort. "And what was that?" he asked.

"Patience, Mr. Potter," the Dark Lord deflected the question. "I will answer that shortly, but for now we must travel forward a quarter of a century, to when David Monroe thrust himself back into my affairs."

"Never mind that you had murdered everyone in his family except his father by then," Harry coldly pointed out.

"Indeed," Voldemort seemed to ignore the tone of Harry's retort. "I was quite enjoying the cat-and-mouse game I was playing with the old man, making him wonder when and how I would come for him. He believed his manor was impregnable. It wasn't, but it would have been too easy to kill him there. I thought the last of an Ancient House deserved a more fitting end. I killed him as he attempted to enter the Ministry for a meeting of the Wizengamot, to speak against me once again." Voldemort sighed with reminiscence.

"I read the Ministry documents," Harry said again.

Voldemort's expression turned hard. "You may imagine my displeasure when it was later announced that David Monroe had returned from abroad only a few days earlier, and that his father had updated his will acknowledging him as his son."

"I'm sure you were furious," Harry murmured dryly. "How is Hermione doing?"

"Still breathing," Voldemort replied, curtly, without glancing at her. "Please don't distract me while I talk, Mr. Potter — I may decide not to make you the offer I plan on extending to you, as a one-time courtesy."

Harry sighed. "You've been full of surprises so far today, Tom," he said, tiredly. "You've been positively gabby about yourself, and how you're offering me courtesies? I am shocked."

Voldemort laughed, a dry cold chuckle that did not fit the face that showed his amusement. "Of course my intentions are not completely selfless. But I will offer you an alternate solution to losing half of both your strength and intelligence, and spending the rest of your life in Azkaban prison."

"You already did make an offer," Harry reminded him. "But as involved killing me, I can't say I'm much interested."

"Another alternative, then," Voldemort clarified. "Your memory would remain intact, and your intelligence, while still not up to its original level, would be higher than it is now."

Harry tilted his head as an alternative to a shrug. He couldn't imagine making a deal with the man who'd tried to kill him more than once while he was still in school, but he could use the time. "What's your offer?"

"I must finish my story about Monroe first," the Dark Lord said. "By the end of it you will see that what I offer is a very good opportunity for you to remain free and in better condition than you are now."

"Go ahead," Harry said. "I'm not going anywhere."

Voldemort chuckled, then composed himself and began. "After Monroe revealed himself to the Wizengamot I stalked him for some time, looking for an opportunity to strike. It was important that I find him quickly and end the Monroe line — my followers were few, and I felt that ending an Ancient and Noble line that spoke so vehemently against me would draw more to me.

"Monroe, however, was clever — and as it turned out, had become quite a skillful wizard. I sent some younger Death Eaters to fight him, to see how he would handle them. He dispatched them easily, and his influence in the Wizengamot increased. I knew I could not let that stand, so I sent a message directly to him, to challenge him to single battle. He accepted and we met at an agreed-upon place, each using our own Portkeys to arrive at a random distance from one another, to ensure that we were both alone."

"So you and Monroe fought," Harry said, slowly. "And obviously, you won —"

"Not so obviously, Mr. Potter," Voldemort said.

"Uuunnnhnh…" Harry almost thought he'd made that noise. But Voldemort had straightened suddenly, staring at the floor next to Harry's chair.

"Interesting…" the Dark Lord murmured. "She awakens…."

"Let me help her!" Harry said instantly, struggling to rise in spite of the Body-Bind. Voldemort raised an eyebrow, but took out a wand and flicked it at Harry, who bolted out of the chair, landing next to Hermione, who was moaning softly. "I thought you put her to sleep!" Harry cradled her head. Her body was no longer frozen, but she could barely move, it seemed.

"I did," Voldemort replied mildly. "Apparently she really wanted to wake up." Harry was checking her wrist, then her neck, for a pulse. There was one, just barely, but it was thin and very weak. He looked up at Voldemort, his expression fierce.

"So help her!" Harry shouted. "You don't want her to die, do you? Won't that screw up your plans for us?"

"As you will," Voldemort shrugged. He pointed his wand at them and said, "Rennervate." Hermione jerked like she was shocked; her eyes flew open, unseeing, and she reached unerringly into her robes, withdrawing a wand which she started to point at Harry. The automatic reaction when she awoke, Harry realized. At a gesture from Voldemort's wand, however, Hermione's flew from her hand.

Harry snatched it out of the air, then lunged toward the Dark Lord shouting "Stupef —"

He fell on his face. His legs jiggled — they'd been hit with the Jelly-Legs Jinx. Voldemort laughed, cruelly and heartily. "Ah, Mr. Potter, you are so predictable when you are desperate!" He flicked his wand and the wand flew out of Harry's hand, caught by the Voldemort. He flicked his wand again, and a chair in a corner flipped back onto its legs and slid over next to them as Hermione shook her head and sat up, finally fully conscious.

"Ginny? Harry?! Where have you been? When did you two get here? I was —"

"Hold on," Harry said sharply. He turned back to Voldemort. "We need to continue our conversation alone."

"Wait — what?" Hermione looked shocked. "What were you and Ginny talking about?"

"ThatsnotGinny," Harry said, speaking rapidly. "ItsVoldemorthestakenoverGinn ysbody — owww!" He rubbed his side where the Dark Lord's Stinging Hex had caught him, giving Voldemort a furious look.

"Since Mrs. Granger-Potter has seen fit to awaken during our conversation," Voldemort said, giving her a cold smile. "I think she should hear it as well, even if she won't remember anything afterwards."

"After what?" Hermione said, shrilly. "You're not —" she jerked as her mind finally caught up with what Harry had said. "You're — not — Ginny!"

Voldemort smiled. "Ginny is here somewhere," he corrected her. "Just not in charge of this body at the moment. At the moment your husband and I are in the midst of a conversation about my old friend Monroe and our battle."

"You fought James?" Hermione's eyes were wide with shock. "Where is he? What — what happened?"

"Not that Monroe," Harry said, his voice low. "The one he supposedly killed in 1971, the one that made him so popular back then. James is —" Harry shook his head, unable to continue.

"Oh, no…" Hermione whispered. Her eyes locked on Voldemort. "You killed him? You bastard! What did he ever do to you?"

Voldemort's face was expressionless. "Nothing but present an opportunity which I exploited. The same way I exploited your trust in Ginny by having you show her your husband's 'Bat Cave'."

Harry jerked in surprise. He'd have leaped to his feet if he legs weren't as soft as taffy. "You showed Ginny the Bat Cave?!" How could she do that?! She knew that he'd only shown it to her and one other person. And that other person was now dead.

"I —" Hermione looked at him helplessly. "She —" She didn't know what to say. "I — I thought I could trust her! I mean, it's Ginny!" She looked anguished. "I thought it was Ginny!"

Voldemort giggled. "Yes, one of my better performances that day, I must admit. You were almost begging to show it to me, my dear."

Harry summoned the herculean effort necessary to put that revelation behind him. "Alright," he muttered. "Moving on, then. You were about to describe the battle between you and David Monroe."

"Indeed. Mrs. Potter, would you have a seat?" Voldemort pointed with his wand to the chair behind her. Hermione glanced slowly at the chair, then at Harry and back to Voldemort, trying to take in everything around her without seeming to do so.

"I would not advise trying to attack me or escape," Voldemort told her, in a cold, matter-of-fact tone. "Your husband is defenseless and unable to move, and I can incapacitate both of you in less than a second." He looked at Harry. "And you will never hear…the rest of the story."

Harry turned to her. His head moved a fraction, side to side, warning her off of trying anything for now. It would be a desperate chance at best. They needed some kind of lucky break. His eyes moved to the chair, indicating she should sit.

Hermione sat down very slowly, looking at Harry all the while. There wasn't much she could do anyway — her wand was no longer in its hidden pocket in her clothing. As her weight rested on the seat of the chair, fingers reached out from the arms and front legs, grabbing and holding her in place. She squeaked involuntarily, but made no other sound, only looking at Voldemort with loathing.

"Now, to continue," Voldemort resumed; Harry wondered if he detected a hint of impatience in the voice, as if the Dark Lord was anxious to finish his tale and make Harry the offer he had obliquely promised earlier. "I shall not trouble you with the details of our battle — needless to say, we both fought brilliantly. Monroe was nearly my equal in Defense; time and again he managed to evade or deflect my curses, and when I finally tired of the game, I cast the Killing Curse at him, at point-blank range.

"To my very great surprise, I missed."

"He dodged your Killing Curse?" Hermione asked, before Harry could say anything. "Harry's told me you could cast it in less than half a second."

Voldemort raised an eyebrow at Harry. "Ah, you remember that, Mr. Potter? But of course you would now."

"What's that supposed to mean?" Hermione asked suspiciously.

"Nothing," Harry said quickly, but he had a sinking feeling Voldemort wouldn't let it drop.

He didn't. "Your husband found a way around the Interdict of Merlin, Madam Minister," the Dark Lord said, smiling cruelly. "One of the spells he learned was a Memory Enhancing Ritual, a spell that gave him a perfect memory."

Hermione blanched. "What was the ritual's sacrifice?" she asked, tremulously.

"Half his intelligence," Voldemort said flatly. "That's why he's not thinking as fast as you might expect him to."

"Oh, Harry…" Hermione said, sadly. "I'm so sorry —"

"It's done," Harry cut her off, inwardly raging at Voldemort. He'd hoped to spare her that knowledge as well as what he would have to do to avoid being killed by Voldemort because he could no longer be Obliviated or False-Memory Charmed while the spell's effects were still active. Voldemort could remove the ritual, but at the additional cost of half his strength. And if he didn't find some way out of this mess he was going to end up in Azkaban for killing Monroe, along with Ginny who was accused of murdering three Aurors. "What happened after you missed?" he growled at Voldemort, hoping to get off the current topic.

"We exchanged more curses, and Monroe cast a combination that damaged my heart. As I fell I cast a Cutting Hex that split him open from crotch to chest, and we both fell to the ground, mortally wounded.

"Now you might wonder at how I managed to survive this predicament," the Dark Lord murmured. He reached into his robes and produced a wand. "This was my first wand, the wand I bought from Ollivanders in 1938." He held it up for Harry and Hermione to see. "Yew, thirteen and a half inches long, with a phoenix feather core."

Hermione was looking at it curiously in spite of the fear she felt, seeing it in Voldemort's hand. "I've never seen Ginny with that wand."

"She never would have shown it to you, even unknowingly," Voldemort replied. "While she was herself she never knew of its existence." The Dark Lord turned to Harry. "One of the spells I learned from Salazar Slytherin's Monster was a way to link my conscious mind with an object that had had the Horcrux Ritual cast upon it. Normally, when you create a Horcrux it stores only an image of you at a point in time, as I did with the diary and Marvolo Gaunt's ring. With the spell I learned from the Basilisk, however, I could always be linked with that Horcrux, and could move myself between my body and that object."

"What does that mean?" Hermione asked, aghast at the idea.

"I can guess," Harry said grimly. "Even if you were killed, if your wand was a Horcrux it could only be destroyed by Basilisk venom or Fiendfyre, and you made sure the Basilisk was dealt with after you took Slytherin's knowledge from it. Am I wrong in thinking that you could influence people who touched your wand, just as Ginny was influenced by you during the time she had your diary?"

"Yes, quite," Voldemort nodded, a cold smile on his lips. "I learned that my wand had been kept by Dumbledore after Quirrell's death in 1992, and I was able to take control of Ginny, having her make her way into Dumbledore's office one day when he was away, and into that room of black pedestals and silver light, where he kept the spoils of his adventures. My wand — this wand — had been placed there after my defeat, and while my diary still had a measure of control over her, you suspected Ginny was being manipulated, somehow; I knew I would have to give up the diary, so I determined to get my wand back and maintain my control of Ginny. I Transfigured a replica of my wand, using Salazar's magic to make it permanent, and left it in place of mine."

Hermione was shaking her head, her eyes wide with horror. "You mean you were in control of Ginny all that time since her first year?"

Voldemort almost looked offended. "Of course not, Mrs. Potter. I had no wish to operate out of the body of an eleven-year old girl! I had her give the wand to a more suitable, shall we say, body donor."

Harry and Hermione's eyes locked for a moment. It had taken six more years for Voldemort to return after Quirrell's defeat, but he had returned, and in a form that no one could have suspected hid the Dark Lord.

He returned in the body of Percy Weasley.

Percy, who'd left Hogwarts in 1994 as Head Boy, had secured a post at the Ministry of Magic working for Cornelius Fudge as his personal assistant. By the time Fudge had worn out his usefulness to the Malfoys and was replaced by Rufus Scrimgeour, Percy had become an undersecretary in the International Magical Office of Law, and Scrimgeour had put him on track to become Senior Undersecretary to the Minister himself in a few more years. If Harry and Dumbledore had not realized that there were still Horcruxes out there tying Voldemort to the material world, he might have gone on to become Minister.

After Percy left Hogwarts he estranged himself from his parents, brothers and sister; it had seemed strange at the time, but in retrospect it made sense. He kept no close relationships, throwing himself into his Ministry work and building up a network of contacts in the Ministry, where he was well-regarded as a hard worker and brilliant at his job. His mother Molly had fretted and cried over his aloofness, continually nagging her husband Arthur to invite Percy home for dinner, but the younger Weasley refused all of his father's overtures.

Harry was ready to leave Hogwarts by the time he and Professor Dumbledore puzzled out the riddle of the resurrected Quirrell. Quirrell's body was still in the Department of Mysteries, carefully watched by the Unspeakables for any sign of movement or life. It would still be there except that Hermione had had it removed after she became Minister, having it placed in an unmarked grave somewhere in Albania. Now, Harry realized, it made sense how "Quirrell" could have come back in Percy Weasley's body.

Voldemort's wand.

But there were still unanswered questions. "You still haven't said what happened after you and Monroe were both mortally wounded in battle with one another," Harry reminded him.

"Ah, yes," Voldemort nodded. "It is important you know this, Mr. Potter, since that knowledge is relevant to the offer I will make you."

"What offer?" Hermione asked, looking back and forth between them.

"Patience, Mrs. Potter," Voldemort told her. "You will hear, soon enough. As I have so far recounted, both Monroe and I were grievously wounded. My heart would not last much longer, and he was bleeding out; even though he managed to slow the bleeding with magic, he could not stop it without dittany or specialized potions. But he would die happy, he told me, because I had been stopped.

"Imagine his disappointment, then, when I told him that I would not die, that I had gone further than any other wizard in my quest for immortality. He would not believe me until I told him of Salazar Slytherin's knowledge, knowledge I had gained from the Monster of Slytherin decades earlier. I began to cast a spell that would draw his life from his body and use it to heal my own damaged form.

"Monroe fought me, even then," Voldemort told them. "He held onto life longer than I would have thought possible. I began to fear that my heart would give out before I would be able to heal it. Then Monroe did something that surprised both of us.

"'Riddle, you foul, Dark creature,'" he said to me, "'what will a spell of Light do to your Horcrux?!'" He cast his Patronus, an eagle that flew directly at me, as if I were a Dementor to be repelled by its form. I held up my wand to defend myself, but the Patronus flew into it and disappeared. At that same moment Monroe's life slipped from his body into me, and my heart was restored.

"But something else had happened to me. It was as if my and Monroe's minds had merged, like mutual Legilimency run amok. Everything he knew, I knew as well. We had become one person."

"That's unbelievable," Harry said. "It's really unbelievable! Patronuses can't do that! They're under the control of the person who cast them — they can't be constrained or held against the caster's will!"

"Have you ever cast your Patronus into an object that's had the Horcrux Ritual performed on it?" Voldemort asked. Harry didn't answer. "No, I'm sure you haven't, Mr. Potter. You've only ever used your Patronus on Dementors, haven't you?"

"You would know that," Harry growled. "You saw me destroy one."

Voldemort nodded. "I suppose in a way I should be grateful for that, Mr. Potter, for that Dementor did tell me that it would hunt me down someday, for depriving it of its sustenance — you."

Harry snorted laughter. He had never heard a Dementor speak — not even the one at Hermione's trial that Harry had used to show the Wizengamot that he could scare a Dementor into retreating from him. They couldn't speak—what wizards thought they heard were words plucked from their own minds by the fear and despair induced by the Dementor's presence.

It occurred to Harry that he really should have destroyed all of the Dementors at Azkaban before now, because he had managed to deduce what Voldemort planned to offer him. "You want me to send my Patronus into your wand," he said, flatly. "To join to you like Monroe did."

Voldemort nodded. "Very good, Mr. Potter — I wasn't certain you were keeping up. It would be quite advantageous to have a perfect memory, and our overall intelligence would not decrease very much; both Monroe and I were quite brilliant, and even at half your intelligence you have a keen and agile mind."

"Harry," Hermione said quietly, though he could hear the tenseness in her voice. "Tell me you are not thinking of doing anything of the sort."

Harry was frowning. "What about Ginny?" he asked. "What can you do for her?" Hermione's mouth fell open.

Voldemort was shaking his head slowly. "Three murders, Mr. Potter. And of three Aurors. It will be impossible to manipulate the Ministry to ignore those three deaths. Ginny could just as easily be guilty of Monroe's death, and of trying to kill you as well, if you decide to join with me. Draco can remain the Head Auror for a while longer, and your considerable wealth can be used to, shall we say, direct policies advantageous to the pureblood families of the Wizengamot and the Wizarding community."

"Hermione will remain as Minister of Magic?" Harry asked.

"There will be no reason for her to resign as long as you are willing to cooperate with me — with us."

"You and Monroe?" Harry said, for clarification.

"And Quirrell," Voldemort added. "Did you not wonder at his role in my return?"

Harry shrugged. "I thought you had simply taken over his body as some point before you arrived at Hogwarts, like you did Ginny's."

"Quirrell," Voldemort informed them, "was quite interested in the Dark Lord's exploits, especially what happened to him after he attempted to kill a young Harry Potter and disappeared, seemingly destroyed. He suspected, as few wizards did, that the Dark Lord had found a way to tie himself to the physical world. His investigations eventually led him to Godric's Hollow and the remains of the Potter house. The burst of magic that had incinerated the Dark Lord's body had also broken the Fidelius, and his remains had been removed, but his wand had never been found — it was assumed destroyed by the same power that reduced him to a burnt corpse.

"But Quirrell believed otherwise, fortunately," Voldemort went on. He searched the ruins of the Potter home very carefully, and found the wand buried beneath the remains of a wall that had toppled over on it."

"And you rewarded him by possessing his body," Harry muttered.

"I rewarded him by giving him the option of joining with me," Voldemort demurred. "An offer which he accepted eagerly."

"But Quirrell couldn't produce a Patronus," Hermione objected.

"Of course he could," Voldemort replied shortly. "When you met him we had already been joined for some time; he knew better than to admit he could produce a Patronus. Now," and Voldemort's gaze returned to Harry, "are you willing to join yourself to me, Mr. Potter, so that we can continue to improve Wizarding Britain?"

Harry sat silent for nearly a minute before holding out his hand. "I'll need a wand to produce a Patronus," he said, quietly. Hermione caught her breath, not believing what she was seeing.

"Of course," Voldemort said. He reversed his wand so the handle was toward Harry, holding it out toward him. Harry's hand moved toward the wand…then stopped. He withdrew his hand, looking at Voldemort's wand.

"I don't think I'm going to touch your wand," he said, shaking his head. "I suspect that you would be able to exert a lot of influence over me once I did."

"Your suspicions are warranted," Voldemort nodded, withdrawing the wand. "But I have my own suspicions, and putting any wand in your hand other than mine would be a powerful incentive for you to try and escape your current predicament."

That was true. Harry had seen Voldemort's offer as a way to get his hands on a wand and make a break for it. If the Dark Lord hadn't held out his own wand, it would have been the perfect opportunity — he would have had to reach for another wand while Harry would have one in hand. But Harry couldn't take a chance that he could resist the influence the Horcrux wand could have over him.

"I suppose I have to refuse your offer, then," Harry said. "Even though it means Ginny and I will go to Azkaban." He turned to his wife. "You're going to have to be strong, Hermione. You have to find a way to remain Minister of Magic after all this goes down, don't let Draco Malfoy take over —" His voice cut off suddenly as Voldemort gestured toward him.

"Enough of that, Mr. Potter," the Dark Lord ordered. "In any event, she won't remember any of this conversation, so anything you say here will be moot."

Hermione began to speak but she suddenly slumped in her chair, asleep. "It is too bad you continue to resist me, Mr. Potter — we could have been a formidable opponent with your abilities added to our own. You were merely lucky before —"

"Twice before," Harry reminded him. "I beat you at the end of my first year and again just before I left Hogwarts." He shook his head sadly. "All the things you were capable of back then — it's a shame you remained a Dark wizard. You know, I never found that spell you said Monroe taught you, the one…"

Harry stopped. A number of disparate memories were coming together in his brain. If Voldemort could move his consciousness between a body and one of his Horcruxes…

"Pioneer 11," Harry said suddenly, his voice a near-whisper. "You told me you snuck into NASA and cast a spell on the golden plaque that would make

it last a lot longer than it otherwise would. You performed the Horcrux Ritual on it!"

Voldemort was actually grinning. "I had already created three Horcruxes by then, but the idea that my consciousness would move outward into space, forever, was too enticing to ignore."

"And that spell —" Harry prompted, dreading the answer. "The spell that showed the stars…"

"An alternate form of possession," Voldemort replied. "One in which I allowed you to see through my senses rather than me taking over your mind. That was what was so draining, Mr. Potter — not the movement between my mind and the Plaque Horcrux."

Harry shuddered. "I can't believe I actually enjoyed that — that aberration."

"I have learned from my aberrations, Mr. Potter," the Dark Lord replied. "A pity you have not." He waved his wand at Harry. Everything faded to black.

=ooo=

The Most Ancient Hall of the Wizengamot was filled well past its capacity. Many more wizards that those fifty or so souls who were its Lords and Ladies had found their way into that Most August Place. Wizards from across Britain, Europe, and even Scandinavia and Asia Minor had made the trek to that most ancient repository of magical power. They came because something unique was about to occur — today the Wizengamot would humble one of their own number, give him over to the horrors of Azkaban. To be sure, this was not the first time this had happened to one of the nobles of the Wizengamot. But it was the first time anyone had seen Harry Potter brought so low.

Testimony had been given, under Veritaserum, and the Wizengamot was currently "discussing" the idea of placing the arguably most well-known person in Wizarding Britain in the very place he had once threatened to destroy. For some there the irony was delicious. For others it was unthinkable. But soon, it would be decided one way or the other.

The Hall was now filled with the noise of a hundred muttered conversations, in a dozen different languages. The only person in the Hall who wasn't speaking, it seemed, was the man hunched in the iron chair in the center of the room, chains wrapped around his arms and legs. He sat, staring straight ahead, eyes focused on nothing, contemplating the confession he had just given the Wizengamot. He believed everything he had said, as alien as it had sounded as he'd said it. He had killed James Monroe in a cold, jealous rage after learning that he and Ginny Thomas planned to run away together, that she was leaving Britain after killing three Aurors who had come to her home searching for information on Harry Potter. She had been protecting Harry, she'd said during her own trial, all of which Harry also believed, though he could not quite wrap his head around the idea that Ginny would kill three Aurors.

The other person in the Hall who wasn't engaged in deliberation or debate, the Chief Warlock of the Wizengamot, stared down at Harry with sad, tired eyes. In contrast to Harry, he disbelieved everything that the Head Auror (and now acting Minister of Magic) had claimed about Harry and the Thomas woman, who was already on her way to Azkaban, having been roundly convicted of the charges that had been leveled against her. Neither of these trials rang true to the Chief Warlock, but the defendants had been questioned under Veritaserum and had confessed to their crimes. The Wizengamot had voted to convict Ginny Thomas, and they would shortly convict Harry Potter of murder. It mattered not what the Chief Warlock believed about either of them or the likelihood that they had actually committed the crimes they were accused of and had confessed to. Never mind that Veritaserum was ineffective against False Memory Charms and Obliviation when the memories altered or removed did not introduce noticeable inconsistency in the witness's story.

It was time. The Chief Warlock tapped the dark stone rod held in his hand against the podium, silencing the Hall. "I call for the vote," he said in a strong, clear voice that belied his internal turmoil. "By a show of hands, those who believe Harry Potter to be guilty of murder."

Too many hands rose in the air, the Chief Warlock saw. But that was a foregone conclusion. Harry himself had confessed to the murder, and Ginny Thomas's testimony as an eye witness had confirmed it. When the vote was tallied, only one or two of the members had not raised their hands. "By a show of hands," the Chief Warlock continued, "those who believe Harry Potter to be innocent of the charge of murder."

No plum-colored sleeves rose into the air. After an interminable silence, the Chief Warlock spoke once again. "The vote of guilty is carried by majority. Thus orders the Wizengamot. The sentence of life in Azkaban shall be carried out immediately. Aurors, please escort the prisoner out and remand him to the warden of Azkaban. Having no other business to conduct, this session of the Wizengamot is hereby adjourned."

The Aurors guarding Harry removed the chains from his arms and legs and helped him to his feet. He moved slowly, the Chief Warlock saw, and looked weaker than when they were last together, in happier times. As the Aurors took Harry's arms to help him walk he looked up toward the Chief Warlock with a wan smile. "Nice to see you again, Remus," he said, softly. "Even if the circumstances are less than pleasant."

Remus Lupin nodded, his lips pressed tightly together. He could not speak. There was nothing he could say to Harry that could convey the anguish he felt at sending the son of his dearest friends to prison for a crime he wouldn't have, couldn't have committed.

As the Aurors led him away, Harry looked back over his shoulder. "Don't be such a stranger," he murmured, then let the Aurors lead him from the room.

A/N: Harry's in a serious fix now, isn't he? Well, sometimes the bad guy wins… Reviews, comments, questions invited.

Chapter 28: The Return

Updated 4/27/2013

=ooo=

"I'm not just giving up!" Harry said flatly, and Sirius nodded agreement.

"Giving up isn't like you, Moony," Sirius added. "Especially against the powers that be. We've got to get out of here now and find someplace else to hole up!" He grinned suddenly, an idea coming to mind. "Say, what if we go up to Hogwarts and sneak into the Room of Requirement? We were always pretty safe there!"

"That's not a bad idea," Harry agreed. "When Monroe and I were in Hogwarts we held off Malfoy and a group of Aurors — they didn't know our exact reason for being in there, and the Room won't let you in if you don't how the current occupants got in there. Remus, we've got to try!"

Remus did not look nearly as confident as Harry and Sirius did. "Just getting into Hogwarts won't be easy," he objected. "And the security system Harry talked about will be able to find us anywhere in the castle —"

"Except the Room of Requirement!" Harry pointed out. "Even the Marauder's Map couldn't find anyone hidden in there!"

"And there's the matter of Mrs. Thomas upstairs," Remus went on. "She needs time to rest and recuperate from the neglect she suffered in Azkaban. I don't think she should be moved."

"We can drop her off in the infirmary at Hogwarts," Sirius suggested. "If that spitfire of a nurse is still there, she won't let anyone take her until she's fully recovered, not even the Minister of Magic!"

"Madam Pomfrey is still there," Harry confirmed. "And yeah, you're right about her, Sirius! Good plan!" He turned back to Remus. "You don't have to go with us, you can stay and wait for the Aurors if you want, but we're going."

Lupin looked conflicted, but he finally nodded. "Alright, let's try it your way," he said. "Meet me upstairs," and he Disapparated. A moment later Harry and Sirius joined him in the drawing room, where Remus was picking up Ginny so he could carry her. Without a word he turned and left the drawing room, moving quietly down the hallway toward the front door. Harry and Sirius followed closely, looking warily at the curtains covering the portrait of Sirius's mother.

At the front door Remus spoke softly. "Harry, you or Sirius create a Portkey to get us to the gates of Hogwarts. From there it's going to be difficult, especially if Headmaster Longbottom doesn't want us there."

"Don't worry about Neville," Harry said. "He's no fan of Draco Malfoy, either. Of course, I don't want to impose on his hospitality too much, so the less he knows about what we're doing there, the better."

Sirius held up an umbrella he'd taken from the troll leg umbrella stand further back in the hallway. "This'll do for a Portkey, won't it?" he asked. "And it'll come in handy if it's raining in Scotland!" He tapped the umbrella with the wand he carried and said, "Portus." The wand flashed blue. "Okay, it'll go in 30 seconds," he said. "Everyone grab hold."

"Outside," Lupin ordered. "Too much residual magic will be held in the walls and floor if we do it here, in closed quarters." Harry opened the front door and Lupin, still carrying Ginny, hurried outside.

"Harry!" Sirius said, getting his attention, then tossed him the umbrella. "Be there in a second."

"Hurry up!" Harry said, then followed Remus outside. What could Sirius be doing?

Lupin had moved away from number 12 and into the grassy square that the other houses surrounded. "Where'd Sirius go?" he asked anxiously as Harry caught up to him.

"He's doing something, I don't know —" A woman's shrill screams suddenly came from the doorway of number 12.

"Scum! Filth! Traitors of our blood! Begone from my home, all of you!" The screams diminished as Sirius exited the front door, closing it behind him, and cut off entirely as he pointed his wand at the door. He jogged out to where Harry and Remus were standing, with Ginny still held in Remus's arms.

"Thought I'd give anyone going in there something to listen to," he grinned as Harry held out the umbrella.

"Very droll," Remus commented dryly, taking Ginny's hand and holding it against the umbrella along with his own. "Hurry up!" he commanded, and Sirius reached out and put a finger on the handle just as the umbrella flashed blue and they all vanished in a whirlwind of color and sound.

Moments later Harry was looking up at the large iron gates of Hogwarts, flanked by columns with winged pigs along their tops. He shivered; it was a cold day, with an icy breeze making the temperature even more uncomfortable. There was a thin layer of snow on the grounds. Harry could see a single track of footprints in the snow, rather large ones, in fact, leading up to the gate then away again. They were likely Hagrid's footprints, when he'd come and unlocked the gates for the day.

It wasn't that long ago that he'd come here with Monroe to seek out information in the Chamber of Secrets, then ended up playing cat-and-mouse with Malfoy and his Aurors. He, Monroe and Ginny had managed to escape, but it wasn't long after that Ginny revealed herself to be possessed by Voldemort, who killed Monroe and framed Harry with his death. Along the way he'd killed three Aurors; their deaths were blamed on Ginny, too, because it appeared to be her who'd killed them.

At that moment Remus was transferring Ginny's unconscious form to Sirius. "Now hold still," he said, taking another wand from his robes and tapping Ginny on the head. She began to fade from view as the Disillusionment Charm took effect, and Remus followed suit with Sirius, Harry, and then himself. "Now let's get out of this cold," his voice said, and the gates slowly swung open.

"Sirius, you lead the way," Remus's voice said. "Harry, find his shoulder and put your hand on it. I'll bring up the rear, to cover our tracks." Harry found Sirius's shoulder, and the invisible Marauder began walking towards the front steps of the castle. Harry felt Remus's hand on his shoulder, then looked down and back at their footsteps in the snow. A few paces behind them the footprints were disappearing as Remus "repaired" them.

"I'm glad you came with us," Harry said quietly to Remus as they walked. "I think we have a real chance of exposing Malfoy as Voldemort."

"We're not going to do it from Hogwarts unless we get Malfoy to come here with the Marauder's Map," Lupin whispered back. "Which, come to think of it, if he figures out we're here he may actually do. He wouldn't need Longbottom's cooperation that way. You and Sirius may be onto something here, Harry!"

They continued up the path towards the front doors of the school, Sirius leading the way with Ginny in his arms and Remus covering their tracks from the rear. Sirius stopped at the front steps, looking up at them. Snow had been cleared off the front steps and an area beyond them, so they were no longer standing in snow. "Now what?" Sirius whispered over his shoulder. "Ready to head inside?"

"There'll be students in the hallways," Remus warned. "Fortunately, unless the class times have changed we have several minutes before the next class ends." They ascended the steps and paused in front of the double oaken doors.

As Sirius reached toward the door handle, however, Remus hissed "Stop!" just loud enough for him to hear. "Don't open it!"

"What's wrong?" Sirius whispered. "We can sneak past a bunch of students, Moony!"

"Not students — Aurors!" Remus whispered urgently. "There are several in the entrance hall, probably Disillusioned like us!"

"How do you know?" Harry whispered.

"I have detection charms to let me know when any Auror gets within 50 feet of me," Remus whispered in reply. "Malfoy has them watching me all the time."

"So what do we do now?" Sirius wanted to know. "This bird is starting to get heavy."

"We need to find an alternate entrance," Remus said. "I wonder if there are Aurors posted at the eastern entrance…"

They made their way back down the steps and walked around the north side of the castle to the east side where the greenhouses were located. Remus had Sirius enter one of the greenhouses, which were several degrees warmer than the outside temperature, and told them to wait there while he checked out the east exit himself.

Ending their Disillusionment spells, Harry found an old wheelbarrow in a corner and Transfigured it into a cot for Ginny; Sirius laid her down on it, then looked her over carefully. "She seems okay," he muttered. "I'm sure glad that potion Remus gave us didn't put me to sleep!"

"It made me drowsy," Harry said. "But I couldn't sleep until I'd talked to Remus about getting us hidden and letting him know about Voldemort. Too bad Tonks had to screw up our Fidelius on your house."

"Ehh," Sirius shrugged. "I'm just glad she didn't go the way most of the Blacks went — to the Dark side, or at best becoming a blood-purity bigot. Mind, she might have cut her cousin Sirius a little bit more slack than she did."

"She might've wanted to cut Remus some slack," Harry commented.

"Heh heh," Sirius chuckled. "You notice that, too? She called him 'Remus' at one point. She sounded like she fancied him a bit."

"Well, he is the Chief Warlock," Harry noted. "He'd be quite a catch."

"What about your wife, Harry?" Sirius asked. "You haven't said much about her."

Harry shook his head. "Not much to say. She was Minister of Magic from 2004 on, until Malfoy (Voldemort, really) framed me for James Monroe's murder, which forced her to resign and leave public life."

"You two met at Hogwarts?" Sirius asked.

"Before, actually," Harry replied. "We met on the Hogwarts Express. Professor McGonagall told me to look for a girl named Hermione Granger on the train to Hogwarts."

Sirius looked bemused. "Funny," he muttered. "I wouldn't have taken McGonagall for a matchmaker."

Harry laughed. "Neither would I, given the interesting time I had with her on our trip to Diagon Alley."

"Your wife, or McGonagall?"

Harry laughed again, but before he could reply they heard Remus's voice outside the greenhouse. "Coming in," he said softly, and the door opened and closed. Remus appeared a moment later. "It's no good," he said at once. "They've got Aurors stationed at the east entrance as well."

"Were they expecting us?" Harry asked.

"It's hard to tell," Remus answered. "I don't think they expected us to come here — they're just covering the school as a contingency. Still, it's going to make it difficult to get inside. It will also be difficult to drop Mrs. Thomas off in the infirmary and make it to the Room of Requirement afterward."

"Moony, there were all sorts of ways in and out of the castle when we were in school," Sirius objected. "Surely you can remember some of them!"

Remus looked thoughtful for several moments. "Well, there's that one-eyed witch statue near the Defense Against the Dark Arts classroom, it leads to the cellar of Honeydukes," he finally said. "And that mirror on the fourth floor has a passage that leads to the shed behind the Hog's Head Inn."

"We need one a bit closer," Sirius argued. "I don't want to walk all the way to Hogsmeade then back to the castle, especially carrying someone! It's getting a bit tiring."

"I can carry Ginny," Harry spoke up.

"No you can't," Remus disagreed. "You're even weaker than Sirius is right now." He rubbed his chin thoughtfully. "Well, I know of one passage that's fairly close, but we hardly ever used it because of where it came out — in Hagrid's cabin."

"Oh, yeah," Sirius nodded, grinning. "That's how the big guy could make it to Dumbledore's office in a minute or so from the grounds — he had his own private passageway!"

"Best of all," Remus went on, "in the castle the entrance to the passage is behind a large picture that's about halfway between Dumbledore's office and the Room of Requirement."

"So all we have to do is sneak into Hagrid's cabin, find the secret entrance, and make our way into Hogwarts and then to the Room of Requirement," Harry finished, with an ironic smile.

"Basically," Remus agreed, smiling as well.

"Then let's get going," Sirius, who was better at making ironic comments than inferring them, said. "After I have another minute or two to rest my arms, that is."

=ooo=

Tonks reappeared near the employee entrance to the Ministry, a shabby pub that had been closed and its windows boarded over for a few decades now. The building next to it was an accountancy shop; the gap between the two buildings looked too narrow for even a child to slip into, but when a witch or wizard approached it expanded by a couple of feet, allowing access down a corridor to the back of the pub, where a password-protected door guarded the room where most Ministry employees went to travel to the Ministry proper.

Tonks tapped the door with her wand, murmuring the password for the day, "International cooperation." The password changed every day for each employee — it was given out as each person left the Ministry. If you were sick or had a holiday you had to owl the Auror Department for your next day's password. The door opened and Tonks quickly slipped inside.

Inside was a long, narrow room lined with a half-dozen fireplaces, allowing employees to Floo to the Atrium. She grabbed a pinch of Floo powder, threw it into the fireplace, which flared up with emerald green flames, and said clearly, "Ministry of Magic Atrium!"

Moments later she bolted from the Atrium fireplace, heading toward the elevators. It was probably too late to catch Black and Potter at Grimmauld Place (unless Remus persuaded them to stay, which she doubted), but that was just as well — getting any reasonable number of Aurors into Black's house through the Fidelius Charm Lupin had cast was going to be a big problem.

Tonks was bouncing on her toes waiting for the elevator to make its interminable way to level one, where the Minister's office was located. She shot out of the elevator the moment the doors opened, heading straight for the Minister's office. The only problem she might have now was —

"Can I help you, Auror Tonks?"

"Yes, Goyle, you can let me past so I can talk to your boss," Tonks sighed, knowing she would have to endure what Goyle thought passed for flirting.

"He's been waiting for you to return," Goyle said casually. "It looks like you even beat Lupin back to the Ministry."

"Lupin's not coming back to the Ministry," Tonks snapped, curtly. "That's what I've got to talk to the Minister about. Are you going to let me in or what?"

"Sure, Tonksie, sure," Goyle grinned, then tapped a box sitting on the desk with his wand. "Auror Tonks to see you, sir," he said, in a now very businesslike tone.

"Send her in," Malfoy's voice replied a moment later, and Goyle gestured toward the door with a smile (more of a leer, really). Tonks ignored him and walked into the Minister's office.

The Minister's office was a lot different than it had been only a month ago, Tonks remembered, though she had been in this office more times in the past month than in all her previous 22 years of being an Auror. Malfoy tended to keep close tabs on Ministry personnel, including the Chief Warlock.

Malfoy was reading something on his desk, a stack of parchments that he did not look up from as she came to an "at-ease" stance in front of his desk. No matter how urgent the news, one did not rush Minister Malfoy when he was working. The longer she stood there, however, the more Tonks wondered just how upset he was going to be when he found out the news she had for him.

"I don't believe Lupin has returned yet," Malfoy said suddenly, without looking up at her. "You showing up before him leads me to think you have some interesting news for me. Do you?"

"Yes, very interesting," Tonks said, feeling suddenly breathless. This was going to be difficult to explain — with Lupin's Fidelius Charm in effect, she could not say or otherwise communicate in any way the location of Black and Potter. "I followed Lupin to a place where he met with Harry Potter and Sirius Black."

Malfoy looked up at her sharply. "Where?"

"I can't say, sir."

"You can't say?" Malfoy echoed. "Can you explain, at least?"

"A Fidelius is in effect, one that I was accidentally included in," Tonks answered.

"So you're a Secret Keeper?" Malfoy surmised.

"Yes, sir. I tried to take Black and Potter prisoner, but Lupin somehow figured out that I was inside his Fidelius when he cast it, he and the others were able to take me prisoner." Her hair went red at her final statement, mirroring her embarrassment.

"But you were obviously able to escape," Malfoy added. "Otherwise you would not be here. Unless…"

"My identity code for today is Hippogriff-Nogtail-Billywig-Unicorn," Tonks immediately rattled off, anticipating Malfoy's next question. Aurors had to memorize a new identity code each day so they could prove they weren't being impersonated by a Metamorphmage (pretty rare) or Polyjuiced witch or wizard (much more likely).

"And what was your identity code for yesterday?" Malfoy continued. It was unlikely someone impersonating an Auror would think to get both today and yesterday's identity codes.

"Hag-Banshee-Nundu-Ukrainian Ironbelly," Tonks recited. Malfoy nodded, convinced Tonks was who she said she was.

"Do you think they're still where you left them?" Malfoy asked. He wasn't surprised when she shook her head; they would all have to be idiots to remain there after their Fidelius was breached, and Lupin, at least ,was no idiot.

"Any idea where they might have gone?" he continued, but Tonks' response was again negative. That was disappointing.

"Not many places they could go, though," Tonks offered. "To the Weasleys, maybe. I understand they own a house in Grimmauld Square. But if Lupin is helping them they could be out of the country by now."

"Perhaps," Malfoy mused, "but Potter won't be content to simply run away from his problems — he'll want to confront them head-on. He's always been that way."

Malfoy stood, his demeanor becoming crisp and businesslike. "Crabbe! Goyle!" he shouted. A few moments later both men were standing at attention on either side of Tonks. "Put all off-duty Auror and Hit Wizard teams on standby," Malfoy told them. "I already have teams stationed in certain key locations — if we hear of anything from them we're going to converge on that location like the wrath of Merlin. Meanwhile, I have a short list of people and places we need to watch for any unusual activity: Fred and George Weasley, Molly and Arthur Weasley, Gringotts, Bill Weasley and Ollivanders, and Ron Weasley. And Dean Thomas, too." The Weasley name had come up quite a few times in that short list, Tonks noted.

"Yes, Minister," Crabbe said, and he and Goyle both strode from the room, leaving Tonks alone with Malfoy, who sat down at his desk and began rearranging stacks of parchment. After a few moments he seemed to remember Tonks was there and glanced up at her.

"You can go, Auror Tonks," he said dismissively. She had been considering asking him about what Potter had said about Voldemort, but decided against it. At best it would piss him off, and at worst…

Well, Potter couldn't be right about that, could he? But if Lupin believed him, what should she think about it?

"Should I be on any of those surveillance teams, Minister?"

Malfoy raised an eyebrow at her. "Did you hear me tell you you were on any of those teams, Auror?"

"Er — no, sir," Tonks admitted. That had been a bad question, she berated herself.

"Do you want me to let you know if Lupin returns, sir?" she went on, wondering what Malfoy would do if Lupin actually showed up at the Ministry now.

"If I'm here, that's fine," Malfoy answered in a distracted tone. "But if we get even a whiff of Potter or Black I'll be out until further notice." Without looking up he pointed at the door. Tonks got the hint and left posthaste.

Back at her desk Tonks watched as the whirlwind of activity Malfoy's orders had generated slowly died down, as Auror Teams left for their assignments. Her hair was doing a cycle of black and gold (Hufflepuff's colors) as she realized she would be one of the few Aurors left at the Ministry along with the desk jockies and those too new to have proven themselves in the field just yet. Malfoy had, in effect, shunted her to one side.

Well, there was one name that wasn't on that list, and Tonks suspected she hadn't heard what had been going on with Harry Potter. She would have to pay a quick visit and fill her in. Tonks stood, casually made her way to the lifts and down to the Atrium, then disappeared through an outgoing Floo.

=ooo=

Mr. Rubeus Hagrid puffed contentedly on a pipe as he cut up tubers into a large iron pot sitting on the scrubbed table in the middle of his cabin. Hagrid's black beared had hints of salt and pepper in it, but he showed no sign of slowing down in his duties as groundskeeper for Hogwarts.

Just outside his window, two pairs of Disillusioned eyes stared at him through the dusty glass. "How do you suggest we work this?" Harry whispered. "Just rush in and Stun him?"

"He's a half-giant," Remus reminded him. "A Stunner won't stop him. A half-dozen probably wouldn't, either. Whatever we do, it's going to have to be pretty powerful magic."

"Well, hurry up and think of something," Sirius whispered irritably. "This girl isn't getting any lighter — I'd like to drop her on Hagrid's bed and be done with her!"

Lupin put up a hand signaling for silence, then turned and looked at Sirius thoughtfully. "You know, Sirius, that's not a bad idea. Hagrid's always responded well when someone becomes sick or injured around him. Perhaps we can use that to our advantage."

"What are you suggesting?" Harry wanted to know. "That we walk into Hagrid's cabin and ask him to take care of Ginny?"

"That I walk in," Lupin clarified. "He'll remember me as a past professor as well as the current Chief Warlock, and it's unlikely he's heard details about the breakout at Azkaban. Also, he's not much of a Malfoy supporter, from what I've heard. I think I can get him to take Mrs. Thomas to the infirmary. Once there, Madam Pomfrey is unlikely to let anyone remove her until she's well, and the headmaster will back her up."

Harry and Sirius nodded agreement, and a few moments later Hagrid looked up at the sudden knock at his door. A furious, high-pitched yipping also sounded throughout the cabin, and Hagrid muttered, "Al righ', Claw, keep yer shirt on, we'll see who it is." He stood and in just three steps was at the door, opening it to finding Remus Lupn holding the unconscious form of a red-headed woman.

"Perfesser Lupin!" Hagrid exclaimed. "I ain't seen you in a boarhound's age! What're yeh doing back at Hogwarts?"

"Hello, Hagrid," Lupin greeted him, his voice slightly strained. Sirius had been right — Ginny Thomas was heavier than she looked. "As you can see, I have a bit of a problem here — this woman is unconscious and I believe she's in need of medical help."

"Well, come in, come in, don' stand out there in the cold jawin'," Hagrid insisted, and watch as Lupin stepped inside, looking around the cabin. "Put 'er on my bed," Hagrid said, as the yipping started up again, and Lupin stepped over to the massive bed, laying Ginny's body on the quilt covering it. "Quiet, Claw!" Hagrid snapped, and the yipping cut off. "Sorry," he muttered. "Claw barks at ennyone he don't know." Lupin glanced around, finally seeing a very small dog, a Jack Russell terrier, staring up at him suspiciously.

"A bit of a change from your last dog," Lupin told Hagrid, smiling.

"Yeh," Hagrid nodded. "Well, after Fang… passed —" he said this with a catch in his throat. "I figgered I'd see how well a smaller dog would do here wit' me." Hagrid was scratching his chin as he stared at the woman on his bed. "Looks like one of the Weasleys, don't she? What happened to her?"

"I'm not sure," Lupin hedged.

"Why dincha bring her up to the infirmary, then?" Hagrid wanted to know.

"I found her not far from your cabin," Lupin answered. "I wanted to see if there was something I could do before taking her up to Madam Pomfrey."

Hagrid cocked his head at Lupin. "So? Whadja figger out, Perfesser?"

"Oh," Lupin said, and took out his wand. He passed it over Ginny's unconscious form several times, then looked up at Hagrid. "She doesn't have any injuries, external or internal. I think she just passed out. I suppose we can take her to the infirmary and let Madam Pomfrey do a more detailed examination."

"I s'pose," Hagrid agreed, but there was a hesitation in his voice. "You know, Perfesser, this kinda looks like Ginny Weaseley — er, Thomas, I mean. I thought she was in Azkaban these days." He was giving Lupin a calculating look. "So whut's really goin' on here, Perfesser?"

"You're right, Hagrid," Lupin replied, "this is Ginny Thomas. I found her at my home over lunch, along with a note from Harry Potter asking me to take care of her, that she had been near death in Azkaban when he and Sirius Black escaped and she needed medical care. I gave her a potion to help her recover but she needs more time, and I'm afraid if I drop her off at St. Mungo's the Ministry will simply throw her back in prison, where she will die shortly thereafter. I think there were details of the crimes she was accused of that were not properly presented; I want an opportunity to reexamine them. Meanwhile, I believe she will be safer here at Hogwarts than anywhere else. I'd like you to bring her to Madam Pomfrey while I work on her case."

"Hmm," Hagrid scratched his chin. "What happened to Black an' Harry Potter, then?" he asked.

"They had gone by the time I arrived home," Lupin said. "I don't know where they might have gone. They could be anywhere by now."

"Yeh, I s'pose," Hagrid agreed. "Well, I don' see the harm in takin' her to Madam Pomfrey. Only —" and the half-giant looked around the room conspiratorially before continuing, "I gotta short cut inter the castle, Perfesser, and I'd 'preciate it if yeh didn't tell ennyone about it, if yeh catch my drift."

"Of course not, Hagrid," Lupin agreed immediately.

Hagrid nodded solemnly, then pulled the chairs around his scrubbed wooden table out from beneath it and slid the table over against a wall, exposing the floor beneath it. Hagrid went to over to his chest of drawers and fished around in the top drawer for a few moments, finally coming up with an iron ring that he slipped onto his index finger. With a grin toward Lupin, he went back where the table had been, leanind over and touching a knot in the floor with the ring. He pulled upward, and a large trap door suddenly appeared, swinging upward to reveal a staircase leading downward.

"Kinda handy when I need a quick word wit' the Headmaster," Hagrid commented, going over to the bed and picking up Ginny. He walked back to the opening, then looked at Lupin. "Are yeh goin' with us, Perfesser? Yeh might need ter explain to Madam Pomfrey."

"You'll be fine, Hagrid," Lupin assured him. "I need to get back to the Ministry and help continue the search for Black and Potter. Hagrid nodded and began walking down the steps. It seemed improbable that he would be able to fit down the passageway but within moments he was out of sight.

"Interesting," Remus commented to himself, then went over and opened the front door. The sound of footsteps were heard, then a pair of cracking sounds as Harry and Sirius appeared, their Disillusionment Charms dissipating.

There was another round of furious yipping as Claw objected to their presence, but Sirius looked at the terrier and growled, "Go lie down, pup," and the small dog retreated to his basket, watching them balefully.

"That was easy enough," Harry murmured, looking down the trap door into the passageway. "So now we just follow Hagrid and head for the Room of Requirement at the other end, right?"

"We'll give him a minute to get further along," Remus suggested. "He might get suspicious if he heard someone following him." A minute later they walked slowy down the steps into the passageway leading to the seventh floor of the castle.

The passageway was larger than expected; it could easily accommodate someone Hagrid's size, and there were glowing balls of light every dozen yards or so that lighted their way. Lupin paused at one to examine it more carefully. "Looks like a permanent Light Charm cast onto a glass ball," he told Harry and Sirius. Simple, but effective. I wonder how long these have been here — Hagrid couldn't have created them."

"If this was so he could get in the castle quickly," Sirius suggested, "one of the headmasters may have done it for him."

"True," Remus agreed. "Probably Dumbledore. I don't think Headmaster Dippet would have — he believed Hagrid summoned the Monster of Slytherin and that it killed Abigail Myrtle."

"I thought we were being quiet so Hagrid wouldn't hear us," Harry interjected softly.

"I cast a Silencing Charm, just in case," Remus said, smiling. "I know Sirius just can't keep his mouth shut."

"Yeah, right, Moony," Sirius muttered. "Thanks for your support."

They came to steps leading upward and followed them for a long way until they arrived at a blank wall. Remus cast a spell detecting for living beings on the other side; finding none, he slowly pushed on the wall. It swung away, revealing a seventh-floor corridor. He motioned for Sirius and Harry to follow him through.

"Dis must be dey place," Sirius quipped as he looked around the corridor. "Now how do we find the Room of Requirement from here?"

"It won't be hard," Remus said. He pointed in one direction along the corridor. "Follow me."

=ooo=

Tonks appeared in the foyer of the TBC building. The foyer was nearly empty except for a woman and a small child walking out of an elevator toward the front exit. The young boy was staring at Tonks as if he'd just seen a woman appear out of thin air (which perhaps he had). "Mummy!" he cried, trying to point at Tonks as his mother hurried toward the exit. "That lady with the pink hair! She —"

"It's not polite to point, Sidney," his mother said crossly to him.

"But Mummy! She was just there, like mag—" the rest of his statement was cut off as his mother pulled him out the door.

Tonks looked around the lobby. According to reports filed a few months ago, there was a separate elevator that led to the Potter apartment. After Potter's arrest, the door had been enchanted so that only wizards could see it, to keep anyone from stumbling upon it. As Tonks concentrated, a section of the wall suddenly expanded a few feet, causing a door to appear. Tonks walked over to the door, cast Alohomora on it, and walked through.

Beyond the door was a hallway, and a few yards down another door, which Tonks magically unlocked as well, stepping through to find a small room with nothing but an elevator door inside. She pushed the button next to the doors and they opened immediately. She stepped inside and hit the button marked "PH."

The elevator began moving, irritatingly slow to anyone used to Apparation or Portkeys. When the doors finally opened again, she stepped into another small room, this one containing a fireplace and another door. The fireplace had been disconnected from the Floo Network, Tonks knew. In fact the whole Potter apartment had been "de-magicked" almost to the point of Muggle-tude: no Extension Charms, no wards, nothing to warn former Minister Granger of anyone's approach, not even a Muggle, assuming a Muggle could get through the wards leading up to this point. The Ministry (read: Draco Malfoy) had effectively cut Hermione Granger-Potter off from the rest of the wizarding community.

Not that Tonks had a dragon in that fight; it was up to the Wizengamot and the current Minister how they treated their former Ministers of Magic. But, Tonks reasoned, if anyone had an idea what Harry Potter might do or where he might go after breaking out of Azkaban, it was his wife.

Tonks knocked on the door and waited nearly a minute before pulling her wand to check for anyone on the other side. There was nothing but a corridor leading to another door. The door wasn't even locked. She went through it, walking down the corridor to the next door, and knocked again. Again, nothing, and she cast her detection spell again. This time she sensed a normal apartment living area that seemed empty, but there was a human presence further inside. Technically, she was trespassing, but… Tonks unlocked the door and stepped inside, following where her detection spell told her the human was.

Hermione Granger-Potter was in bed, curled up and seemingly asleep. It was the middle of the afternoon, Tonks remembered; how long had the former Minister been sleeping? "Minister?" she said, softly.

"I'm not the Minister anymore." Hermione's voice was dull, listless. "Whoever you are, go away. I don't want to speak to anyone."

"It's Auror Tonks, ma'am," Tonks offered. "You remember me, don't you?"

Several seconds of silence. Then, "Yes," Hermione's voice came from beneath the covers, "but I still don't want to speak to you. So go away."

"I have news about your husband."

There was another moment of silence. "What did he do, break out of Azkaban?"

Tonks was a bit taken aback by that. "Actually, he did, ma'am. And Sirius Black escaped with him."

"What, the man who killed his parents? That seems unlikely. And how do you know that, anyway?"

"Well…" Tonks didn't really want to admit how she knew, especially to a former Minister, but — "Well, they sort of captured me and told me, before I escaped."

Hermione slowly sat up. She was thinner than Tonks remembered her, and there were lines on her face that hadn't been there a month ago. She was giving Tonks a penentrating look. That Tonks remembered. "What are you doing here, again?"

"We need to find them, ma'am," Tonk said matter-of-factly. "We thought — well, I thought, you might have some idea where they might have gone to hide."

"Where did you find them first?" Hermione asked, rubbing sleep out of her eyes.

"I can't tell you, ma'am. It's protected by a Fidelius."

"Then how do you happen to know? Why would you be included in a Fidelius to hide Harry?"

"By accident, ma'am. Chief Warlock Lupin cast the spell without knowing I was present until it was too late."

"Remus was part of this as well?" That seemed to surprise Hermione most of all. Hermione's eyes narrowed suspiciously. "That doesn't seem credible, Auror. Remus Lupin has been an exemplary Chief Warlock for many years now. It seems unlikely he'd help Harry or Sirius Black break out of Azkaban."

"I agree, Minister," Tonks nodded. "But it may have had something to do with Lupin's past friendship with Sirius Black. They apparently attended Hogwarts together."

"Harry told me they had," Hermione added. "But Sirius Black went into Azkaban in 1981 for the murder of Peter Pettigrew — that's… 35 years ago."

"Harry claims Pettigrew visited him in prison before he broke out."

Hermione shook her head slowly. "Harry said that? I think he must've hallucinated that. He's been in Azkaban a month now. Do you really expect me to believe something like that, without proof? Do you believe any of it?"

"I don't know what to believe, ma'am," Tonks said, honestly. "It seemed like Potter believed what he was saying, and Lupin believed him."

"Harry can be very persuasive," Hermione said. "Believe me, I know that. But… what else did they tell you?"

"Well," Tonks hesitated, but she needed to get the former Minister engaged in this manhunt, make her want to find Potter and Black. "He said that Voldemort was still alive, and that he was possessing Draco Malfoy."

Hermione stared at her for several moments. "And do you believe that?"

"Well, not really," Tonks conceded. "There's a spell that might prove the Minister is possessed, but I don't think anyone but the Chief Warlock has authorization to use it on him, and Remus has already lost his objectivity in this case by helping Harry and Black. But if we can find Harry, get him to argue his case before the Wizengamot again, we might have a basis for testing Malfoy for possession."

Hermione raised an eyebrow. "That sounds like a thinly veiled attempt to get me to predict where Harry might go to hide out." She gestured tiredly toward the apartment. "Obviously, he's not here — I assume you've checked."

"Yes, ma'am," Tonks conceded.

"And he probably would go to any of his friends like the Weasleys," Hermione went on, like she was trying to work out this puzzle for herself.

"Well," Tonks volunteered. "They did break Ginny Thomas out as well. Harry insists she, too, is innocent of the deaths of the three Aurors she's convicted of murdering."

"Ginny, too, huh?" Hermione ran her hands through her disheveled hair, clearing it out of her eyes. "That's interesting. Well, I'm sure Malfoy has them under surveillance in case Harry or Ginny shows up, but Harry would expect that."

"I don't know, ma'am," Tonks shook her head doubtfully. "Harry didn't seem too sharp during the time I observed him. It looked more like he was letting Remus take the lead on what they should do."

"Did you check back at the location where you found them?" Hermione asked.

"Not yet," Tonks admitted. "But it seems certain they would have left once they knew their protection was blown."

"Then you can't be certain theyaren't still there," Hermione pointed out, reasonably. Tonks realized she was correct.

"I ought to go back and check," she said, "just in case." She turned to leave.

"Wait," Hermione said. She tossed off the covers and threw her legs over the side of the bed. She was still dressed in the clothes she had worn last night. "I'm going with you."

"I can't allow that, ma'am —" Tonks began to object.

"You shouldn't even be in my apartment without Minister Malfoy's permission," Hermione cut her off, standing. She picked up her wand from the bedside table and passed it over herself, straightening and cleaning her clothes. "Do you have permission to be here, Auror Tonks?"

Tonks didn't answer. "Didn't think so," Hermione went on.

"I can't get you through the Fidelius," Tonks bluffed. "I'm not the primary Secret Keeper."

"A Portkey can," Hermione replied, calling her bluff. "It's a loophole in the spell — Portkeys weren't invented when the Fidelius was first created. Sorry, Tonks, I'm going with you whether you like it or not, if you want my help finding Harry Potter-Evans-Verres."

Tonks nodded. She did want to find Harry Potter-Whatever-Whatever.

=ooo=

Harry, Sirius and Remus moved down the seventh-floor corridor in the direction Remus had pointed out. Sirius was looking around, smiling happily. "Almost feels like a classs reunion," he said to Remus. "With Harry here taking James's place."

"They aren't the same person," Remus reminded him. "Harry is a lot different than James was, though I'd estimate he's about as smart as James was."

"I don't know about that," Harry said over his shoulder. "I had some weird shit go down with me and James Monroe before I ended up in Azkaban. My Patronus has helped me remember a lot of stuff, but I've got a ways to go before I get back to the way I was."

"Don't worry about that, Harry," Sirius said confidently. "We'll help you get back to normal. There's a lot the Room of Requirement can do for you, I'd wager."

"We'll see," Remus said in a more non-commital tone. "The Room of Requirement will be just around this corner."

They rounded the corner, looking for the tapestry of Barnabas the Barmy, knowing the Room of Requirement's entrance was just opposite it. What they did not expect to find, however, was the Headmaster of Hogwarts standing in the middle of the corridor waiting for them.

He did not look happy to see them.

"Well," Neville Longbottom said, in a rather irritated tone. "The prodigal wizards have returned to the scene of the crime." His wand was out and held at the ready, in a position that could either initiate offensive spells or react with defensive ones.

"Who's this kid?" Sirius asked in a condescending tone. "He hardly looks old to have graduated from Hogwarts, much less teach here."

"He's the Headmaster," Harry said, sotto voce. "Let us do the talking, Sirius."

"I know who you are," Neville responded. "Sirius Black, convicted of thirteen murders, including the wizard Peter Pettigrew, in 1981 and sentenced to life in Azkaban. The question at the moment is, what are you doing here with the Chief Warlock?" Neville's gaze shifted fractionally to Lupin. "Remus?"

"We need asylum," Remus answered at once. "We have new information in Harry and Sirius's cases that could exonerate them, and we may also be able to prove that Lord Voldemort —" Neville frowed at the name but did not flinch "— is not dead but is possessing the body of another wizard."

"Who?" Neville asked. "Wait," he went on. "Don't tell me, I'm keen to guess. Let's see, could it be — Minister Malfoy?"

"Actually," Remus nodded. "That's exactly who we believe he's possessoing —"

"Malfoy's on his way here," Neville cut over him. "I just informed him that you three are here, and Ginny Thomas as well."

"Neville!" Harry cried out disbelievingly. "You haven't even heard out side!"

"I'm not the Wizengamot," Neville informed him. "I'm not taking sides, I'm making my school safe for my students!"

"How'd you figure out we were here?" Lupin asked, as his eyes quickly scanned the corridor around them and Neville. They would have to do something quickly before Malfoy arrived and the school went into Auror Lockdown.

"My security system," Neville replied, "let me know the moment you entered the grounds. I've been tracking you for minutes now, waiting for you to make your move. Clever of you to have Hagrid take Ginny Thomas to the infirmary so you could follow him along his secret passageway into the castle. Once you left the exit I knew exactly where you were heading, and I made sure I got here before you."

"One of the perks of being the Headmaster," Harry muttered. Neville controlled the Anti-Apparition spells within the school and grounds; he could turn them on or off whenever he wanted. Very likely he was keyed into the wards themselves, so they didn't prevent him from Appariating.

"True," Neville agreed. "So let's just settle in wait for Malfoy and his Aurors to show up — this time for you, not to make trouble in the school like the last time you were here, Harry."

Remus held up both hands placatingly. "Alright, alright Neville. We're not going to make any trouble, we'll just wait —" Remus's hand suddenly twitched in a quick gesture. Neville's wand went flying out of his hand.

At the same moment Sirius and Harry's wands were both out. Neville's hands were moving as well and both Stunners they sent at him were deflected away, though Neville staggered back at the impacts on his wandless shield.

Remus, meanwhile, was reaching up to snatch Neville's wand from the air and it spun toward him, but it suddenly stopped and reversed direction, flying back into Neville's wand hand. "Impressive," Harry muttered to himself, wishing he'd studied more wandless magic, and tried to Banish the wand, but Neville had already caught it. Remus's wand was moving in another spell gesture but before he could complete the spell Neville Disapparated.

Well, I was right about the wards, Harry thought.

"We need to leave," Remus said urgently. "If they can track us anywhere we go in the castle —"

"But not in the Room of Requirement!" Harry argued. "We can use it to figure something out before Malfoy gets here!"

"Not enough time!" Remus disagreed.

"Where else can we go, Moony?" Sirius asked matter-of-factly. He pointed down the corridor in Remus's direction. "Check for Disillusioned wizards — I'll do the same in the other direction. Harry, you get the door open!"

Harry hurriedly began pacing back in front of the blank wall opposite Barnabas the Barmy's tapestry. "We need a place to hide ourselves," he muttered beneath his breath as he quick-stepped back and forth. "We need a place no one can find us, a place we can figure out what to do next!"

Just as a heavy oaken door appeared in the wall as Harry completed his third pass, a Stunner richocheted off the tapestry as Sirius blocked it. "It's open!" Harry shouted, grabbing the door and jerking it open. He, Sirius and Remus disappeared through it just as two more Stunners hit the door from opposite directions and whined away.

Harry's breath was coming in short gasps as he pulled the door closed and let go of it. He turned back to Sirius and Remus, smiling triumphantly. Sirius shared his grin but Remus looked less than happy.

"Well, we're inside," he said to Harry. "And now they know right where we are. I hope you're ready for some siege warfare."

"Beats the alternative," Sirius pointed out. "I'd rather be hiding in here than caught and back in Azkaban out there. Now, d'you think we can get some food up in here? I'm beginning to feel a bit peckish."

Lupin shook his head. "Sirius, it's a long time since we were students here and could coax the house-elves to bring us food from the kitchens. I'm afraid we're going to have to make do with wand water and some protein bars I have in my robes until we come up with a solution to our problems."

"Then we need to remember just what this room could do when we asked, Moony," Sirius insisted.

"Remember," Harry muttered. "That's a good idea, Sirius." He held up his wand and began the motions for a certain spell. "Expecto Patronum!"

=ooo=

The dark hallway of number 12, Grimmauld Place erupted into a sudden explosion of color and whirling air as two people suddenly appeared there, both of them falling as their feet touched the hallway floor.

Hermione shook her head and decided to wait a moment before standing. Well, that's one question solved, she thought to herself, watching as Auror Tonks quickly jumped to her feet, embarrassed to have fallen in front of the Minister (well, former Minister, who'd incidentally fallen as well). Then, "What in the world is all that screeching?"

Tonks covered her ears. "It's Black's mother!" she shouted at Hermione. "Her portrait, really! She screams like that whenever she's disturbed!"

Hermione was covering her ears as well. "How do we shut her up?" she yelled back.

Tonks took out her wand. "Hang on a sec," she growled, and walked off down the hallway. Hermione jumped to her feet and followed.

"Filth! Scum! Freaks!" she could hear an old woman screaming. "Begone from the house of my fathers —" the screams suddenly cut off. By the time Hermione caught up with Tonks, she was gesturing at a pair of dusty velvet curtains that drew shut over a life-size painting of a batty-looking old woman—a woman whose eyes were now covered in a blindfold.

"That's that," Tonks muttered, then turned to Hermione. "Well, Minister, welcome to number 12, Grimmauld Place — the Black Family's ancestral home. Since you arrived with me and the Portkey, I should be able to tell you this is where Harry and Sirius Black were holed up with Remus Lupin. And obviously, I just did tell you," she added, smiling.

"Right," Hermione agreed. "What we need to know, however, is where they are right now."

"I hope they left some clues as to where they might have gone," Tonks explained. "Let me show you where they held me before I escaped." Hermione followed the Auror down the stairs to the kitchen.

"I disguised myself as Chief Warlock Lupin and brought them groceries, something the real Remus said he would do," Tonks told Hermione. "I had hoped to fix Harry and Black some stew laced with Sleeping Potion and bring them to the Ministry to be returned to Azkaban, but Remus returned unexpectedy and exposed my disguise. They captured me and Harry explained he thought that Minister Malfoy was really Voldemort and that he'd framed Harry and the Thomas woman for crimes he'd committed."

"Oh my god," Hermione sighed. "I can't believe Harry would try to resurrect that Dark wizard again! How was he going to prove Voldemort was still alive this time?"

"He has some idea that an artifact called the Marauder's Map could prove that Malfoy and Voldemort were inhabiting the same body if he could lure Malfoy to Hogwarts with the Map," Tonks said, sounding doubtful. "Harry even wanted me to break into the Minister's office to look for the Map!"

Hermione shrugged resignedly. "Once Harry latches onto an idea he hangs on with the tenacity of a bulldog. But," she added, thoughtfully, "that could be an indication of where he is right now…"

Tonks saw it at once. "You mean Hogwarts? That would not be the smartest place for him to be. You can't Apparate or Portkey in or out or anywhere within the grounds, and the Floos are restricted. Plus, I understand there's a security system that can track anyone on the grounds the same way the Marauder's Map is supposed to do. Potter would be foolish to go there."

"Maybe," Hermione replied, "but Harry would find some way to turn all that into an advantage."

"If he can do that," Tonks retorted disbelievingly, "we should have made him an Auror. What the hell —?"

A brillian silver light had suddenly illuminated the room. Tonks had spun around toward the source of the light, her wand instinctively coming up to protect the Minister. "You again!" she gasped, recognizing the new arrival. "What are you doing here now?"

Hermione had recognized the form as well. But she was staring at Tonks. "Do you know what this is?" she asked.

"It's Potter's Patronus — or so he told me," Tonks answered, still holding her wand at the ready. "I don't know if it's here for you or me, though."

Hermione smiled. "No offence, Auror Tonks, but I doubt Harry knew who you were before he captured you earlier today. I think it's here to bring me a message from Harry."

"I am," the Patronus nodded. "But my message is for both of you, seeing that you are here together in Sirius's home."

Hermione blinked. "What?" she said blankly. "How could a Patronus know anyone was with me?"

"I can see it plainly enough, Hermione," the Patronus answered. "I am capable of more than simply parroting messages."

"What?" Hermione frowned. "Harry never told me his Patronus could act independently of him!"

"Until he cast me for the first time in years, earlier today," the Patronus replied, "he was unaware of it himself, or of the other things I am capable of doing. He has sent me to you in the hopes that I might be able to help you understand as well."

The Patronus reached out a silver hand toward Hermione, who froze as Tonks tried to come up with a spell to stop it should the Patronus hurt the Minister in some way. The glowing fingertips touched Hermione's forehead, and her eyes widened as memories suddenly formed in her recollections. "Oh. Oh my god," she whispered. "It's unbelievable, but it has to be true. Tonks, we have to go to Hogwarts immediately!"

But the Patronus shook his head. "That would not be advisable. Harry wants you to go to the Ministry immediately and call for an emergency meeting of the Wizengamot so they can be assembled when he returns to the Ministry with Malfoy."

Tonks lowered her wand. "Is that where Potter's at?" she asked Hermione. "Hogwarts?"

"He and Remus and Sirius Black as well," Hermione confirmed. "Malfoy and Aurors will be on their way their as well. We can't let Malfoy take Harry — if he does we'll never see him or Black again. And they're all innocent, Tonks! It's Malfoy who's behind all this — or really, Voldemort!"

"But —" the Patronus said, looking back and forth between the two women. They seemed to be ignoring him.

"Right," Tonks said ironically. But it would remain to be seen whether Malfoy was acting strangely or not — they would have to bring Potter and Black before the Wizengamot to get this nightmare cleared up legally and get the allegations Remus planned to make against Malfoy dropped. "Okay, then, let's go. We should do this outside," she added, then grabbed an umbrella from the troll's leg umbrella stand. "This should make a good Portkey." She and Hermione exited the front door and moments later had disappeared in a whirl of wind and color.

Harry's Patronus stared at the spot they had disappeared from. "That did not work out as planned," it said, then vanished itself.

=ooo=

Minister Malfoy and a squad of Aurors burst into the entrance hall, Malfoy barking orders before the doors were out of his way.

"All Disillusioned Aurors drop their charms, be prepared to converge on Potter's location once it's ascertained. Where's the Headmaster?"

Neville appeared in the middle of the entrance hall. Seeing Malfoy, he strode toward him. "Potter, Black and Lupin are on the seventh floor near the Room of Requirement. They are probably inside by now." He looked upward. "Security, where is Harry Potter right now?"

"Harry Potter cannot be located," the cool female voice replied. "His last location was on the seventh floor near the —"

"Nevermind," Neville snapped. "I know where he was." To Malfoy he said, "Well, I reported to you the moment I knew he was here, but if he's inside the Room of Requirement I don't know what we can do short of waiting until he and the others run out of food and water. And if they brought either with them it could be a long time before that happens."

The front doors flew open again, and Hermione and Tonks ran into the entrance hall. Malfoy opened his mouth but Hermione cut him off. "Don't give me that look, Draco!"

"Call me Minister," Draco said, curtly. "And how do you know Potter's here?"

"He sent me a message that couldn't be faked, so don't try to lie to me about that, Minister!"

"Oh, I won't lie to you," he said, calmly. "In fact, I'm glad you're here. I think it will simplify my negotiations with our three fugitives quite a bit."

"What's that supposed to mean, Minister?" Tonks asked, not liking the tone Malfoy had adopted. Things were starting to feel strange.

"It means Mrs. Granger-Potter is going to help me talk Potter out of the Room of Requirement," Malfoy said, evenly. "And from there we'll see that he gets his day in court." He smiled at Herminoe. "I'm sure that's what you want, isn't it, Hermione?"

Hermione decided she definitely didn't like Malfoy calling her by her first name. "Call me Granger," she said shortly. "And let's go get Harry."

=ooo=

"Look, I'm not asking for a damn banquet," Sirius was complaining to the house-elf who had appeared after Sirius spent several minutes telling the Room that he wanted something to eat. "Just something simple — say, like roast beef and potatoes — maybe some corn or peas, and some butterbeer would be nice, too."

"Noddy is very sorry, sir," the house-elf was pulling his ears as he spoke — he was not comfortable with the orders he'd been given, but orders they were. "Headmaster has said you are not to be brought any food from Hogwarts kitchens."

Sirius folded his arms, frowning down at the house-elf, who was practically groveling under him. "That's not being very house-elf-like," he said, shaking his head with disappointment. "Aren't you supposed to do what's asked of you?"

"Noddy wants to, sir!" the house-elf looked frantic now. "But orders is orders!"

"And what if I order you to bring me some food?" Sirius growled.

"Then Noddy will have to punish himself most severely for disobeying," the house-elf said, miserably.

"Sirius," Lupin looked over at Black from where he and Harry were discussing their situation. "Don't torment the poor fellow. You know he has to obey Longbottom's orders above all else."

"Fine," Sirius snarled, frustrated. He waved a hand dismissively at the elf. "Go on, then, get back to your kitchen." Noddy gratefully disappeared with a crack and Sirius joined his fellow fugitives. "So what's the plan now?"

"Same as it was before," Harry answered plaintively. "Wait until Malfoy shows up then force a meeting of the Wizengamot so we can prove he's possessed."

"Yeah, that's all going to work out fine," Sirius said pessimistically. "They'll probably charge me with the rat's murder as well."

"Remus thinks he can force the issue with Malfoy," Harry explained. "The Chief Warlock still controls the Wizengamot, not the Minister of Magic. If Malfoy refuses to be tested for possession he's going to lose a lot of support in the Wizengamot."

"Or so you hope," Sirius shrugged.

"It's pretty cut and dried," Remus added, confidently. "Malfoy is already on shaky ground — he hasn't assigned a new Head Auror to take his place now that he's Minister. Some in the Wizengamot see that as a power grab."

"And what do his supporters say?" Harry wanted to know.

Remus smiled wanly. "That his first choice would have been Hermione Granger-Potter, but since she retired from the Ministry he's had a hard time finding someone qualified for the job. That much, at least, is politics-as-usual. But after a month that excuse is getting a bit thin."

Sirius turned to Harry. "So where'd your shiny doppleganger get off to?"

"I sent it to tell Hermione to go to the Ministry and call the Wizengamot in for an emergency meeting," Harry replied. "I think it's coming back now — I can feel it, sort of…" a moment later the Room was illuminated in silver light as the Patronus appeared next to Harry.

"She did not listen," the Patronus said, gravely. "She comes here, instead."

"Ah, dammit!" Harry swore. "What does she think she's going to do here?"

"POTTER." An amplified voice boomed through the walls of the Room. "CAN YOU HEAR ME?"

"Well, Draco's here," Remus said, with false cheer.

"Right," Harry agreed, sourly. He turned to his Patronus. "Go see what he wants us to do."

"Yes," the Patronus turned and walked through the wall. Harry watched it disappear, then tilted his head thoughtfully.

"Interesting," he murmured. "I wondered who was out there, and I can see them through the Patronus! They've brought quite an array of Aurors to take us in." His expression fell. "Hermione's out there, too. I don't think I like that."

"What are they saying to you — to your Patronus?" Remus asked anxiously.

"Malfoy is demanding that we all leave the Room of Requirement and surrender our wands immediately." He listened a moment. "Hermione is demanding that we all be taken to the Most Ancient Hall of the Wizengamot to hear new information in our cases. Malfoy doesn't like that — he wants us back in Azkaban before he'll convene a hearing."

"Of course he does," Sirius muttered. "If we go back to Azkaban we'll never get that hearing, will we?"

"Most likely not," Harry agreed. "Hermione is saying essentially the same thing, a bit more diplomatically, though. Crabbe is trying to shut her up — holy crap, that Tonks woman just pulled her wand on him! That was pretty gutsy of her."

"Maybe we should get out there," Remus suggested quickly. "Perhaps our presence will defuse that situation."

"Out of the frying pan and into the fire," Sirius snorted. "But what the hell — what've we got to lose now?"

Harry wasn't sure he wanted that answered, but he had to do something to protect Hermione. If she pushed Draco too far now there was no telling what he would do, possessed by Voldemort or not! "Let's go," he said, and the three men walked out into the corridor beyond.

The corridor was nearly full of people. Besides Malfoy and Hermione there were Crabbe and Goyle, and behind them stood Tonks, wand still out but no longer pointed at Crabbe. On the other side of the corridor were three Aurors Harry didn't recognize; one was an older man whose left hand had been replaced with a hook. The other two were younger Aurors, one male and one female. All of them looked angry.

"Alright, we're here," Harry said to Malfoy. "What's next?"

"Surrender your wands," Malfoy said again. "You and Black are guilty of escaping from Azkaban. In addition, you've destroyed valuable Ministry assets."

"We made a few holes in your precious walls," Harry began, dismissively, but Draco cut him off.

"No. I mean the Dementors you destroyed. Only a few survived your onslaught."

Harry stared in frank surprise and no small amount of — well, horror. "You've got to be kidding, Malfoy! Those things are — blights on the world! The sooner we're rid of all of them the better!"

"So you admit it," one of the nameless Aurors spoke up. "You destroyed nearly one hundred Dementors when you broke out of Azkaban!"

"And I'd do it again!" Harry declared forcefully. "How many people have they destroyed over the years? Not just at Azkaban, but over the centuries across Britain and Europe? It's like you're defending bubonic plague!"

"Nevertheless," Malfoy said, with no emotion in his voice. "You will be held accountable for them." His voice turned crisp as he continued. "I've also been told you wish to level charges at me?"

"That would be me, Minister," Remus said, taking a step toward Draco. Crabbe and Goyle's wands were instantly on him, and Remus stopped, keeping his wand pointed toward the floor. "I think we should determine whether Harry's allegations that you've been possessed have any merit, and that such determination should be done before the full Wizengamot. Immediately."

Draco rolled his eyes. "I'm sure you'd like to find a way to discredit me, Chief Warlock — that's been on your agenda since I became Minister, obviously."

"Wait a minute," Tonks spoke up. "I've never seen any evidence he's been trying to do that!"

"Shut it, you," Crabbe growled at her. "Nobody's talking to you." Malfoy put up a hand and Crabbe said no more as Tonks glowered at him.

"I have no problem submitting to such a check," Malfoy said to Lupin. "But it will be at the Wizengamot's convenience, not yours, Chief Warlock. In the meantime, Potter and Black will be returned to Azkaban, and I will be bringing charges of my own for your part in aiding with their escape."

"He didn't have anything to do with that!" Tonks piped up again. "He was contacted after the fact, not before it!"

"I have evidence that suggests otherwise," Malfoy retorted. "And you have het to file your reports on the Chief Warlock's whereabouts when he was out of the Ministry, Auror Tonks." Tonks jaw dropped.

Sirius, standing right behind Harry, leaned close to his ear and whispered, "I don't like where this is going. Malfoy seems hell-bent on sending us back to Azkaban without a hearing. And these Aurors all seem to want that, too."

"How can you tell that?" Harry whispered.

"When the only people you talk to for decades are pissed-off, burned out Aurors, Harry, you get good at reading their moods."

"That's completely unacceptable, Draco," Hermione was saying as Sirius finished his whispered comment. "If there are new facts in the case, the Wizengamot has an obligation to hear them before returning the prisoners to prison! We've had that protocol in effect for over a decade now!"

"Since you became Minister," Malfoy finished dryly. "I remember. You pushed them through when it became obvious you couldn't get the Dementors removed from Azkaban — the Wizengamot wants prisoners kept on a shorter leash than you like.

"But in this case the 'facts' you refer to are nothing more than a wild attempt by the prisoners to avoid their just punishments as well as the extra punishment they will receive for their breakout attempt —"

"Breakout success, you mean," Sirius said with a grin. "We kicked some major ass back there." The three Aurors reacted to that, muttering darkly about whose ass would get kicked next.

"Enough of this!" Malfoy said loudly. "Potter! Black! Drop your wands or you will be disarmed and immediately removed back to Azkaban!"

"No!" Hermione shouted. "Harry, don't give up your wand! This needs to go to the Wizengamot before anything —" Her voice cut off suddenly as Goyle grabbed her and pulled her back.

"Goyle!? You— Stupefy!" Tonks put a Stunner into Goyle's back and he crumpled to the floor, pulling Hermione on top of him. At the same moment Crabbe pushed Malfoy behind him and pointed his wand at Tonks. On the other side of the corridor the three Aurors brought up their wands, pointing at Tonks, and fired Stunners at her. Tonks, who'd been concentrating on Crabbe, was knocked off her feet and hit the floor, unconscious.

"Stop! Stop! Stop!" Lupin was shouting, both hands raised high and waving to get everyone's attention—

— but Malfoy was shouting at the same moment "Don't let them get away!" and pointing at Harry and Sirius, who'd both backed up against the corridor wall, wands up but not aimed toward anyone. Hermione was struggling to stand again, trying to move toward Harry, but Crabbe and Malfoy were blocking her way.

"Disarm them!" Crabbe shouted at the three Aurors, who immediately trained their wands on Harry, Sirius and Remus. Harry's wand flew from his hand, as did Sirius's, but Remus held onto his.

"Stupefy!" Crabbe shouted, and a red bolt burst from his wand toward Remus, who easily blocked it. The three Aurors all cast Stunners at Lupin, but he blocked all three without difficulty.

No one moved for several seconds.

Harry scanned the corridor, looking for his wand, but one of the Aurors must've caught it. He didn't see Sirius's wand either. Malfoy muttered something to Crabbe; he pointed his wand at Goyle, who jerked awake. Must've used Rennervate on him, Harry assumed. Crabbe pulled Goyle to his feet and whispered something to him. Goyle nodded, then grabbed Hermione and began pulling her away down the corridor.

"Hey!" Harry shouted. "Bring her back!" But Goyle kept dragging her away.

"She's going to Azkaban," Malfoy yelled at him. "Unless you surrender immediately, Potter! You and Black both!"

Harry hesitated only a bare second. "I surrender, then!" he shouted. "Bring her back!" But Goyle and Hermione had already rounded a corner and were out of sight. "Goyle! You bastard! Bring her BACK!" He took a step toward Malfoy.

Crabbe's wand was instantly on Harry as was the wands of the three Aurors behind him. Harry took another step but Remus took him by the arm.

"Harry," Remus whispered urgently. "Don't force anything with Malfoy! He's trying to goad you!"

Harry ignored him. "Malfoy, get Hermione back here," he demanded.

Malfoy only smiled triumphantly. "Your surrender is the only thing that'll keep her from Azkaban."

"You don't really want us to surrender, do you?" Harry suddenly realized. "We're already disarmed but your men haven't moved in to take us. You have something else in mind, don't you?"

A mask of nonemotion had settled on Malfoy's face. He turned slightly toward Crabbe and said in a low voice, "Permission granted."

"Thank you," Crabbe said, and pointed his wand at Harry. "Avada Kedavra!"

As Crabbe finished the spell, Lupin shouted, "NO!" and leaped forward, moving between Harry and Crabbe. Time seemed to slow down as a bolt a green energy erupted from Crabbe's wand and flew toward the Chief Warlock.

Then time seemed to stop.

Harry blinked. Time had stopped. What the hell?

The Killing Curse was hovering in the air only inches from Remus Lupin's chest. He looked at Crabbe and Malfoy — both were unmoving, not even breathing. In the other direction the three Aurors' wands were pointed at him, Remus and Sirius, but they had frozen as well. Even Remus was still; he hadn't reacted to the green death that was about to strike him.

Harry glanced at Sirius, who was staring fixedly at Remus as well. Then Sirius turned to look at Harry. "That didn't work out well, did it?" he asked, matter-of-factly.

"Huh?" Harry said.

Sirius nodded toward the others. "I thought we'd get this fracas under control. Or at least, enough to get Hermione free of these Aurors and get her and Tonks out of here. I should've guessed Malfoy would want us dead if Voldemort is in his head now."

"Huh?" said Harry again.

"Oh, yeah — sorry," Sirius said, then concentrated for a second. A pale image separated from him and stepped away, solidifying into —

James Monroe. Sirius had stopped moving and was as frozen as the others now.

"Huh?" Harry said, a third time.

"Hi, Harry," Monroe said, grinning. "I'm baaack."

Chapter 30: For All the Marbles Pt 1

Updated 7/12/2013

=ooo=

Four former students of Hogwarts School of Witchcraft and Wizardry stared at the wall running along the northern boundary of the school, not far from the gates but beyond the edge of the wards protecting the school. And further away than where the Marauder's Map would begin showing them when activated.

The oldest of the four glanced at the three redheads. "I hope you had a plan before coming here," she said, plaintively.

"A plan? Pffft," the next-oldest waved a hand airly as he repled. "That would ruin the fun of it!"

"I really don't want to get caught," the pink-haired Auror pointed out. "Maybe you three should just go ahead on your own, if you haven't figured out what you're going to do yet."

"We didn't say that," the third-oldest objected. "We know what we're doing, we just didn't plan it out ahead of time."

"Yeah, that would be boring," the youngest redhead agreed. "Even if we are trying to snatch our only sister away from the Aurors guarding her and hide her where they'll never find her."

"Yeah," the renegade Auror said skeptically. "I think you'd better plan on finding someone who can cast a Fidelius for you. The Auror Department takes a dim view of prisoners escaping from Azkaban — they will look for her anywhere and everywhere they think she might be."

"I'm sure they will," the elder redheaded twin agreed. "But short of accidentally including an Auror in the Fidelius —" both twins smiled at this. "I don't think they stand a puffskein's chance in a nundu's lair of finding her."

"So what are we doing?" the youngest of the group wanted to know. "We're assuming Malfoy has the Marauder's Map, right?"

"Right you are, Ronnikins," the twins answered. "He'd be foolish to trust the security system we designed. Especially since we've already told it to ignore our presence here at Hogwarts."

"Nice," the Auror said, somewhat impressed. "You added a backdoor to your system."

"That's a secret, of course," the elder twin put a finger over his lips. "Don't tell Nevillie. He still doesn't know we're selling our wares in the Gryffindor common room every third Saturday of the month."

Tonks giggled. "My lips are sealed, then." She cocked her head, her hair turning a curious yellow. "So how are you getting past the Marauder's Map, then?
"We're not," George said. "Can't be done, and we've tried a lot of different ways, but it doesn't matter — if you're a ghost, an Animagus, Disillusioned, or whatever, the Map knows where you are. The only thing that might work is Harry's Invisibility Cloak, and we don't have that at our disposal right now. More than likely Malfoy has got that as well. We talked to Hermione after Harry went into Azkaban and she told us the Ministry came and cleaned out every magical item in their apartment. Shut down all the wards and protection spells. Left her pretty much defenseless. We offered to put up some protection spells for her but she said she didn't want us getting into trouble." George shook his head. "Wish she'd reconsidered."

"Okay, so if Malfoy sees us on the Marauder's Map our gooses are collectively cooked," Tonks said, her pessimism beginning to feel warranted. "That's not good. It's a long way from the gates of Hogwarts to the infirmary."

"Oh, we're not going to walk into Hogwarts. Not even one of the secret passages would keep from beign seen on the Map. We're taking a short cut," Fred told her, reaching into his robe and taking out a metallic ring about a foot in diameter. He held it out for her to see: the ring was a dark metal with runes carved into the top.

"We got the basic idea from this when were still in school, when we saw some upperclassmen creating rune arches," Fred continued, flipping the ring over to reveal more runes on its opposite side. "But it's been harder to implement than we expected." He reached into his robes and pulled out another ring, this one identical to the first, then put it away again.

"Our first idea," Fred continued, "was to create a ring that we could use to Apparate through the wards around the school to anywhere within the school or grounds."

"Our basic problem," George went on, "was how much magic a ring big enough for three or four persons was required to Apparate through the wards. You could do it, but you ended up weak and magically drained when you landed. That increased the chance of Splinching when you tried to Apparate a second or third time. It's also a problem carrying around big metal rings that are each three or four feet in diameter."

Ron took up the story at that point. "But then one of us —" Ron pointed a thumb at himself "— had the brilliant idea of asking if we could just use a smaller ring to create a Portkey rather than Apparate. With a Portkey you can't get Splinched. It took off from there."

"Meaning," Fred said, leaning conspiratorially toward Tonks, "that Ronnie here came up with the idea, but George and I had to figure out how to make it happen. Which we did," he finished proudly, holding up the ring again.

"And what does this wonderful ring do?" Tonks asked, patiently.

"It creates a small area within an anti-Portkey ward that will let us key into the ward when we create a Portkey," George explained. "We can then use the Portkey to go anywhere within the anti-Portkey ward area we want."

"The only problem with that," Ron added, "is that some wizards create their wards to change harmonics whenever a keyed-in spell or item is activated. "And Neville Longbottom is one of those wizards."

Tonks nodded. "So the Portkey is only good for one use, right?"

"Give the little lady a gold ring!" Fred beamed. "Yes, that's why we have a second ring to use to get out of the school — using the first ring drains its magic."

"And what if your ring doesn't work?" Tonks wanted to know.

"It will," Fred said confidently.

"Humor me for a moment," she insisted.

Fred scratched his chin, looking at George, who made a shrugging gesture and indicated he should go ahead and answer. "Well, in the best case we won't be able to create the Portkey in the first place — the wards at the destination would prevent that — and in the worst case, we will bounce off the ward and end up in some random location; whether that location is above or below ground, or inside some object, we wouldn't know until we got there."

"Nice," Tonks said sarcastically. "How sure are you that this will work?"

"Definitely," Fred answered at once.

"Pretty sure," George said at the same time.

"Fairly sure," Ron said at the same time. The three brothers looked at each other, then at Tonks.

"We're sure," Fred finished. "Trust us."

Tonks shook her head dubiously but said nothing. At least they had a way in and out.

"So the plan," George summed up, "is to create the Portkey, drop into the infirmary, have you and Ron grab Ginny while Fred and I make the second Portkey, and head out to an as-yet undisclosed location where Ginny will be safe. Total time in Hogwarts, about ten seconds."

"And if Malfoy's not looking at the Map during that time," Tonks surmised, "they'll never know anyone was there until they realize Ginny's missing."

"That's the rumor," Fred nodded. He held out the rune ring in front of him and looked around at the others. "Are we ready to go?"

Tonks, George and Ron nodded assent. "Everyone line up with me," Fred said, and they began moving forward slowly. "We have to find the edge of the Portkey ward, then George will cast the spell on the object — what are we using?"

Ron held up a shot glass still filled with firewhiskey. "I didn't think old Alderforth would miss it," he grinned.

Tonks made a face, but Fred and George both beamed. "Excellent!" they said in unison. Ron drank a bit of the firewhiskey, then passed the glass to George, who drank and passed it to Fred. Fred knocked back most of the glass, then held it out to Tonks. Tonks looked at the little bit of firewhiskey still in the glass, shrugged, and downed the rest. At that moment the black ring in Fred's hands began to glow a pale blue.

"Alright, it's inside the Portkey ward," Fred said quickly. "Cast the spell!"

George put the now-empty shot glass in the middle of the ring and pointed his wand at it. "Portus," he said, and the glass flashed blue. "Five seconds," George warned everyone.

Fred put the first ring into his robes as he, Tonks and Ron each put a finger on the Portkey. "Everyone remember your jobs —" he said, then a whirlwind of color scooped them up and they vanished.

=ooo=

The Portkey whirlwind deposited the four of them in the center of the infirmary, all landing expertly on their feet. "There she is!" Fred said, pointing to a corner where a screen hid the bed from view.

"Waitaminute!" Ron said, pointing toward another corner, where an identical screen was set up. "What about that one?"

Fred spun around, cursing to himself. "They set up multiple screens!" he rasped. "Check them all!" He sprinted toward the one he'd pointed to, pointing his wand and knocking the screen aside. There was no one in the bed.

"Aaaaaah!" a girl in a nearby bed screamed at seeing an unknown adult wizard throwing things around in the infirmary.

"Quiet!" Fred hissed, turning and running back to the center of the room. Tonks, Ron and George had each gone to an opposite corner looking for Ginny. "Not here!" Tonks said loudly, looking behind her screen.

"Not here either!" George's shout followed right behind Tonks. "She's supposed to be in here!"

"Over here," Fred spun toward the barely audible words. Ginny was in a bed in plain view near Madam Pomfrey's office. He raced over to the bed and picked her up.

"Ginny! Are you okay?" Fred asked her anxiously. She nodded weakly. "Here she is! Let's get out of here!"

Tonks, George and Ron turned and ran toward Fred and Ginny. But as Ron ran past a bed, an arm reached out and caught at his pants leg, causing him to stumble. He reached down and grabbed the hand holding his pants leg, trying to make it let go.

The patient reached out with her other hand, grabbing his pants leg again, and Ron hissed "Let go!" then gasped as he looked at the face of the person in the bed. The girl in the bed had jet-black hair, but her face was Ginny's. Her mouth moved but nothing came out, and she pointed at her throat. Ron pointed his wand at her and said, "Vocalis!" the countercurse for the Silencio spell. "Ron, it's me," she whispered. "Other Ginny — Polyjuice…"

"Fred!" Ron immediately shouted. "Polyjuice!"

Fred instantly dropped the girl in his arms, drawing his wand as he did so. The girl was drawing hers at the same time, but Ron managed to shout "Stupefy!" before she got off a spell. She hit the bed, unconscious, and Fred followed with "Polyfluis Reverso!" Ginny's form began to melt, and Fred turned and ran toward Ron, with Tonks and George converging on him and Ginny at the same time.

Fred pulled out the second ring as he ran toward them. Ron picked up Ginny and held her ready as George drew the second Portkey from his robes, a Fanged Frisbee and jammed it into the center of the black ring Fred held. "Portus," George said, and the Frisbee flashed blue.

All hell broke loose.

At least four "patients" in beds around the infirmary suddenly sat up, pointing their wands at either Tonks and the Weasleys or into the air. Tonks instinctively raised a shield encompassing the group at the first unexpected motion. Curses bounced off the shield; Tonks smirked as at least one "patient" was knocked out by his own Stunner — she'd managed to twist the spell as it ricocheted off her shield back at him.

"Grab the Frisbee!" Fred yelled. "Five seconds — NO!" He suddenly knocked the Portkey out of George's hand.

"What's wrong?" Ron yelled, staring as the toy bounced off Tonks shield. "Why'd you —" Everyone inside the shield flinched as the Frisbee suddenly exploded and at the same time became a rainbow-hued whirlwind and vanished. "Holy shit!" Ron exclaimed. "What happened?!"

"They put up more Portkey wards," Fred said. "We didn't test for that! The Frisbee thought it was good to go but those extra wards stopped it. If we'd gone with it we'd be —"

"We're still going to be," Tonks warned, "if we don't get out of here. A couple of those 'kids' who were playing possum in the beds are casting Breaking Drill Hexes on my shield!"

Fred shook his head. "I knew I should have made three rune rings," he muttered, then looked up at them, beaming. "Oh wait! I did!" He pulled a third ring from his robes.

"Freddie, I could kiss you!" George laughed, patting his twin on both cheeks.

"Well, don't," Fred warned, holding out the third ring. "No need to make Angelina jealous."

"Is that going to work?" Tonks asked, wincing as she poured more magic into her shield, fighting the Breaking Drills being applied to it. "There are multiple Portkey wards holding us here."

"It can handle them if the Portkey is set after they're up," Fred said. "I did tests for multiple wards. Hurry up and cast the spell, George!"

George was looking around frantically for something to charm. "What do I use?"

"Oh for Merlin's sake!" Ron snapped. He reached down and pulled a trainer off one of his feet. "Here!"

George grabbed the shoe and stuck it into the ring Fred held. "Portus!" he said, and everyone grabbed hold of the shoe. There was flash of whirling colors inside Tonks' shield, which popped out of existence as the whirlwind died away.

A fourth-year girl in blonde curls reached into her hospital robe and pulled out a two-way mirror. "They Ported out," she said. "As you expected, sir."

"Good," Malfoy's image in the mirror smiled. "Did the Portkey detection charm catch their destination?"

The blonde concentrated for a moment. "It did," she confirmed. "I can charm another Portkey and be down in the Entrance Hall in less than a minute."

"Make two," Malfoy said. "We're done here for now. And drop that ridiculous disguise."

"Yes, sir." The blonde stood, casting Polyfluis Reverso on herself, growing several feet in height and becoming Vincent Crabbe. He picked up two trays, casting word-trigger Portkeys on each of them, then ran out of the infirmary for the Entrance Hall. The Weasleys and the traitorous Auror Tonks were about to have a rude surprise show up at their "secret" location!

=ooo=

"Ready for this?" Remus asked.

Harry and Sirius both nodded. Their wands were out and ready, and Harry was breathing slowly in preparation for the spell he had to cast immediately upon arrival at their destination. It was not going to be easy, because they would be at ground zero, and it would not be pleasant.

Remus handed a shot glass to Sirius, who held it for several seconds before finally pointing his wand at it and saying, "Portus." The glass glowed blue and Sirius said, "I set it for fifteen seconds, in case you need a running start, Harry."

Harry nodded again. He reached out and took an edge of the glass in forefinger and thumb. Remus and Sirius did the same. While the Weasleys had something of a plan (Fred just shrugged when asked before they left, but Harry knew they never leaped before they looked) his strategy was a bit less developed. Nevertheless, Remus and Sirius were still coming with him, and he was grateful. And he hoped they could make it in and out Askaban before the Aurors even knew they were there.

It wasn't very likely, but if he could find Hermione and get back in the central shaft, where the magical protections were drained away by the Dementors, they could enchant another Portkey to take them out and back to — somewhere.

The Portkey activated and an invisible hook pulled Harry forward into a whirlwind of color, spinning him and the two Marauders with him. They were pulled forward, twisting color and howling winds all about them, until Harry's feet slammed into what felt like mud.

They were atop the mound of dirt that was the nesting place of the remaining Dementors of Azkaban. Harry immediately began casting the Patronus Charm, while Remus and Sirius checked for the hole Harry had made in the wall at the lowest level of the prison.

"Expecto Patronum!" Harry's Patronus blazed into existence, hovering above him and protecting him and the others. The few remaining Dementors, floating higher in the air shaft, moved away but otherwise did not seem to notice them.

The hole Harry had made was still in the wall, left unplugged. Remus followed the hole down along the side of the building to where a great round section of the wall lay near the bottom of the Dementor mound. "That's…impressive," he muttered to Sirius. "Partial Transfiguration?"

Sirius shrugged. "That's what he said. I've been meaning to ask him to explain but I don't think we've had a spare minute since we got out."

"A spare minute for what?" Harry asked from behind them.

"Explaining Partial Transfiguration," Remus said. "Albus told me once you could do it and I've been meaning to ask for a demonstration, but —" he gestured at the section of wall below them. "— I'd say that qualifies."

"Where do you think Hermione is?" Harry asked of no one in particular.

It was Sirius who answered. "The holding cells for prisoners bound over for trial is in section 2-A. Assuming the Aurors didn't act like complete assholes, that's probably where she's at. That means a long climb up this bitch."

Harry grimaced. "What if the Aurors were assholes?" he asked. "That means they could have put Hermione in any one of the cells between here and there, doesn't it?"

Sirius and Remus glanced at each other. "Well, yes," Remus admitted. "Or Malfoy could have ordered them to put her close to the Dementors."

"Shit," Harry muttered. "We'll have to check every cell on our way up."

"I will be able to locate her," Harry's Patronus, who had been floating above the three of them, spoke at last.

"Oh, yeah," Harry muttered, irritated that he should have remembered that on his own and hadn't. "Good."

Remus put a hand on Harry's shoulder to get his attention. "We shouldn't use magic, by the way — the Dementors can't detect us with your Patronus nearby, but they might be able to sense any magic we perform and warn the Aurors."

Harry looked up at the hole in the wall above them. "How are we getting up there without magic, then?"

"I've got that covered," Remus said, reaching into his robes and taking out a mokeskin pouch. He reached inside and said, "Rope ladder," and "magnetic bar," removing both items from the pouch. He attached the top of the rope ladder to two clasps on the bar, then handed one side to Sirius, pointing upward toward the hole. "Aim for just below the bottom lip," he instructed, and he and Sirius threw the bar upward.

The bar hit the wall a foot below the hole with a loud clang and stuck. "Now we simply climb up the rope," he told Harry and Sirius, smiling triumphantly. "No magic needed." A minute later the three of them were standing inside the hole Harry had made barely a day ago. Remus retrieved his rope and magnetic bar and returned them to his pouch. "We should start looking for Hermione," he said, unnecessarily.

"Like this?" Sirius asked. "What about Disillusionment Charms, at least?"

Remus folded his arms, looking thoughtful. "Harry, I noticed the Dementors don't seem to sense our presence," he said, gesturing to the dark-cloaked entities floating a dozen yards or so above them. "Is your Patronus preventing them from stealing our emotions?"

Harry nodded. "Even more than that — we become invisible to them, like we're not even here. They don't even seem to sense the Patronus except to avoid getting too near to it."

"If that's the case," Remus mused, "we might be able to cast some personal magic on ourselves without their noticing it. We can test that." He raised his wand over his head.

"Wait a second," Harry said, stopping him. "What if it doesn't work?"

"Then the Dementors will likely inform the Aurors in the control center that magic was performed somewhere in the prison, and they will investigate," Remus hypothesized. "But if they do not sense our presence then a magical spell performed only our persons will very likely not be sensed, either. Disillusionment isn't our best protection, but it's better than nothing."

Harry couldn't argue about that. He gestured for Remus to go ahead. The Chief Warlock tapped himself on the head. There was a sound like eggs cracking, and Remus faded from view. Harry looked up. The three Dementors still hovered above them, oblivious to their presence and seemingly to the magic that had just been performed.

"Looks like it worked," Sirius said, beaming. "Good job, Moony!" He took out his own wand and repeated the spell on himself. Harry did the same. In a few moments only the Patronus remained visible.

"All right, let's go," Harry said, and his Patronus began walking down the corridor to the main hallway of section 9-A, with the three wizards following it closely. As they walked, Harry noticed that the gas lamps along the walls were not lit; if it weren't for the light of his Patronus they would walking in complete darkness. That was not going to make things any easier for them, but at least they could see for now.

Only eight more levels, eight more trips around the perimeter of Azkaban, before they could find Hermione, get themselves and her out of here and somewhere safe, and Harry could begin to deal with Voldemort directly again.

=ooo=

Five figures appeared in the backyard of the Burrow amidst a whirlwind of color. A moment later the backdoor burst open and a tearful Molly Weasley rushed toward the group sobbing, "Ginny, oh Ginny!" She hugged both Ginny and Ron, who was still holding her, as Fred, George and Tonks stood smiling happily (and also a little sadly) at the scene.

All too soon, Molly stopped hugging and started talking, her manner suddenly brisk and efficient. "Alright, then. We need to get Ginny to safety right away. Can she walk?" she asked Ron.

"I can walk, Mum," Ginny said, her voice a raspy whisper. "Put me down, Ron." Ron complied, but still held onto her as her feet touched the ground. As he started to let her take her weight her legs began to wobble. She looked at Ron. "I think I need a Pepper-Up," she said, huskily.

"I have some in the house!" Molly said, turning to run inside.

"Never mind," Ginny called, her voice louder than before. Turning back to Ron, she said, "Hit me."

Ron grinned and punched her softly in the arm with his free hand. "Ha-ha," Ginny snarled. "You prat. Hit me with a Rennervate, doofus."

Smiling, Ron pulled out his wand and held the tip a few inches from her chest. "Rennervate," he said, and Ginny jerked as the spell took effect. She took a step away from Ron, but still held his shoulder.

"I think that's done it," she said, nodding. "Now, where are we going?"

"Come with me, dear," Molly said, putting an arm around Ginny to help her.

"Mum," Fred said, stopping her and Ginny. He turned to Tonks. "Maybe you should go with them," he suggested. "You might want to disappear for a while."

"Where are they going?" Tonks asked, warily.

"We set up a special place for Ginny to hide when we busted her out of Azkaban," Fred explained. "Mum's the Secret Keeper."

"Good advice," George told Tonks. "Can't imagine Malfoy will be happy with you, especially if he saw your name with ours on the Marauder's Map."

"Probably not," Tonks agreed unhappily. She looked torn about going into hiding. Finally, she sighed resignedly. "Okay, what the hell. I can keep Ginny company." She walked over to where Molly and Ginny were waiting for her and put an arm around Ginny as well, helping to support her.

"Don't worry, dear," Molly patted Tonks on the shoulder. "Everything will be fine, my boys will see to that. Now, let's get you and Ginny squared away." The three of them walked out into the back yard toward the old broom shack that stood behind their garden. Molly whispered something into Ginny's ear, then leaned behind her and whispered something to Tonks. Looking back at her sons, she made a spinning motion with her finger.

Fred and George immediately turned around, and Ron followed suit. When they looked back a minute later, the three women were gone.

"Well, that's that," Fred said happily, slumping with exhaustion. He rubbed his neck tiredly and looked at George. "D'you think Mum has any butterbeers in the —"

All hell broke loose again.

A dozen Aurors suddenly popped into existence around Fred, George and Ron, surrounding them. "Go!" Fred shouted, but when he tried to Disapparate he slammed into an Anti-Disapparition ward. He shook his head, dazed by the unpleasant sensation.

Several cries of "Expelliarmus!" and three wands flew into the air, leaving the Weasley brothers unable to attack, defend, or escape. They automatically put their backs to each other, ready to do something — anything — if any of the Aurors came close enough to them.

There were a few final Apparition cracks some distance away. A moment later Draco Malfoy stepped into the ring of Aurors surrounding them, followed by Crabbe and Goyle. "Here you are," he said with mock surprise. "You know, I thought I just saw your names on a certain piece of parchment you used to have. Would you know anything about that?"

Fred hesitated only a moment before letting his defensive posture flow into an elaborate half-bow directed toward Malfoy. "Evening, Minister," he said. "Nice of you to drop by. I see you brought a few friends with you. You saw our names on a piece of parchment, you say? I've no doubt you have many pieces of parchment with our names on them," he smiled.

Malfoy smiled as well. "It was a particular piece of parchment, as I'm sure you recall. It's titled 'The Marauder's Map.' Quite an interesting document, if I do say so — it shows the castle grounds and every being at Hogwart, whether they're living, a ghost, or whatever."

George and Ron frowned worriedly, but Fred's smile remained in place. "That's very interesting, Minister. But —" Fred leaned forward, a curious expression on his face. "How do you know that what this so-called Marauder's Map is showing you is real?"

Malfoy snorted derisively. "What would make you think it's not, Weasley?"

"Did the Hogwarts security system record that any of us were there?" Fred asked.

"No," Malfoy snapped. "But you designed the security system, probably using the Map!"

"If that were true, wouldn't our names have shown up in the security system, then?" Fred pointed out.

"Not if you keyed yourself into the system and told it to ignore you!"

Fred shrugged; he'd let Malfoy have that point. But — "For another thing," he went on, "Hogwarts is Unplottable, so you can't show its layout on a map."

"But it clearly does!" Malfoy argued. He took a blank piece of parchment out of his robes and shook it at Fred. "I saw your name appear on it!"

Fred chuckled. "You saw the words 'Fred Weasley' on a piece of parchment that's supposed to be of an Unplottable location. Come now, Minister — doesn't that sound a bit silly to you?"

"No," Malfoy growled. "I watched your name appear at the edge of the Map, then suddenly it was in the infirmary. All of your names, in fact," he added, pointing at George and Ron, who were now facing Malfoy behind Fred, grinning.

"But you can't Apparate within the grounds of Hogwarts," Fred merrily pointed out, enjoying this little cat-and-mouse game with Malfoy, keeping him distracted from his real mission here. "You should know that, Minister."

"You used a Portkey," Malfoy growled, not liking this game at all.

"Portkeys are warded, too," Fred shook his head. "How could we get through the wards?"

"It doesn't matter," Malfoy snarled dismissively. "We're not here to debate the hows or whys of the Marauder's Map —!"

"That's good, because you clearly don't know much about it," Fred retorted, deadpan. George and Ron both lowered their heads to smother their laughter.

"We're here," Malfoy said loudly, finally losing his patience, "to arrest you three, as well as Auror Nymphadora Tonks, on the charge of freeing a prisoner that was being held in the infirmary until she could be returned to prison — your sister, Ginevra Weasley Thomas. Where is she?"

Fred glanced back at Ron and George, both of whom just shrugged. "We don't know where she is," he told Malfoy.

"What about in there?" Malfoy asked, jerking a thumb at the Burrow. "You sure you don't know, Weasley? Because if you do and you don't tell us, it's obstruction of justice."

"What do you want me to do, chug a bottle of Veritaserum?" Fred sneered. "I really can't tell you where she is." Which was true enough; Fred knew there was a location protected by a Fidelius Charm, but he couldn't tell Malfoy anything about it — neither he, George nor Ron were the Secret Keeper.

"Where's your mother, Molly?" Malfoy asked.

"We don't know," Ron answered in an irritated tone. "Maybe you should go look for her!"

"Do you want to file a missing wizard report?" Malfoy asked, blandly. Without waiting for an answer he turned to his Auror Teams. "Search the house and the yard. I want Level Three searches on everything."

The three Weasley brothers were escorted to the edge of the Burrow's property to watch the searches unfold. "What do you think?" George muttered as they stood there just outside the perimeter established by the Aurors.

"Level Three is pretty thorough," Fred said softly, after checking that there were no Extendable Ears or other spy spells on them. "But it still won't find a Fidelius. I'm just glad none of us are the Secret Keeper — they can't make us take Veritaserum and force the location out of us."

"Hurray," Ron muttered. "It still looks like we'll be going to Azkaban ourselves."

"Man up, Ronnie," Fred said, giving him a disapproving glare. "Better us than Ginny." Ron nodded agreement, though he still wasn't happy about it.

A few minutes later the search looked to be winding down. Of course neither Ginny nor Molly had turned up in the search. Malfoy was conferring with his two right-hand goons, Crabbe and Goyle — probably with a Quietus Charm in place to prevent anyone from overhearing them.

"They look a bit miffed," George dryly observed.

"They don't like it much when they lose at hide-and-seek," Ron quipped.

"Their next move will be to interrogate us," Fred muttered, still keeping his voice low. "They've probably guessed a Fidelius is in place, but we don't want to give them any more information."

"We can't, can we?" Ron frowned. "I mean, it's a bloody Fidelius, for Merlin's sake! The magic prevents us from talking about it if anyone who doesn't know about it could hear us!"

"That's the idea," Fred agreed, "but stay on your toes anyway."

Two Aurors came over and walked the trio back to where Malfoy and his subordinates were standing. Malfoy appeared to be reading a report, but nobody believed he was really reading — it was more likely a ploy to psych out the Weasleys, who didn't appear to be falling for it.

Malfoy finally looked up at them. His expression was calm and collected, though his eyes — Fred watched the man's grey eyes as they stared at him and his brothers; there seemed to be no respect or compassion at all there. "Well, your sister and mum aren't here, of course," he said, quietly. "Nor is Auror Tonks, who we also saw was with you at Hogwarts."

"Maybe that's what that supposed Map showed you," Fred hedged. "But unless you can bring them to the Wizengamot all you have is us. And we don't know where any of them are."

"That remains to be seen," Malfoy replied. He stood quietly for several moments, rubbing his chin with an index finger, staring at the three Weasleys. "I might be wrong, but I think there's a Fidelius involved in all this. What do you think?" His grey eyes moved from Fred to George then back to Ron; if he was using Legilimency it was hard to tell, there was no wand in his hand.

The three brothers shook their heads and Fred answered for them. "You can think whatever you like, Malfoy, but we don't know where they are and we wouldn't tell you if we did. If that means you're going to take us in for obstruction of justice, do what you've gotta do."

"I suppose we could go that way," Malfoy murmured, waving a hand airily, "but I think we'll just dispense with the bureaucratic bullshit and get right down to it." He pointed at George. "Him first."

Goyle's wand was instantly out. "Crucio!" he shouted and George dropped to the ground, screaming in agony.

"Malfoy! WHAT THE FUCK?! STOP IT!" Both Fred and Ron were screaming at the Minister. They tried to charge forward into Goyle, to knock him down and stop the curse, but Impediment Jinxes from other Aurors held them back.

After about ten seconds Goyle raised his wand and George stopped screaming, though he was still gasping loudy as aftershocks of the pain reverberated in his brain. Malfoy was giving Fred an even look. "Want to tell us now where your sister and mum are?" he asked, expectantly.

"You maniac!" Fred screamed. "You can't use Unforgiveables on people!"

Malfoy smiled. "You don't think so, Weasley? Didn't you read that I reinstituted the Monroe Act when I took over as Minister? The Wizengamot approved it by a wide margin."

"You mean your father's bought-and-paid-for votes approved it," Fred snarled. He bent down to check on his broher. "All right there, George?" he asked quietly.

"Oh, yeah, I'm having a ball," George said, his voice barely a whisper.

"Ready to tell us where they are?" Malfoy asked. "Or do you need more convincing?"

Fred stood furiously, facing Malfoy. "I don't know!" he shouted angrily. "I'm not —" he hesitated. "I've got nothing to tell you," he finished.

Malfoy gestured toward Crabbe, who whipped out his wand and pointed it at Ron. "Crucio!" he cried, and Ron fell to the ground screaming.

"Stop! Stop!" Fred pleaded, watching helplessly as his youngest brother thrashed around on the ground. "Crucio me if you think I'm the Secret Keeper!"

"Who said I think that?" Malfoy asked, shrugging.

"Stop it! Stop it, you bastards!" A new voice made several Aurors spin around, their wands at the ready, where they saw Molly Weasley charging toward them from the backyard of the Burrow. "Leave them alone!"

Molly was quickly disarmed and captured, then brought to Malfoy. She glared defiantly up at him as he smiled condescendingly at her. "Mrs. Weasley, I'm so pleased you decided to join us. I hope you can put an end to this futile resistance your sons have been putting up in an effort to protect your daughter."

Molly was older and thinner, but she'd lost none of the temper she was famous for in her earlier days. "Malfoy, you horrid, pathetic little worm, how you ever managed to become Minister of Magic I'll never understand! In a month you've managed to set back years of progress in the Wizarding world! If you think you're ever going to see Ginny again you are sadly mistaken! She's safely away from your horrible prison and she's never going back!"

"I wouldn't be too sure of that," Malfoy said, coldly. He was infuriated by the tongue-lashing this old woman was giving him but none of it showed in his cool, calm demeanor. "I assume you are the Secret Keeper for your daughter's Fidelius hideaway?"

Molly hesitated a bare moment before answering. "Of course not!" she snapped. "Why would I come here if I knew you were looking for that person, assuming there is a Secret Keeper in the first place!"

"Well, we can easily find out," Malfoy said mildly, giving a nod to Crabbe.

The big Auror pointed his wand at Molly. "Crucio!"

Molly fell to the ground, screams ripped from her by the agonizing pain the Cruciatus Curse produced. The three Weasley brothers started to jump forward, but wands pointed at them from all directions forced them to stand still, watching in anguish as their mother suffered horribly.

After what seemed like an eternity Crabbe lowered his wand, leaving Molly sobbing in silence. "You know," Malfoy said casually, examining his fingernails, "I can have them keep this up all day. You'll probably go insane after a few minutes, but a few drops of Veritaserum might get you to tell where your daughter is hidden. And if not," he shrugged indifferently. "Well, she'll have to leave her hidey-hole eventually to get food, supplies, and so on, because everyone else here will be in Azkaban or St. Mungo's and won't be able to help her at all." Malfoy looked at the Aurors surrounding the Weasley brothers. "Let them go to her — this will probably be the last time they ever see her again."

The Aurors stepped back and the three brothers rushed to Molly's side. Fred knelt and lifted her head tenderly. Molly was trembling from the effects of the Cruciatus. George leaned close to her and whispered, "Mum, you can't take much more of that. Tell them I'm the Secret Keeper."

"No, me," Fred whispered in her other ear. "Tell them it's Fred."

"You know we can hear you morons whispering," Malfoy said, and several Aurors around him laughed derisively. "You'd better hurry up and agree on who the Secret Keeper is before we Crucio the lot of you and go to Plan B."

Ron looked up at Malfoy in rage. Without speaking he suddenly launched himself upward, swinging wildly, and one of his fists connected with Malfoy's nose, breaking it and making the Minister stagger back in pain.

Malfoy held his nose in both hands, shock and pain written across his face, as Ron watched him, teeth bared and arms ready to begin flailing again. Malfoy's eyes seemed to flash red for a moment before his hand moved. Faster than anyone imagined, his wand was out and he slashed it at Ron, screaming "Sectumsempra!"

Ron fell to the ground , a slash across his chest rapidly turning his shirt red. His left arm spun away, sliced at mid-forearm, and fell in the dirt. "Get him to St. Mungo's," Malfoy said painfully, cupping his nose with his free hand, and two Aurors took hold of Ron; one activated his emergency Portkey and the three of them vanished. Another Auror hurried forward and looked at Malfoy's injury, applying a quick spell to fix the nose. Malfoy irritably waved her away and looked down at Molly and the remaining Weasleys who were staring at him in horror.

"What have you done to Ron?" Fred whispered, mentally cringing at the memory of Ron's arm flopping to the ground.

"Will they be able to reattach that arm?" George asked anxiously, worried because it had been magically severed.

"I'm afraid not," Malfoy said coldly. "They'll be able to fix the wound to his chest, but the arm is gone forever." He touched his nose gingerly. "He shouldn't have attacked me, so he got what he deserved."

"What he deserved?!" Molly Weasley bolted upright despite still being weak from the Cruciatus. "You bloody bastard! If you want to talk about what's deserved you deserve to be chopped to bits and fed to a nundu!"

"That sounded like a threat," Malfoy said dangerously, pointing his wand at the Weasleys as a group. "I am no longer in the mood to hear threats —"

"All right, enough," a new voice said. Ginny Thomas and Tonks were standing just beyond the ring of Aurors watching Malfoy and the Weasley brothers.

Molly Weasley had heard her daughter's voice. "Ginny, noooo!" she moaned, covering her face with her hands.

"Sorry, Mum," Ginny said. "This has gone too far already." To Malfoy she said, "Alright, Minister, I'm here. Let my mum and brothers go."

Malfoy shook his head, looking very happy. "Can't do that, Thomas. They're guilty of aiding and abetting a convicted murderer. And so are you, Auror," he added, staring coldly at Tonks. "I'm very disappointed, as are your fellow Aurors, I'm sure."

"Give me a break," Tonks retorted hotly. "You're just happy these ball-less flobberworms didn't have the guts to stand up to you and your goonsquad for all the shit you've pulled the last —" her voice cut off as Malfoy pointed his wand at her.

"Very good," he said to the others assembled around him. "Now that we have Thomas back, we'll be taking her back to Azkaban." He looked at Fred, Ron and George. "I suppose you three can come along as well, to watch her go back in." He pointed to two junior Aurors. "Griffen, you and Blackthorne bring Molly Weasley to HQ, put her in one of the detention cells until I return. And you two," he said to Crabbe and Goyle, "take Auror Tonks back and put her in the most secure cell we have. With any luck, we should arrive at Azkaban just in time to see Harry Potter recaptured."

A dozen or or so Disapparition cracks later the back yard of Burrow stood empty once again.

=ooo=

"For a search and rescue mission," Sirius complained as he, Remus and Harry followed Harry's Patronus through level four of A-section, "this has all been pretty boring. And I'm getting pretty tired of being the pack mule of this group." He hefted the bolt cutters he'd been using to remove the locks from the doors along each section.

"Just be thankful I had those in my pouch," Remus retorted dryly. "And that we haven't had to use them yet." He shrugged. "It could have been a lot trickier, however — if I didn't have the bolt cutters we might've have to use the Universal Solvent Solution I have."

"You have Universal Solvent?" Harry asked, interestedly. They had been walking for several minutes along the A-spiral, following it upwards. So far none of the doors between sections had been locked or secured with a padlock. "Too bad we're going up. But it would have been very useful going down through this place."

"Probably," Remus agreed with a wry smile. "Especially if we wanted a hole below Azkaban reaching several miles deep in the Earth."

Harry shrugged. "That could be Plan B, I guess — weaken the ground beneath it enough to drop it into the Earth's mantle."

"But when it went," Sirius pointed out, "you'd go with it, plus everyone else in the place."

"Just details to be worked out," Harry muttered. He addressed his Patronus walking before them for the tenth time since beginning the walk up. "No sign of Hermione yet?"

"She is still above us," the Patronus answered. "Most likely she is section 2-A — I will know more precisely when we reach that level."

"Then all we have to do is get her out of her cell," Sirius said, hefting the bolt cutters he held, "and in all likelihood fight our way through a dozen or more Aurors. Piece of cake."

"Get that Universal Solvent ready," Harry said to Remus.

"We're not using the Solvent on Azkaban," Remus said.

A short pause.

"Unless we absolutely have to."

Harry smiled grimly. Their fight with half a dozen Aurors in the seventh-floor corridor of Hogwarts had been weird enough. He hoped to get Hermione out, make the walk back down to the lowest level, and get out the way they'd come in. So far their trip had been uneventful — they'd come upon no roving bands of Aurors nor had they heard any loud screaming from the inmates.

Which, come to think of it, was strange.

"Sirius, how often did the Aurors patrol the corridors when you were a prisoner?"

Sirius looked thoughtful for a moment. "I don't know… it didn't seem like they did it very often, maybe to distribute water or our meals."

"Either we arrived between anything like that," Harry mused, "or something is going on. Patronus, have you sensed the presence of anyone in any of these cells since we arrived?"

"No," the Patronus confirmed, "but the deepest level that contained prisoners the last time we were here was level 5, and Ginny was the only prisoner being held on that level. However, I sense no prisoners on this level or level Three of any of the spirals. The prisoners may have been moved after our escape."

"Or before our arrival, perhaps?" Harry hypothesized.

"It is possible," the Patronus agreed. "We should exercise caution."

"That's the understatement of the year," Sirius snorted.

"Can you determine the location of the Aurors here?" Harry asked the Patronus.

"Not without getting close enough to them for their own Patronuses to notice me," the Patronus answered. "If Hermione is in level Two they may notice me anyway. It could be difficult to return the way we came if the Aurors lock down the prison and give chase."

"That Universal Solvent is starting to look like an option," Sirius quipped.

Remus shook his head. "If you're thinking it'll just eat a big hole in all the floors between here and the bottom of Azkaban, it doesn't work that way. It would need to be bound into a circular area as it eats its way through the metal — I don't know how well that will work. And if anyone gets in its way…" Remus just shook his head. "The final problem would be lowering someone almost 800 feet using a Levitation Charm. And there will be four of us, counting Hermione."

"One complication at a time, please," Harry muttered tiredly, rubbing his temples. "I could sure use —" he cut himself off before finishing.

"Use what?" Sirius asked curiously.

"A drink," Harry finished, though that wasn't what he was thinking. He was about say he could sure use James Monroe's help getting Hermione, Sirius, Remus and himself out of here. But Remus had convinced him that seeing Monore had only been some kind of hallucination or delusion. They would have to get out of Azkaban on their own.

"No drinking until we're safely out of here," Remus said with a smile. "No use impairing yourself on top of what we've already got to deal with."

They passed through section Three without incident and made their way toward the entrance of section 2-A.

As they approached the door, however, the Patronus began to dim in intensity, becoming almost silver-gray as he stopped in front of the door leading to the section.

"I sense humans on the other side of the door," it said, speaking softly, "in the main corridor as well as in the cells of this section. Their Patronuses are nearby but not within the section itself, probably to hide their presence from you. I have reduced my output so they will not feel any additional relief from the Dementors."

"I can tell," Sirius muttered in a low voice. "I can feel them."

But Harry shook his head. "I don't. I think you just think you feel them, Sirius."

"Be that as it may," Remus put in. "We are at a stalemate unless we find a way to neutralize them and get Hermione —" he glanced at the Patronus "— I assume one of the people in the next section is Hermione."

"Yes," the Patronus nodded. "And the Weasley brothers Fred and George, and their sister Ginny Thomas as well," it added, surprisingly.

"Well, that tears it," Sirius grumbled resignedly. "If they caught the Weasleys they have to be onto us as well, don't they? What do we do now?"

"I wish you'd stop asking that question," Harry said, irritably. After a moment he looked at the Chief Warlock. "Er — so what do we do, Remus?"

Sirius snorted a laugh but covered his mouth to keep quiet. Harry spared him a momentary glare then looked Remus again, who was rubbing his chin thoughtfully. After several seconds of thinking Remus shrugged and said, "No idea."

Harry palmed his face. "I really don't know, Harry," Remus added apologetically. He turned to the Patronus. "What can you tell us about any Aurors on the other side of this door, if anything?"

"Aurors are positioned in the far two corners of the corridor," the Patronus answered. "But they seem to be near the ceiling, not the floor. I do not sense any magical spells on them other than Disillusionment, so they are probably using broomsticks. They have the advantage of position from which to cast spells, but are vulnerable to an attack that renders their brooms inoperative."

"Broomsticks," Harry repeated. "If we can get ahold of those broomsticks they might be useful to us."

"All eight cells of the middle cellblock are occupied, but four of the cells have Aurors Polyjuiced to look like Hermione, Ginny and the Weasley brothers," the Patronus continued. "The actual prisoners are Disillusioned and Body-Bound so they cannot call or signal for help. And I can sense at least two dozen more Aurors in the control section above us, 1-A."

"They're probably awaiting confirmation that we're here before they deploy more Aurors," Remus surmised. "So the first inkling these guys get that anything is amiss and we're probably going to be inundated by Aurors and Hit Wizards." He turned to Harry. "I suppose trying again another day is not an option?"

"No," Harry said shortly. "We'll never have a better chance than we do right now — they'll always be expecting us from this point on, and security is only going to get tighter. Not to mention the fact that Hermione and three of the Weasleys are imprisoned in here, and I don't think Malfoy will let any of them have a fair trial now. Especially since you're compromised now as well, Remus." Harry looked down at the floor. "I'm sorry for that, it wasn't what I —"

"Don't worry about it," Remus replied gently. "I may have some political tricks I can bring to bear against Malfoy."

"Speaking of tricks," Harry went on, nodding to the mokeskin pouch on Remus's belt. "I think it's time to delve into your bag of tricks and see what we can come up with to free Hermione and the Weasleys."

=ooo=

Nearly fifteen minutes later Harry and the two Marauders had come up with a plan of attack. To keep noise down during their work they each cast a Quietus Charm on themselves; their voices and any noise made by an object they held would not be heard by anyone other than the individual. To communicate, Remus handed out Extendable Ears to each of them; to speak to one another they would grasp the listening end of the Ear and hold it — the other end, in one of their ears, would be able to pick up the sounds they made but no one else could.

The plan wasn't complicated, but what it lack in complexity it more than made up in danger. Remus had taken his bottle of Universal Solvent, two globes of Sunlight Potion, a potion Harry had used during Quirrell's battle games in his first year, three green goggles, and his bottle of Soverign Glue from his pouch.

Now they just had to take out the Aurors guarding the far end of the corridor, neutralize the Aurors pretending to be Hermione and the Weasleys, free the actual prisoners, prevent the Aurors in the control level from coming after them, and get the hell out of here with everybody safe. Like Sirius had said earlier, a piece of cake.

Remus was holding Harry and Sirius's Extendable Ears. "We can assume that, even if the lamps are on in the next section the brightness of the Sunlight globes will be enough to dazzle the Aurors." Each of them were wearing the green goggles that would filter out most of the purple-white light of the globes. "When they break they will spill the light enclosed inside. Harry, you and Remus will Stun them and retrieve their brooms.

"Put them on the other side of the corridor door leading out of 2-A then use this —" he handed Harry the bottle of Sovereign Glue "— on the door to seal it shut. Then come back to the cell block where Hermione and the others are.

"Now here's the part I don't like," Remus admitted. "Sirius, when you get back to the cell block door I'll cancel the Unbreakable Charm on the Universal Solvent. You then throw the bottle, making sure it's far enough away from us that none of it splatters on anyone! That's going to eat a hole in all the floors of the prison, probably down to the Earth's mantle if not further. It will take a little while to get through all the metal floors, which will give us time to do what we're going to do next.

"If the Aurors haven't rushed out of their cells pretending to be the prisoners who've conveniently escaped while we're breaking them out —" Remus smiled ironically "— we can have Harry's Patronus identify who's in each cell. We will seal the Aurors in the cells, release Hermione, Fred, George and Ginny, and use the brooms we've captured to fly down to the bottom level and Portkey out of the central pit, hopefully before the Solvent has reached the mantle and molten rock comes shooting up from the hole it made, providing a distraction for our escape."

Sirius was smiling broadly. "Easy as cake," he said, holding onto Remus and Harry's Ear ends. Harry palmed his face again, while Remus just shook his head.

"Glad you think so," Remus said dryly. "Are you ready?"

"I was born rea —"

"Right," Remus said, cutting Sirius off. He placed the two globes of Sunlight Potion on the floor. "Just be careful not to swallow these things."

"Ready, Harry?" Remus asked. Harry nodded, not bothering with the Extendable Ears.

Sirius dropped to the floor, transforming to his Animagus dog form. He picked up the two globes in hi mouth and positioned himself next to the door. Harry got behind him, smiling at the green goggles Sirius was still wearing, and Remus stepped behind the door, taking hold of the handle.

Remus yanked the door open and both Sirius and Harry charged into the corridor, Harry with his wand at the ready to counter any curses coming from the Disillusioned Aurors. The gas lamps were on in this corridor, which would have alerted them if they'd simply walked in, but they probably would have been Stunned or immobilized before they could mount a defense. Red bolts shot from the upper far corners of the corridor, as expected, and Harry batted them aside.

Sirius had pulled away from Harry, running twice as fast as he could, and as he crossed the midpoint of the corridor he leapt into the air, transforming and spitting out the Sunlight globes, then catching them in either hand. He windmilled his arms, throwing the globes toward the corners of the room. A red bolt shattered one globe, scattering dazzlingly bright purpule-white light in the air; the other globe hit an invisible object and exploded into another mini-sunburst.

There were twin thuds as two bodies hit the floor. Harry sent Stunners into one corner while Sirius targeted the other; after a few shots apiece the unconscious bodies of the Aurors appeared. Harry spared a quick glance over his shoulder to make sure Remus was guarding the cell block where Hermione and the others were.

Running up to the two unconscious men Harry began feeling around on the floor for broomsticks. Following his lead Sirius did the same in the other corner. After several seconds Harry found what felt like a broomstick and cast the counter for the Disillusionment Charm on it. Sirius had already found his and slid the broom along the metal floor toward Remus, then Levitated the unconscious Auror and began moving him toward the section door marked 1-A.

"Come on, Harry," Sirius laughed as he canceled his Quietus spell, seeing Harry was slower than him. "Let's get this show on the road." He pushed open the door.

"Sirius, wait!" Harry hissed. "Did you check the other side for —"

A Stunbolt flashed through the open doorway, slamming into Sirius's chest and knocking him to the ground. Another Stunner, aimed for Harry, was deflected by him as he jumped on the broom he'd just captured and took to the air. It had been a while since he'd been on a broom but it was still very familiar to him. Just below the ceiling he stopped and spun around, pointing his wand at the open door. "Accio door!" he shouted, but the door didn't budge. Another Stunner narrowly missed him and Harry spun again, flying the broom toward where Remus was firing Stunners of his own toward the door.

"Quick, inside!" Harry shouted, slashing his wand at the padlock on the cellblock door. The padlock fell apart and Harry grabbed the handle, yanking the door open to provide a barrier against the curses coming from the other end of the section.

Remus dashed inside the door, and Harry pulled it shut, reaching into his pocket and pulling the bottle of Sovereign Glue. He applied a thin line of the material along the top and on each side of the door.

"What happened?" Remus asked in a low voice.

"They must've been waiting for us," Harry whispered back. "Sirius didn't check the other side of the door!" He looked around wildly. "Where's my Patronus?"

"It vanished while you were fighting the Aurors," Remus said. "I thought you sent it somewhere."

"No. I must've gotten too distracted," Harry groaned. "I've got to get it back —"

Four cell doors flew open and Hermione, Fred, George and Ginny rushed out. Except the weren't really who they were supposed to be — Harry could tell by the wands in their hands.

"Don't move, Potter!" Fred's Polyjuice twin shouted, and both Remus and Harry looked at each other for a bare moment before silently agreeing they were outmatched and raised their hands in the air, giving up. As the Aurors warily approached them, out of the side of his mouth Remus muttered, "Time for Plan B."

Harry started to laugh, but a Stunner from an Auror wand dropped him to the floor and everything went black.

=ooo=

Sometime later Harry, Sirius and Remus found themselves bound and seated in the control section of Azkaban, surrounded by Aurors and, worst of all, being lectured by Minister Malfoy, who was enjoying himself immensely.

"What I cannot believe, Potter," Malfoy was saying, "is that you managed to corrupt the Chief Warlock to your nefarious plans. It was unlikely enough that you got a long-term prisoner like Black to help you, but the Chief Warlock? I am amazed and disappointed with you, Lupin," Malfoy shook his head in mock sadness.

"Maybe if you hadn't kept sending in your supposedly-dead lackey, Peter Pettigrew, to torment me we wouldn't have figured out what you were up to," Harry replied.

Malfoy chuckled. "Pettigrew? Really? The man's been dead for 35 years now, Potter, and you're going to try to resurrect him to make me look bad?" He grinned wolfishly. "Who else do you plan to resurrect? James Monroe perhaps, the man you murdered?"

Harry didn't respond to that, but Sirius spoke up. "We'll find out the truth soon enough at the retrial, when you question me under Veritaserum."

Malfoy's eyebrows shot up. "Why would we have a retrial, exactly? Because the Chief Warlock planned to call for one? The man who aided and abetted you after you escaped from prison? I don't think you should look forward to that trial, Mr. Black — you're going back into a cell. After we've made some modifications to remove the windows that made it easier for you to escape. And after your Animagus form has been neutralized." Sirius paled upon hearing that.

Malfoy looked at Remus. "You, on the other hand, will be given a trial before the Wizengamot, Mr. Lupin, as soon as we've found a Chief Warlock pro tem. That may be a little difficult, you understand, since we've never done anything like that before."

"Maybe you should consider the position, Malfoy," Lupin answered tightly. "Since you already hold the positions of Head Auror and Minister of Magic now."

"Perhaps I will," Malfoy said, smilling. He turned to Harry. "And you, Potter. All that running around rescuing Ginny Thomas and sending my men on wild goose chases ended up for naught, didn't it? Now she's back in prison, and her brothers Fred and George are awaiting their own trials, while Ron Weasley will end up missing an arm for the rest of his life."

"Because of your dark spell," Harry snapped. "You should be on trial for that, if nothing else!"

"The Monroe Act authorizes Aurors to use dark spells, including the Unforgiveables, if required to in the line of duty," Malfoy pointed out. "And as Mr. Lupin rightly stated, I am still acting in the capacity of Head Auror."

"Good work, everyone," Malfoy turned, addressed the Aurors present. "We're taking Lupin back to the Ministry — I'll want him tried by the Wizengamot as soon as possible. To those on duty here at Azkaban, make sure Black and Potter are locked away as securely as possible. Dismissed!"

As the Aurors dispersed to go about their duties, Malfoy took one of the long-time Azkaban guards by the arm and drew him aside to speak privately. "I'm a little concerned about Potter," he told the man, one of the few he trusted to do his bidding just as Crabbe and Goyle did. "He's been entirely too much trouble these past few days."

The Auror nodded agreement. "I wonder if I should arrange for one of the Dementors to Kiss him?" he suggested.

"Too obvious," Malfoy shook his head. "What about that cell I had you set up? Have you used it on anyone yet?"

"No, sir." The Auror smiled evilly. "I understand. It will look like an accident. If there's an investigation we can blame it on the maintenance — in the worst case a house-elf can be blamed for being negligent."

"Good," Malfoy agreed. "You're about due for a bonus," he smiled.

"I'll take care of it," Auror Lesath Lestrange told him. He nodded slowly. "It will be a pleasure, sir. I've been waiting for a chance to pay Potter back for a long time."

"Really?" Malfoy was mildly interested. "What did he do to you?"

"It's not what he did," Lestrange answered. "It's what he didn't do."

If Malfoy was puzzled by the cryptic response he didn't react. "Carry on," was all he said.

A few quick orders to subordinate Aurors and Harry was suddenly pulled to his feet and led away followed by protests and questions from Remus and Sirius, taken to the C-spiral, section 2-C, and placed in a cell that looked every bit as nice as the holding cells in 2-A. The cot and mattress in the cell was new, and the sink and toilet were both in pristine shape. There were even two gas lamps in the upper corners of the room on either side of the door. The two Aurors pushed him into the cell, one saying "Enjoy your stay, murderer," before spitting on the floor and slamming the door closed.

Harry looked around the room. The windows in the side walls weren't present in this cell, but they hadn't been in the holding cells in 2-A, either. Apparently that had only been done in the regular cells. Harry sat on the bed, bouncing up and down on the mattress. It was not very soft but it was better than sleeping on a bare cot. There was even a blanket and sheets on the bed! That was rather unusual, Harry thought — he would have expected a bare room with nothing in it at all rather than "V.I.P." accomdations like this for him.

Harry wasn't sure how long he sat there before the cell door began to open — he noticed that it lacked a viewing window and a food door, unlike the cell he'd been in before — another unusual difference. An Auror carrying a food tray with a cup and bowl on it stepped into the room. "Figured we'd better feed you," he said gruffly. "You won't be getting fed again until tomorrow — we can't have you being mistreated, can we?" He laughed, setting the tray on the floor and backing out of the room, closing the door which made a strange squelching noise as it sealed shut, reminding Harry of an Inperturbable Charm.

Harry hadn't moved or spoken while the Auror was in the room. He stood, slowly, and walked over to the tray, picking it up and looking at the food in the bowl. Stew again, and lukewarm water to drink. He eyed the food suspiciously; if Malfoy wanted him dead there were any number of poisons he might have added to the food somehow. He walked back to his bed, setting the tray on the small table next to the cot, and began to think about what his next move should be.

There weren't many options, of course.

Not only was he, Sirius and Ginny back in Azkaban for murders they didn't commit, but Malfoy had put Hermione in as well, trying to force Harry to surrender. And Fred, George and Remus were now accused of crimes that would land them in Azkaban as well, assuming they were even tried for those crimes! Harry was wandless again, exhausted, and even though there were only a few Dementors left in the prison, depressed and unable to work up any determination to free himself and the others. He wasn't sure how it could get much worse. He rubbed his eyes tiredly, wondering if he should try to get some sleep before trying to figure out his next move — the room was becoming dimmer, as if he were about to fall asleep sitting up on his cot.

Glancing up at the gas lamps, Harry watched them for several seconds. It wasn't his eyes that were going out — it was the lamps! As he watched they dimmed considerablely then winked out. What was this, lights out for the night?

Then he heard the sound.

It was barely audible, but Harry could hear a soft hissing sound. At first he wondered if they had set a snake loose in the cell, perhaps a poisonous one, but the sound was far too steady and regular to be a live snake. Then he smelled it, too — the smell of gas. The lamps had gone out, but the gas was still on, and it seemed to be building up in the cell. Harry reached beneath his cot, where the small vent hole that pushed air into the room, but he felt air flowing out through the hole, not in.

So that was it. Malfoy was going to kill him by asphyxiation, by replacing the air in the room with gas he couldn't breathe. Harry sighed, defeated. He could pound on the cell door, but what Auror was going to respond to him? "All the things I've been through," he muttered to himself. "And now to die in Azkaban, not from Dementors sucking the life from me or in a firefight with Aurors, but from breathing natural gas…

Harry stared helpless into the dark. Without a wand there was nothing he could do about his predicament except wait for unconsciousness and death to claim him. Maybe if he hadn't lost half of his intelligence he could have come up with something to get himself out of this. As things stood, however, without a miraculous save, somehow, he was doomed.

Harry sighed. "Where's Luke Skywalker when you really need him?"

=ooo=

A/N: This chapter begins the end of this story. I will release a new chapter each Friday until the conclusion. I hope you enjoyed reading Methods of Chaos and ask that you leave a review, however short, letting me know what you think of these final few chapters.